<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <item>
            <title>
                U.S. EPA Recognizes SAMSUNG Electronics America&#039;s Commitment to Helping Consumers Lead a Greener Digital Lifestyle
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J. - April 1, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America</b>, a market leader and award-winning innovator in consumer electronics and telecommunications, today announced two important achievements as a result of its relationship with the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) and the U.S. Department of Energy (DOE), and its continued commitment to responsible environmental stewardship. Samsung has been named as an award recipient for Excellence in Product Labeling from the EPA and DOE's ENERGY STAR program. Samsung's ENERGY STAR accomplishments were recognized at an awards ceremony in Washington, D.C. yesterday. In addition, Samsung has become an official member of the EPA's SmartWay<sup>SM</sup> Transport Partnership, as a shipping participant. <br><br>"Samsung is committed to helping consumers lead a greener digital lifestyle, whether it is making the identification of energy-efficient products easy, or taking the necessary steps for the environmentally friendly transport of those products," said <b>Kris Narayanan, director of marketing for Samsung Electronics America</b>. "We are honored to work with the EPA and DOE, both as a SmartWay Partner and ENERGY STAR award recipient, to further our collective commitment to advancing environmental initiatives within the electronics industry." <br><br>Samsung has been recognized for Excellence in Product Labeling as part of the ENERGY STAR program, a joint initiative between the EPA and U.S. Department of Energy to promote energy-saving products. This award recognizes important contributions to raising ENERGY STAR visibility among consumers through consistent, high-profile placement of the ENERGY STAR logo on select, energy-efficient products. The ENERGY STAR Awards for Excellence in Product Labeling are given to organizations to recognize their efforts to improve energy efficiency and reduce greenhouse gas emissions, resulting in significant cost savings to consumers. Award winners are selected from more than 12,000 organizations that participate in the ENERGY STAR program. Last year alone, Americans with the help of ENERGY STAR initiatives saved $19 billion on their energy bills and reduced greenhouse gas emissions equivalent to those of 29 million vehicles.<br><br>Samsung, which holds the #1 marketshare in LCD HDTVs in the U.S., has been an ENERGY STAR partner since 1996, demonstrating the company's commitment to helping consumers lead a greener digital lifestyle through the creation of energy-efficient electronics. These products not only reduce power consumption, but also save consumers money. In 2008, Samsung helped consumers save more than $50 million in energy costs with its ENERGY STAR products. In 2009, more than 600 Samsung models across its product categories will meet or exceed ENERGY STAR guidelines, including all Samsung HDTVs, dishwashers and washing machines. <br><br>"Widespread, consistent use of the ENERGY STAR label is critical to helping consumers find quality, energy-efficient products," said<b> Kathleen Hogan, Director of the Climate Protection Partnerships Division at the U.S. EPA</b>. "Samsung's dedication to placing the ENERGY STAR label on all qualifying products helps consumers identify products that not only save energy and money, but also help combat climate change." <br><br>Samsung also recognizes the impact that the freight transport of its products to their end destination has on the environment. That is why Samsung has become part of the SmartWay Partnership. SmartWay is an innovative partnership with the EPA that reduces greenhouse gases and other air pollutants, improves fuel efficiency and recognizes partners for setting and achieving greenhouse gas reduction goals in freight transport. As a shipping partner, Samsung will, among other activities:<br><br>-	Determine the percentage of freight shipped (or received) by SmartWay Transport Partnership carriers <br>-	Measure the greenhouse gas emissions of freight facility operations using EPA's FLEET Performance Model -Shipper Module<br>-	Increase the percentage of freight shipped (or received) with SmartWay Transport Partnership Carriers on the FLEET Performance Model, and identify a goal to reduce the greenhouse gas emissions of freight facility operations<br>-	Report progress toward achieving each of these goals to EPA annually<br><br>"I am pleased to welcome Samsung to the SmartWay Transport Partnership," said<b> Marge T. Oge, Director of the Office of Transportation and Air Quality, EPA</b>. "They join the Partnership in a commitment to increase fuel efficiency and make freight-related environmental improvements."<br><br>For more information about Samsung's environmental initiatives, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>. <br><br><b>About ENERGY STAR</b><br>ENERGY STAR was introduced by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency in 1992 as a voluntary market-based partnership to reduce greenhouse gas emissions through increased energy efficiency. Today, in partnership with the U.S. Department of Energy, ENERGY STAR offers businesses and consumers energy-efficient solutions to save energy, money and help protect the environment for future generations. More than 12,000 organizations are ENERGY STAR partners committed to improving the energy efficiency of products, homes, buildings and businesses. For more information about ENERGY STAR, visit www.energystar.gov or call toll-free 1-888-STAR-YES (1-888-782-7937).<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, is a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. The company markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products, as well as oversees all of Samsung's North American operations including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. As a result of its commitment to innovation and unique design, the Samsung organization is one of the most decorated brands in the electronics industry. The company was ranked #6 in the Electronics Industry segment in Fortune Magazine's "Most Admired Companies 2008," and named as one of Fast Company's "Fast 50 Most Innovative Companies of 2008." Among popular BusinessWeek rankings, the company ranked #26 in the publication's "Most Innovative Companies of 2008" and #21 in the "100 Best Global Brands" for 2007.  Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is also a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2007.  Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> for more information.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Tops Brand Keys Customer Loyalty Study for Eighth Straight Year
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>DALLAS - March 2, 2009 - Samsung Telecommunications America (Samsung Mobile)</b> announced today that for an unprecedented eighth year in a row, the company has been recognized by the <b>Brand Keys Customer Loyalty Engagement Index</b> as No. 1 in customer loyalty in the cell phone category. Since 2001, Samsung continues to be the only wireless handset provider to be awarded this honor for consecutive years. <br><br>The 12th annual national survey identifies brands that are best able to engage consumers by meeting or exceeding their expectations, which creates loyal customers. The report accurately predicts which products consumers are most likely to purchase over the next 12 to 18 months. In the cell phone category, consumer preferences were based on wireless phone design and performance. <br><br>"Winning this award is very important to Samsung because it means we're creating an emotional tie with the people who buy our phones," said <b>Bill Ogle, Chief Marketing Officer at Samsung Telecommunications America</b>.  "This award is proof that more and more people value and recognize Samsung Mobile as a quality brand each year."<br><br>Brand Keys is the only research consultancy in the world that specializes in customer loyalty, providing brand-equity measures that accurately predict future consumer behavior. Findings from the index rank brands based on those that consumers felt best met or exceeded their expectations and were most likely to demonstrate the highest levels of consumer loyalty and profitability over the coming two years. <br><br>"This award is a great tribute to the Samsung brand. The results of this year's Customer Loyalty Engagement Index clearly indicate that the formula consumers use to calculate brand differences and, more importantly, to decide which brands to buy and remain loyal to, have increased the contribution that the overall "value perception" makes. This year's findings indicate that shopper-consciousness has shifted from a personal responsibility to ferret out the deals, to a brand responsibility to provide them, and in tough category and for eight years in a row, Samsung has done that better than the competition," said <b>Robert Passikoff, Brand Keys founder and president</b>.<br><br>For more information about the 2009 Brand Keys Customer Loyalty Awards, please visit <a hrefg="http://www.brandkeys.com/awards" target="_blank">www.brandkeys.com/awards</a>. <br><br><b>About Samsung Telecommunications America</b><br>Samsung Telecommunications America, LLC, a Dallas-based subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., researches, develops and markets wireless handsets and telecommunications products throughout North America. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsungwireless.com</b>. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Electronics America Announces Senior Management Transitions
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J. - January 23, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America</b>, today announced the appointment of <b>Chang-Soo Choi</b> to the position of President and Chief Executive Officer, replacing <b>Dong Jin Oh</b> who is retiring after a successful 35-year career with Samsung and is now considering a leadership role in a non-profit social contribution organization in Korea.   Also announced were the promotions of Tim Baxter as President of Samsung's Consumer Electronics Division (CED), and <b>Young Hoon Eom </b>as Co-President of CED replacing Jae-Soon Park.<br><br>"Along with the entire staff of Samsung Electronics America, it is my great pleasure to welcome Chang-Soo Choi to the organization," said Dong-Jin Oh, retiring President and Chief Executive Officer.  "It has been an honor and privilege to lead Samsung Electronics America during its rise to prominence and multi-category leadership in the North American marketplace.  Under the guidance of Choi and his team of exceptionally-talented division Presidents and senior executives, Samsung Electronics America is well-positioned for continued growth and success in the years ahead."<br><br>Over the past 30 years Choi has served in a variety of leadership roles within Samsung Electronics' Telecommunications, Information Systems and Computer Systems Divisions in Korea.  Most recently he served as Executive Vice President in the Mobile Communication Division in Korea where he was responsible for leading international sales and marketing for the world's #2 mobile phone manufacturer.  In his new role as President and CEO at Samsung Electronics America, Choi will be responsible for leading the company's North American operations which include the Consumer Electronics and Information Technology Divisions within Samsung Electronics America (SEA), Samsung Telecommunications America (STA), Samsung Electronics Canada (SECA), and Samsung Electronics Mexico (SEM). Choi is expected to assume his new role in February. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, is a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. The company markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products, as well as oversees all of Samsung's North American operations including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. As a result of its commitment to innovation and unique design, the company was ranked #6 in the Electronics Industry segment in Fortune Magazine's "Most Admired Companies 2008," and named as one of Fast Company's "Fast 50 Most Innovative Companies of 2008." Among popular BusinessWeek rankings, the company ranked #26 in the publication's "Most Innovative Companies of 2008" and #21 in the "100 Best Global Brands" for 2007.  Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is also a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2007.  Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> for more information.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Company </b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solution. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Showcases Its Award Winning Home Appliances At CES 2009
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>LAS VEGAS, January 7, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America, Inc</b>., a market leader and award-winning innovator in consumer electronics and home appliances, displays its latest award winning home appliance offerings at the 2009 International CES tradeshow. These exciting products include a <b>French Door Refrigerator </b>with 7" LCD Touch Screen and a <b>Front Loading Washer</b>, with  a Steam Dryer and  the quietest wash at top spin speeds available.. The French Door Refrigerator is a CES Innovations 2009 Design and Engineering Award honoree, and the Front Loading Washer is a recipient of the CES Innovations 2009 Eco-design Award.<br><br>"We are honored that CEA has awarded two of our pillar home appliance products with this esteemed industry recognition," said<b> James Politeski, vice president of Home Appliance sales and marketing at Samsung Electronics America</b>. "As an award-winning home appliance company, Samsung is committed to technology and innovation that can make a big difference in consumers' lives. Both our French Door Refrigerator and Front Loading Washer attest to this commitment."<br><br><b>RFG299 French Door Refrigerator</b> <br>The new RFG299 French Door Refrigerator includes a convenient 7" LCD touch screen above the ice and water dispenser and delivers the industry's largest internal storage at 28.5 cu. ft. in a standard footprint.<br><br>Understanding that the kitchen is the true heart of the home, Samsung developed the LCD touch screen to give consumers easy access to calendars, schedules, showcase photos, nutrition facts, and unit conversions, allowing the refrigerator to act as an interactive, digital lifestyle centerpiece. <br><br>The RFG299 French Door Refrigerator's larger interior capacity is made possible by high-rate urethane insulation technology, which reduces the refrigerator walls from 2.04 inches to 1.38 inches. This results in an extra 3.5 cubic feet or 14 percent more storage space. Despite the extra internal space, the RFG299's overall physical size remains the same and provides quality cooling without the need for a new kitchen layout. <br><br>Along with its breakthrough technical advancements, the RFG299 French Door Refrigerator features smart engineering elements that combine to create an ideal refrigerator solution. For example, the fridge's interior LED lighting is extremely bright and Samsung's EZ-Open™ Handle allows easy opening of freezer doors, eliminating the need to strain. The attractive-styled exterior door handles, hidden hinges and stainless steel finish will also add a touch of hi-end taste to any kitchen.<br><br>In addition, Samsung has been named by J.D. Power in the 2008 Home Appliance Study as the brand ranked highest in customer satisfaction for Side-by-Side/French Door Refrigerators. Samsung excelled in the areas of performance, ease of use, styling/feel, and operational features. This marked the fourth year in a row that Samsung has received the prestigious customer satisfaction award from J.D. Power for refrigerators. <br><br><b>WF448 Front-Loading Washer </b><br>Not to be outdone by its home appliance siblings, the Samsung 448 front-loading washer line is the first to offer an extra large capacity of 4.5 cu. ft., which can result in fewer loads. Utilizing Samsung's VRT™ technology, the front-loading washer line significantly reduces the noise and vibration commonly associated with other front-loading washers, making it the quietest washer at top spin speeds currently available. This allows the washer to be set up and used in more convenient, easily-accessible locations, , or in compact living areas without being a distraction.<br><br>The 448 line also offers a steam cycle available on the front-loading washer along with the option to add steam to conventional cycles, plus select Steam Refresh and Odor Removal in the dryer. There's also gentler fabric care abilities made possible by Diamond Drum, a diamond-shaped washing surface with smaller drain holes, helping to prolong the life of delicate and fragile clothing by reducing fabric snags.  The 448 line also features a 1300 RPM maximum spin speed and Samsung's SilverCare™ cycle option, which is an uncompromising solution for washing delicates and colors. The SilverCare™ feature also saves 92 percent on energy when compared to hot water sanitization, resulting in a home appliance that's much more environment-friendly.<br><br>Offered in a Stainless Platinum finger print-free true metallic finish and traditional Neat White, the Samsung 448 line is much more than your average collection of home appliances - they are indeed fashion statements.  <br><br>Both the RFG299 and WF448 are just part of Samsung's entire line of kitchen appliances, which also include ranges, over-the-range microwave ovens, and dishwashers. For more information please visit: <a href="http://www.samsung.com/homeppliances" target="_blank">www.samsung.com/homeppliances</a>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, digital consumer electronics and home appliance products, including HDTVs, home theater systems, MP3 players, digital imaging products, refrigerators and washing machines.  A recognized innovation leader in consumer electronics design and technology, Samsung is the HDTV market leader in the U.S.  Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> for more information.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG'S Innovation Further Demonstrates Its Commitment To The Environment
            </title>
            <description>
                
                <![CDATA[
                    LAS VEGAS - January 7, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America, Inc., a market leader and award-winning innovator in consumer electronics, today announced a number of award-winning products and technologies that are designed to contribute to the growth of ‘greener' consumer electronics and appliances industries. Samsung's new products include innovations that reduce the impact upon our natural resources, and help consumers lessen their environmental footprint while enjoying the best available digital entertainment and home life experiences. Samsung's new products will be on display at <b>Booth #11033 </b>during the International Consumer Electronics Show, to be held at the Las Vegas Convention Center, January 8 through 11.<br><br> "More than ever before, it is paramount that we create products that meet the expectations and preferences of consumers in ways that reduce environmental impact without sacrificing quality, design or ease of use," said <b>DJ Oh, President and CEO, Samsung Electronics America</b>. "Our dedication to delivering on these principles can be seen throughout our manufacturing operations, the energy efficiency of our products, and our end-of-life recycling programs such as SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECTSM.  We are very proud of our environmental contributions, especially in our groundbreaking new line of LED HDTVs, ultra-slim plasma HDTVs, and the 448-series of front-loading washers." <br><br><b>Energy- Efficient Products</b><br>The new 9000, 8000, 7000 and 6000 Series build upon the success of Samsung's first and second generation LED HDTV models. These cutting-edge TVs use LEDs as their primary light source, rather than traditional Cold Cathode Fluorescent Lamps (CCFL). The Samsung 6000 Series was also honored with an Eco Design Award in the 2009 CES Innovations Design and Engineering Awards. <br><br>The benefits of using LEDs include not only improved picture quality, but also reduced power consumption levels to easily meet the stringent new Energy Star® v3.0 guidelines.  The LED modules are mercury-free, which makes for cleaner manufacturing and safer recycling when compared with backlight technologies currently available. In the LED HDTV line, energy consumption is reduced by 40 percent versus traditional LCD HDTVs of a similar size. The LED HDTVs also include a power indicator menu, and an optimized energy savings mode. In addition, these TVs require less material to manufacture and are thinner, reducing packing material and consumer waste. The smaller packaging allows for more units to be shipped and less fuel to be consumed at a time which potentially reduces Samsung's carbon footprint.<br><br>As the trend towards delivering sleeker and thinner electronics products for consumers continues, Samsung has re-designed its Plasma HDTVs to use less material and less energy. The Series 8 Plasma, an Honoree for the 2009 CES Innovations Design and Engineering Awards, is trimmed down to depths that are comparable with LCDs, for easier wall-mounting, and less material is required in the manufacturing process. The latest Samsung plasmas also feature new circuitry and panel techniques to meet the latest Energy Star® v3.0 requirements, and they are produced entirely with lead-free materials.<br><br>In addition to energy-efficient HDTVs, Samsung's WF448 front-loading washer line also earned an Eco Design Award for the 2009 CES Innovations Design and Engineering Awards. The 448 laundry line has entered consumers' homes not only as the world's first 4.5 cubic foot front-loading washers, but as a gentler way to keep clothes clean while reducing impacts upon the environment. With such a large capacity, the total number of loads run during the life of the product is potentially reduced for lowered water and power use. The 448 laundry line boasts the Energy Star® -based CEE Tier 3 ranking (the highest available), and also features Samsung's SilverCare™ cycle option, which saves 92 percent on energy when compared to hot water sanitization..<br><br>"Manufacturers' commitment to developing products that are environmentally friendly is extremely important to the future of the consumer electronics industry," said Kathleen Hogan, Director of the Climate Protection Partnerships Division, U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "As an ENERGY STAR partner, Samsung is working to ensure that its products are as sleek in design as they are environmentally responsible."<br><br><b>Convenient and Responsible Recycling</b><br>Samsung's dedication to designing energy-efficient and environmentally safe products is complemented by the Company's commitment to providing convenient and responsible recycling options for its consumers. SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT, launched on October 1, 2008, provides more than 170 fixed drop-off locations across the country, as well as recycling events, for consumers to bring their old electronics for recycling. <br><br><b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> will accept, for no fee, all Samsung-branded consumer electronics sold in the United States ranging from televisions, DVD and VHS players, audio equipment and home theater systems, to mobile phones, cameras, camcorders, computer monitors, printers, and peripherals.  Non-Samsung-branded consumer electronics in the same categories will also be accepted through SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT for a nominal fee paid directly to the recycler upon delivery of the e-waste. In addition, a growing number of fixed drop-off locations will be made available for Samsung-branded home appliances.  <br><br>For a complete list of drop-off locations, and to learn more about Samsung's respected recycling partners and standards, please visit: <a href="http://www.samsung/com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank">www.samsung/com/recyclingdirect</a>. <br> <br><b>About Energy Star </b><br>Energy Star was introduced by EPA in 1992 as a voluntary, market-based partnership to reduce greenhouse gas emissions through energy efficiency. Today, the Energy Star label can be found on more than 50 different kinds of products, new homes, and commercial and industrial buildings. Products and buildings that have earned the Energy Star designation prevent greenhouse gas emissions by meeting strict energy-efficiency specifications set by the government. Last year alone, Americans, with the help of Energy Star, saved about $16 billion on their energy bills while reducing the greenhouse gas emissions equivalent to those of 27 million vehicles.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, is a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. The company markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products, as well as oversees all of Samsung's North American operations including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. As a result of its commitment to innovation and unique design, the Samsung organization is one of the most decorated brands in the electronics industry. The company was ranked #6 in the Electronics Industry segment in Fortune Magazine's "Most Admired Companies 2008," and named as one of Fast Company's "Fast 50 Most Innovative Companies of 2008." Among popular BusinessWeek rankings, the company ranked #26 in the publication's "Most Innovative Companies of 2008" and #21 in the "100 Best Global Brands" for 2007.  Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is also a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2007.  Please visit <b>www.samsung.com </b>for more information.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>. <br><br><b>About Samsung Recycling Direct<sub>sm</sub></b><br>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT is Samsung Electronics America, Inc.'s new, convenient and comprehensive commitment to the recycling of consumer electronics throughout the United States. SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT is available in all 50 states and it enables consumers to recycle Samsung-branded and non-Samsung-branded consumer electronics sold in the United States, with the exception of home appliances. However, there will be a growing number of drop-off locations that will also accept home appliances.  A full list of locations, including those that accept home appliances can be found at <a href="http://www.samsung/com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank">www.samsung/com/recyclingdirect</a>.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Takes &#034;Seamless Experience&#034; Beyond Convergence, Forging New Ground In Interactivity And ECO-Management At CES 2009
            </title>
            <description>
                
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>LAS VEGAS — January 7th, 2009</b> — The next evolution of the seamless user experience - one of greater interactivity, more intuitive user interfaces, and fresh eco-friendly technology - debuts today at the 2009 International CES as Samsung Electronics unveils an exciting array of new products and features at the company's annual press conference.<br>Samsung's product portfolio will be displayed <b>January 8-11 at booth 11033 </b>in the Central Hall of the Las Vegas Convention Center, as well as in the Innovations Pavilion. Full details, high-resolution images and downloadable videos are available at <a href="http://www.samsung.com/icespress" target="_blank">www.samsung.com/icespress.</a> <br><br>This year's offerings earned Samsung an unprecedented 46 CES Innovations Awards, reinforcing the company's leadership position in visual display, digital music players and home theater systems, while highlighting Samsung's growing commitment to environmentally-aware product development.<br>The result is a "second wave" of the Seamless Experience that Samsung unveiled in 2008, built on its "4Cs" approach to product development - content, creativity, connectivity and components. The next iteration is focused on the lifestyles of consumers themselves who face an overwhelming number of choices.<br>"Consumer electronics has moved beyond the convergence of individual products and categories to the convergence of these solutions with the lives of consumers, which in turn demands the creation of new user experiences," said<b> Dr. Jong Woo Park, President of Digital Media Business at Samsung Electronics</b>. "Samsung's vision is to foster the evolution of new and rewarding lifestyles through seamless user experiences that are emotional, intuitive and content-rich, while also ensuring a healthy respect for our environment."<br><br><b>LED - Backlight in the Spotlight</b><br>Samsung has established a new stand-alone category in its family of HDTVs for 2009 with the creation of a lineup of LED TVs that will set new benchmarks for picture quality and energy efficiency. This year, Samsung will introduce a full lineup of LED TVs ranging from 40-55 inches that achieve previously un-reachable mega-contrast ratios.<br><br>All of Samsung's LED TVs contribute to the company's eco-friendly vision, consuming 40 percent less power than standard CCFL-backlit LCD TVs, far below the stringent Energy Star version 3.0 requirements. The TVs use low electricity and contain no mercury, while the neck and stand are made of eco-friendly materials.<br><br>Included in this new line is the B6000, which is the slimmest of any LED TV on the market with tuner inside and features the world's slimmest wall mount solution that reduces the gap between the TV and the wall to 0.6 inches. Samsung's Series 6, 7, 8 and 9 LED TVs have all been selected for CES Innovation Awards. <br><br>"This new lineup of LED TVs represents the next chapter in Samsung's global television leadership," said<b> Tim Baxter, Executive Vice President for Sales and Marketing, Consumer Electronics Division, Samsung North America</b>. "Not only have we achieved unprecedented levels of picture quality and design excellence, but we've done so in a way that is environmentally sound."<br><br><b>Yahoo! Partnership Enriched</b><br>CES 2009 marks a milestone in the partnership between Samsung and Yahoo! with the launch of the "Internet@TV - Content Service" on Samsung flat panel televisions that will allow users to enjoy a vast array of rich digital content through a series of widgets available. Samsung's 2009 Series 7, 8 and 9 LED, LCD and plasma TVs will support the new service, which can be accessed via either the built-in Ethernet port or using an optional Wi-Fi USB dongle.<br><br>"Internet@TV - Content Service" brings a wealth of Web content and services to Samsung's TVs, ranging Yahoo! properties such as Flickr™, Yahoo! News, Yahoo! Weather and Yahoo! Finance, to third-party content like USA TODAY®, YouTube™, eBay® and Showtime Networks®. The Yahoo! Widgets Engine, an application platform that creates lightweight Javascript and XML applications, is the foundation of Internet@TV - Content Service and will also allow developers to create and deploy customized widgets for the television through an open platform.<br><br>The launch of The "Internet@TV - Content Service" is a product of Samsung's Medi@2.0 initiative and a key component of Seamless Experience. Samsung has also upgraded its "Content Library Flash," which allows users to download content from Samsung servers through an Ethernet connection to the TV. Enhancing this experience is the introduction of the BD-P4600, the world's thinnest Blu-Ray player that features an auto-adjusting function designed to deliver the clearest possible picture quality on Samsung TVs.<br><br>The BD-P4600 is the centerpiece of Samsung's most comprehensive Blu-ray lineup to date, featuring three stand-alone players and three home theater systems, including the HT-BD8200, the first Blu-ray home theater sound bar.<br><br><b>Touch of Color, Haptic Feel with Connectivity</b><br>Samsung has extended its leadership in design and built on the success of 2008's "Touch of Color," a patented dual-injection production process that transformed the look of the traditional piano black slim TV design, by introducing an enhanced ToC design, which features a softer, more subtle color gradation for an even more vibrant look. Samsung has also added chrome to its pallet of colors, which can be found on the LED 8000 TV.<br><br>Samsung has expanded the ability to transmit wireless HD content across its product groups. Several flat panel HDTVs feature the company's Wireless DNLA technology while select Blu-ray players are WiFi-enabled and include a wireless dongle for easy connectivity.<br>Samsung is applying this emotional, intuitive approach to connect with the needs of its users across its product lines. The HZ10W digital camera is the world's first to offer a 24mm wide-angle, 10X optical zoom that allows users to be more creative in the way they shoot and capture the image the way they see it through the wide-angle lens. The HZ10W also features an HD video capability to capture moving images. <br><br>Six new camcorders have been introduced at CES 2009, including the HMX-H106, its flagship full-HD camcorder that is the first to feature an internal 64GB solid-state drive, providing consumers with higher performing and more durable internal memory. Samsung also unveiled the SMX-F34, the company's next generation YouTube™ compatible compact digital camcorder.<br><br>Samsung has added elements of look and feel to its newest portable multimedia player, the P3. At less than 0.4 inches thin, the P3 features a three-inch widescreen video player, studio-quality audio player, ultra-portable photo album, personal voice recorder and FM radio. In addition, the EmoTure™ interface with haptic feedback allows consumers to enjoy features such as swiping a finger across the screen to switch audio tracks or fast forward video.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics</b> <br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of approximately US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of four main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, and Telecommunication Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG, Microsoft, DirecTV And Teen Music Star Jordan Pruitt Award More Than $2 Million Worth Of Technology, Software, Cash Grants And Educational Television Programming Packages To 31 Schools Through SAMSUNG'S Hope For Education Program
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>Tallahassee, Fla. - Dec. 16, 2008 </b>- Samsung's Hope for Education, Microsoft Corporation, and DIRECTV, Inc, along with teen music star <b>Jordan Pruitt</b>, presented Oak Ridge Elementary School in Tallahassee, Fla., with more than $200,000 in technology products, software, cash grants and educational television programming packages at a special assembly today for students, teachers and local dignitaries. Oak Ridge Elementary School is this year's grand prize winner in Samsung's fifth annual Hope for Education essay contest. Thirty first-prize schools from across the country will each receive more than $60,000 in technology, software, cash grants and educational television programming packages.<br><br>Thousands of essays were submitted through students, parents, teachers and principals looking for their community schools to benefit from this unique program.  This year's essay question addressed the environment, asking entrants, "How has technology educated you on helping the environment and how or why has it changed your behavior to be more environmentally friendly?"  The grand prize and first prize schools will receive technology from Samsung including its award-winning and energy efficient  LCD high definition televisions, laptops, multi-function products, smart phones, digital camcorders and cameras, blu-ray players, LCD computer monitors, and color printers, as well as Microsoft's latest, award-winning software. The program's newest partner, DIRECTV, will provide cash grants and the SCHOOL CHOICE® educational television programming package*. The person who submitted a winning entry on behalf of each of the 31 winning schools will be awarded the Samsung Ultra Mobile PC, a handheld multi-media PC which features a 7" LCD screen and built-in keyboard.  (Please see below for a complete list of winners, or visit www.hopeforeducation.com.)<br><br>"We are honored and grateful to be selected as the grand prize school in Samsung's Hope for Education program," said <b>Ms. D.J. Wright, principal of Oak Ridge Elementary School</b>. "The technology, software, cash grants and educational television programming being donated by Samsung, Microsoft and DIRECTV will provide the teachers of Oak Ridge Elementary School with the most up-to-date education tools to help enhance the learning of our students."<br><br>In addition to the more than $200,000 in cash and prizes, Oak Ridge Elementary School was awarded a classroom assistance dog at today's assembly for the school's special education classroom. Samsung works with the National Education for Assistance Dog Service (NEADS) to provide an assistance dog to the winning school. Since 1976, NEADS has provided specially trained dogs for nearly 1,000 deaf and disabled children and adults. Introduced last year, the "Friends for Life" program was created by Samsung Group in Korea to provide financial support for the training of special service animals to assist those in need lead a better life through the use of a dedicated service dog.<br><br>"With programs like Hope for Education, we have the opportunity to help bridge the technology gap that many of our schools face," said <b>D.J. Oh, president and CEO, Samsung Electronics America</b>. "The students of Oak Ridge Elementary School will certainly benefit from these new products and technology. It will allow them to reach new frontiers via the Internet and through the software, cash grants and educational television programming packages that Microsoft and DIRECTV are providing. In addition, the classroom assistance dog will support the students who need it most."  <br><br>"Microsoft is proud to be part of Samsung's Hope for Education program - recognizing deserving schools that are exploring how technology can make real, impactful environmental contributions to our world," said <b>Anthony Salcito, general manager of U.S. Education at Microsoft</b>. "The tools we are providing these winning schools will facilitate students' learning and discovery in new ways."<br><br>"DIRECTV is proud to support this educational initiative," said <b>Caroline Leach, vice president of Communications for DIRECTV</b>. "Television does not exist in a vacuum, so to us, being a good corporate citizen stretches beyond the living room and into the classroom. We hope this year's winning schools can benefit from our cash grants and SCHOOL CHOICE® educational television programming package." <br><br>Furthering education and reading is an important initiative for teen superstar Jordan Pruitt.  Through Samsung's partnership with her label, Hollywood Records, the teen sensation helped launch the 2008 Samsung Hope for Education program this spring in New York City with a special performance. She was also on hand at today's grand prize event to perform for the children of Oak Ridge Elementary School.  <br> <br>"I am so excited to work with Samsung's Hope for Education program and meet the students at Oak Ridge Elementary School," said Pruitt.  "Receiving the best education possible has definitely helped me achieve what I have in my career and I appreciate the opportunity to work with Samsung, Microsoft and DIRECTV to spread the message about how important technology and education is in our day-to-day lives." <br><br>Samsung's Hope for Education contest was first announced in 2004 at the opening of the Samsung Experience, a unique and creative technology emporium in the Time Warner Center in New York City.  Since the original launch, more than 280 U.S. schools in 43 states have benefited from over $9 million in technology, software, cash grants and educational television programming package. <br><br>* SCHOOL CHOICE programming available as long as the prize winning school continues to qualify under the DIRECTV GOES TO SCHOOL program and as long as DIRECTV has the DIRECTV GOES TO SCHOOL program or a similar program.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, is a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. The company markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products, as well as oversees all of Samsung's North American operations including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. As a result of its commitment to innovation and unique design, the Samsung organization is one of the most decorated brands in the electronics industry. The company was ranked #6 in the Electronics Industry segment in Fortune Magazine's "Most Admired Companies 2008," and named as one of Fast Company's "Fast 50 Most Innovative Companies of 2008." Among popular BusinessWeek rankings, the company ranked #26 in the publication's "Most Innovative Companies of 2008" and #21 in the "100 Best Global Brands" for 2007.  Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is also a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2007.  Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com. <br><br><b>About Microsoft</b><br>Founded in 1975, Microsoft (Nasdaq "MSFT") is the worldwide leader in software; services and solutions that help people and businesses realize their full potential. For more information, please visit www.microsoft.com.<br><br><b>About DIRECTV, Inc.</b><br>DIRECTV, Inc. (NASDAQ:DTV), the nation's leading satellite television service provider, presents the finest television experience available to more than 17.3 million customers in the United States and is leading the HD revolution with more than 130 HD channels - more quality HD channels than any other television provider. Each day, DIRECTV subscribers enjoy access to over 265 channels of 100% digital picture and sound, exclusive programming, industry-leading customer satisfaction (which has surpassed all national cable companies for eight years running) and superior technologies that include advanced DVR and HD-DVR services and the most state-of-the-art interactive sports packages available anywhere. For the most up-to-date information on DIRECTV, please visit directv.com. For more information about DIRECTV's educational programs and other corporate citizenship activities, please visit directv.com/community.<br><br><b>About Jordan Pruitt</b><br>Born in Loganville, Georgia, Jordan Pruitt began singing at a very early age - in fact, she began singing in public when she was only four years old and she hasn't stopped since.  Her debut single, "Outside Looking In, was featured in the Disney Channel Original Movie Read It and Weep.  Her debut album, No Ordinary Girl, was released in 2007, and her latest album "Permission To Fly" is in limited online release with a full nationwide release to Music Stores coming soon.<br><br><b>About Hollywood Records</b><br>The Disney Music Group encompasses all of the Walt Disney Studio's recorded music and music publishing operations, including Hollywood Records, Walt Disney Records, Lyric Street Records and Walt Disney Music Publishing. Artists include Aly & AJ, Raven Simone, Vanessa Hudgens, Jonas Brothers and more. For more information, please visit www.hollywoodrecords.com<br><br><b>About NEADS (National Education for Assistance Dog services Inc.)</b><br>NEADS is a non profit organization that trains dogs to assist adults and children who are deaf, physically disabled or who have special needs. Established in 1976, NEADS has placed over 1000 Assistance Dogs nationwide and is considered a leader in the Assistance Dog Industry.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                The SAMSUNG Experience and US Marine Corps Reserve to Host Toys for Tots Drive
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>NEW YORK--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Samsung Electronics America</b>, an established leader and innovator in consumer electronics, information technology, semiconductors and telecommunications, and the U.S. Marine Corps Reserve Toys for Tots Program will provide underprivileged children in the New York City area with a special holiday celebration. Now through Dec. 16, 2008, the Samsung Experience will be accepting toys for boys and girls as part of the annual Toys for Tots campaign. The toys will be distributed on Dec. 16, from 6-9 p.m. to approximately 300 children from the New York City area. The Samsung Experience, Samsung's innovative product showcase, is located on the third floor of The Shops at Columbus Circle in the Time Warner Center. <br><br>Founded in 1947, the Toys for Tots program evolved by collecting and distributing toys to needy children and soon became a nationwide initiative. To date, more than 173 million toys have been donated to less fortunate children. The Marines establish close relationships with social welfare agencies, local churches and other community agencies to identify children who may not receive holiday presents and arrange marketing campaigns creating a call to action for community members to donate to the cause. <br><br>"We are honored to work with the U.S. Marines and Toys for Tots on a campaign that so closely embodies our commitment to helping the community," said<b> D.J. Oh, president and CEO, Samsung Electronics America</b>. "Especially in these difficult economic times, it is important that everyone does their part to help make the holidays special for children and their families." <br><br>The Marines play an important role in the success of this program as it was founded by Maj. Bill Hendricks of the U.S. Marine Corp Reserve. Several members of the U.S. Marines will be on hand on Dec. 16 to distribute toys to the children. Scheduled to make a special appearance is Joe Lisi. In addition to having served the U.S. Marine Corps Reserve, Lisi is best known for his television roles on "The Sopranos" and "Third Watch." Vincent Pastore, veteran of the U.S. Navy and best known for his roles in "The Sopranos" and "Goodfellas" will also be in attendance, along with television, stage and screen actor Tony LoBianco, currently starring in the off-Broadway play, "LaGuardia." LoBianco's credits include "The French Connection," "A View from the Bridge," and "Police Story." Finally, opera singer Inbal Sharett will sing the national anthem and a set of holiday favorites. <br><br>Drop-off bins are located at the Samsung Experience now through Dec. 16. Samsung encourages the local community to donate toys at this location, as well as drop-off locations around the country to help children in all local communities. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br><br>Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, is a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. The company markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products, as well as oversees all of Samsung's North American operations including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. As a result of its commitment to innovation and unique design, the Samsung organization is one of the most decorated brands in the electronics industry. The company was ranked #6 in the Electronics Industry segment in Fortune Magazine's "Most Admired Companies 2008," and named as one of Fast Company's "Fast 50 Most Innovative Companies of 2008." Among popular BusinessWeek rankings, the company ranked #26 in the publication's "Most Innovative Companies of 2008" and #21 in the "100 Best Global Brands" for 2007. Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. Is also a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2007. Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> for more information. <br><br><b>About Samsung Experience </b><br><br>The Samsung Experience is a remarkable 10,000-square-foot interactive brand emporium that provides a creative experience through Samsung's vision of digital convergence. The site features hundreds of Samsung products in unique technology demonstrations that allow you to discover, touch, hear, and engage with the latest technology to create your own digital lifestyle. This permanent venue is located on the third floor of The Shops at Columbus Circle in the Time Warner Center. For more information about Samsung Experience, visit: <b>www.samsung.com/experience</b>. <br><br><b>About Toys for Tots </b><br><br>The U.S. Marine Corps Reserve Toys for Tots Program collects new, unwrapped toys during October, November and December each year, and distribute those toys as Christmas gifts to needy children in the community in which the campaign is conducted. Toys for Tots helps needy children throughout the United States experience the joy of Christmas; to play an active role in the development of one of our nation's most valuable natural resources - our children; to unite all members of local communities in a common cause for three months each year during the annual toy collection and distribution campaign; and to contribute to better communities in the future
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Receives 46 CES Innovations Awards For 2009
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, NJ, Nov. 11, 2008 </b>- Samsung Electronics America, an established leader and innovator in consumer electronics, information technology, semiconductors and telecommunications, has won an unprecedented <b>46 International CES Innovations 2009 Design and Engineering Awards</b>.  Products entered in this prestigious program are judged by a preeminent panel of independent industrial designers, engineers and members of the trade press to honor outstanding design and engineering in cutting edge consumer electronics products. <br> <br>Samsung once again displays why the company is a worldwide leader winning coveted CES honors for innovation across a broad range of technologies and product categories.  Samsung's award-winners include eight mobile phones, seven mobile phone accessories, six HDTVs, two laser printers, four digital cameras, two digital camcorders, a pair of large screen professional displays, a front loading washing machine, LCD panels, and a solid state drive in addition to more product innovations. All of Samsung's innovation award-winning products will be on display during the 2009 International CES, January 8-11, in Samsung booth 11033 in the Central Hall of the Las Vegas Convention Center, as well as in the Innovations Pavilion.<br><br>"Samsung strives to consistently lead the consumer electronics industry in product design and engineering innovation. We are extremely pleased that 46 of our product innovations for 2009, in a variety of categories, have been recognized by the Consumer Electronics Association judges," said <b>D.J. Oh, president and CEO, Samsung Electronics America, Inc</b>. "These prestigious awards reinforce Samsung's ongoing efforts to introduce the most groundbreaking technologies and products that enrich the lives of our consumers to the U.S. market."<br><br>As a leader in consumer electronics technology and design innovation, Samsung's commitment to research and development across all product categories allows the company to continue to bring the latest advancements in product technology and design to consumers.  The company invested $5.58 billion in overall research and development in 2007 with projections to sustain that level of investment in the upcoming year.  Samsung will continue to introduce new innovative technologies throughout all product lines in 2009, including enhanced user interface with touch screen devices, messaging devices with QWERTY keyboards, higher megapixel camera phones, smaller and lighter laser printers, advanced HDTV technologies and an increase in eco-friendly products. <br><br>As a widely renowned consumer technology awards program that began in 1976, the prestigious Innovations Design and Engineering Awards recognize achievements in product design and engineering. It is sponsored by the Consumer Electronics Association (CEA) ®, the producer of the International CES, the world's largest consumer technology tradeshow, and endorsed by the Industrial Designers Society of America (IDSA), the voice of industrial design, committed to advancing the profession through education, information, community and advocacy.<br><br>The Innovations entries are judged based on the following criteria:<br><br>-	Engineering qualities, based on technical specs and materials used<br>-	Aesthetic and design qualities, using photos provided <br>-	The product's intended use/function and user value <br>-	 Unique/novel features that consumers would find attractive<br><br>Products chosen as an Innovations honoree reflect innovative design and engineering of the entries. Examples may include the first time various technologies are combined in a single product or dramatic enhancements to previous product designs. <br><br>Innovations 2009 Design and Engineering honoree products are featured on <a href="http://www.CESweb.org/Innovations" target="_blank"> www.CESweb.org/Innovations</a>, which lists product categories, as well as each product name, manufacturer information, designer, description, photo and URL. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, is a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. The company markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products, as well as oversees all of Samsung's North American operations including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. As a result of its commitment to innovation and unique design, the company was ranked #6 in the Electronics Industry segment in Fortune Magazine's "Most Admired Companies 2008," and named as one of Fast Company's "Fast 50 Most Innovative Companies of 2008." Among popular BusinessWeek rankings, the company ranked #26 in the publication's "Most Innovative Companies of 2008" and #21 in the "100 Best Global Brands" for 2007.  Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is also a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2007.  Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> for more information.<br><br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Company </b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$103.4 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>. <br><br><b>About CEA</b><br>The Consumer Electronics Association (CEA) unites 2,200 companies within the consumer technology industry. Members tap into valuable and innovative members-only resources: unparalleled market research, networking opportunities with business advocates and leaders, up-to-date educational programs and technical training, exposure in extensive promotional programs, and representation from the voice of the industry, CEA, promoting and advancing member needs and interests. Find CEA online at <a href="http://www.CE.org" target="_blank"> www.CE.org</a>.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Withdraws Proposal To Acquire SanDisk
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>Seoul, Korea, October 22, 2008</b> - Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. ("Samsung") (005930:KS) today announced that it has withdrawn its proposal to acquire all of the outstanding shares of SanDisk Corporation ("SanDisk") (NASDAQ: SNDK) for $26 per share in cash. The full text of Samsung's letter to SanDisk's Board of Directors withdrawing its proposal follows: <br><br>October 22, 2008 <br><br>Board of Directors <br>SanDisk Corporation <br>601 McCarthy Boulevard <br>Milpitas, CA 95035 <br><br>Attention: Dr. Eli Harari, Chairman and Chief Executive Officer <br>Mr. Irwin Federman, Vice Chairman and Lead Independent Director <br><br><br>Dear Eli and Irwin: <br><br>After nearly six months of efforts to pursue a transaction with no meaningful progress, we are withdrawing our proposal to acquire SanDisk. I am disappointed that we have been unable to reach an agreement on our proposal. I continue to believe that a combination of our two companies would have created a superior global brand, an unparalleled technology platform and the scale and resources to drive convergence in the marketplace. Had we been able to execute on our proposal, your shareholders would have received full, fair and certain value for their shares and your employees and other stakeholders would have benefited from a broader platform and a wider range of opportunities. <br><br>Nevertheless, we have obligations to our own shareholders which require that we take a disciplined approach, particularly with respect to significant initiatives such as this. That disciplined approach requires that we squarely face the growing uncertainties in your business, which may continue to deteriorate in this difficult economic environment and further impact your standalone value. Your recently announced third quarter results serve only to illustrate this risk. Your surprise announcements of a quarter billion dollar operating loss, a hurried renegotiation of your relationship with Toshiba and major job losses across your organization all point to a considerable increase in your risk profile and a material deterioration in value, both on a stand-alone basis as well as to Samsung. As a result of these developments, we are no longer interested in acquiring SanDisk at $26/share. <br><br>While I regret that we were unable to work together to achieve a business combination that would have created new opportunities for all of us, we wish you the best in meeting the challenges ahead. <br><br>Sincerely, <br><br><br>Yoon Woo Lee <br>Vice Chairman & CEO <br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. <br><br><b>About Samsung </b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of four main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, and Telecommunication Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www. Samsung.com. <br><br>Samsung is a registered trademark of Samsung in the U.S. and other countries. <br><br>Forward Looking Statements <br><br>Some statements set forth in this communication contain forward-looking statements that are subject to change. Statements including words such as "anticipate", "believe", "estimate" or "expect" and statements in the future tense are forward-looking statements. These forward-looking statements are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual events or actual future results to differ materially from the expectations set forth in the forward-looking statements. All information in this communication is as of October 22, 2008. Samsung undertakes no duty to publicly update any forward-looking statement, whether as a result of new information, future developments or otherwise. <br><br>US Media Contact: <br>Sard Verbinnen & Co <br>Jim Barron/Kathryn Kranhold  +1-212-687-8080  <br>Elizabeth Hanahan/Lucy Neugart  +1-415-618-8750
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT Launches In 174 Sites Across 50 States
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J. - October 1, 2008</b> - Samsung Electronics America, Inc., a market leader and award-winning innovator in consumer electronics, today launched <b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b>, its commitment to the take-back and recycling (TB&R) of Samsung consumer electronics across all of its product lines. Beginning today, consumers can bring their Samsung-branded consumer electronics sold in the United States to 174 fixed drop-off locations across all 50 states for recycling for no fee. The program will also accept non-Samsung-branded consumer electronics for a nominal fee paid directly to the recycler upon delivery of the e-waste. Home appliances are currently being taken back in a growing number of locations.<br><br><b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> was announced on September 3, 2008. Today, Samsung unveiled additional information on this program at <a href="http://www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect</a>. Consumers who visit the site can learn about the program, find recycling collection sites in all 50 states, and read about upcoming recycling drives to be held in many locations throughout the U.S. In addition, Samsung hosted recycling events for thousands of its employees at seven of its campuses in the United States, including Ridgefield Park, NJ; Mt. Arlington, NJ; Rancho Dominquez, CA; Richardson, TX; Austin, TX; San Diego, CA; and San Jose, CA.<br><br>"We invited our employees to participate in the launch of SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT by dropping off their consumer electronics at work, where we have collaborated with our respected recycling partners to accept retired electronics," said <b>DJ Oh, President and CEO, Samsung Electronics America.</b> "Thousands of Samsung employees across the country demonstrated their shared commitment to the environment by recycling consumer electronics products, including mobile phones, televisions, cameras, VCRs, computers and monitors. We are truly inspired by this level of receptivity and participation."<br><br>programs under Samsung's control in certain states and its current 50-state initiatives for the TB&R of toner cartridges, mobile phones and office equipment. Today's <b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> kick-off expands the scope of products that are now being collected in all 50 states and the convenience for consumers to responsibly recycle their consumer electronics. The program got off to a fast start as Samsung employees added their consumer electronics to the <b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> total that will be processed and recycled responsibly by Samsung's leading recycling partners. These partners are obligated under the program not to incinerate, send to solid waste landfill, or export toxic waste (defined in a manner consistent with the commonly accepted definition of hazardous electronic waste) to developing countries. Details about our standards for responsible recycling are available at <a href="http://www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect</a>.<br><br>On the website consumers can also find information regarding <b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> including the ability to search by zip code to find a detailed map and list of fixed drop-off locations in their area, as well as information on future recycling drives sponsored by Samsung, its retail and business partners, and its respected recyclers. In addition, the <b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> web site will serve as an ongoing reporting tool to showcase the results of this program. "On September 3rd, 2008 Samsung set a goal of securing at least one <b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> location in each state by today's launch. I am proud of Samsung's progress in exceeding that goal and developing a 174 permanent site network, which we believe sets an industry precedent in making it easy and convenient for consumers to recycle their consumer electronics," said Steven Cook, senior vice president and chief strategic marketing officer, Samsung Electronics America. "We are committed to providing a public record of our environmental progress, and are confident that we can raise the standards of consumer electronics recycling by working with an interdisciplinary Samsung team and a highly-qualified network of recycling partners, all of whom are governed by stringent standards & guidelines that ensure accountability,transparency and responsibility at every step along the way."<br><br><b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> provides four convenient ways for consumers to get involved: <br><br><b>1.</b> Fixed Drop-off Locations: <b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> includes 174 static locations for participants to drop off consumer electronics in all 50 states. These drop-off locations are maintained by our partners and include a growing number of sites that will also accept home appliances. A list of fixed collection points can be found at: <a href="http://www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank">Locations.</a> <br><br><b>2.</b> Samsung- Sponsored Events: <b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> sponsors recycling events in all 50 states. A list of Samsung-sponsored take-back and recycling events can be found at<br><a href="http://www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect</a>.<br><br><b>3.</b> Samsung Drives with Retail and Business Partners: <b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> participates in consumer electronics recycling drives sponsored by Samsung with our retail partners and other business partners across the country. A regularly updated list of special retail and partner recycling drives can be found at <a href="http://www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect</a>.<br><br><b>4.</b> Non-Samsung-Sponsored Events: Consumers can recycle their Samsung-branded consumer electronics at pre-scheduled recycling drives sponsored by Samsung's recycling partners. A regularly updated list of pre-scheduled recycling drives and non-Samsung sponsored events conducted by our recycling partners can be found at <a href="www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect</a>.<br><br>"Samsung is proud of our history in providing innovative consumer electronics complemented by corporate initiatives designed to protect and preserve our natural resources. <b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT</b> is further evidence of our values and we are confident that it will serve as a catalyst that enables convenient, efficient and increased recycling of consumer electronics across the country," concluded Mr. Oh.<br><br><u><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc.</b></u><br>Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, is a subsidiary of Samsung<br>Electronics Co., Ltd. (SEC). SEA markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products, as well as oversees all of Samsung's North American operations including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. As a result of its commitment to innovation and unique design, SEA was ranked #6 in the Electronics Industry segment in Fortune Magazine's "Most Admired Companies 2008," and named as one of Fast Company's "Fast 50 Most Innovative Companies of 2008." Among popular BusinessWeek rankings, SEC ranked #26 in the publication's "Most Innovative Companies of 2008" and #21 in the "100 Best Global Brands" for 2007. SEC is also a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2007. Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> or call 1(800) SAMSUNG for more information.<br><br><b><u>About Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd.</u></b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$103.4 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of four main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, and Telecommunication Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit<b> www.samsung.com</b>.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Electronics America Launches SAMSUNG Recycling Direct SM
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J. - September 3, 2008</b> - Samsung Electronics America, Inc., a market leader and award-winning innovator in consumer electronics, today announced<b> SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT<sub>SM</sub></b>, its commitment to the take-back and recycling (TB&R) of Samsung-branded consumer electronics across all of its product lines. Beginning October 1, 2008, people will be able to drop off their Samsung-branded consumer electronics sold in the United States at convenient collection sites, including permanent drop-off centers in all 50 states, and at a wide range of recycling events across the country. Through this convenient recycling program, Samsung-branded consumer electronics will be accepted for no fee, and non-Samsung-branded consumer electronics will be accepted for a nominal fee paid directly to Samsung's contracted recycling partners upon delivery of the e-waste.<br><br>"Since the 1996 launch of our global Green Management Initiative, Samsung Electronics Company has been a staunch advocate of preserving our environment and greening the consumer electronics industry," said <b>DJ Oh, President and CEO, Samsung Electronics America</b>. "As a global enterprise, we have worked diligently to put our environmental responsibility philosophy into practice across our worldwide operations, among our suppliers and partners, and within our local communities. Today we are very pleased to once again affirm those philosophies by announcing that our SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT 50-state take-back and recycling commitment extends across all Samsung-branded consumer electronics sold in the United States with the exception of home appliances. However, there will be a growing number of drop-off locations that will accept home appliances."<br><br>Samsung elected to contract directly with recycling companies, unlike other consumer electronics TB&R programs that rely on intermediaries. Samsung conducted extensive research into the qualifications, capabilities, and integrity of these companies to ensure that they mirror Samsung's own environmental philosophy. As such, the SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT program will only utilize recyclers that do not incinerate, landfill, or export toxic waste to developing countries. The SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT program also allows Samsung to track and monitor all of the collected consumer electronics for added assurance that it is recycled responsibly.  Mr. Oh added, "We took the extra care to develop the SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT program to achieve the highest integrity end-of-life standards. Samsung Electronics America has set scorecard standards with our contracted recyclers, and we will track and monitor their processes and results very closely."  SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT results will be posted on www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect throughout the year. This will provide an unprecedented level of transparency to the public.<br><br>The SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT program joins the numerous TB&R initiatives that the Company currently has in place. Samsung's Information Technology Division currently has a 50-state S.T.A.R. Toner Recycling Program for printer cartridges and the Envirosync initiative which takes back and recycles Samsung-branded and other branded office equipment for no fee to the end-user or reseller when purchasing new Samsung-branded office equipment. In addition, Samsung also provides recycling for mobile phones through its 50-state Samsung Mobile Take-back Program. Samsung's commitment will now apply to all Samsung-branded consumer electronics ranging from televisions, DVD and VHS players, audio equipment and home theater systems, to cameras, camcorders, computer monitors, printers, and peripherals.  In addition, a growing number of fixed drop-off locations will be made available for home appliances.  <br><br>"As a leader in the consumer electronics industry, we at Samsung listened carefully to our consumers' needs and wants to build the consumer-centric SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT program which delivers on their highest priorities," stated <b>Steven Cook, senior vice president and chief strategic marketing officer, Samsung Electronics America</b>, "This resulted in a convenient way to responsibly recycle their consumer electronics products so that our consumers can enjoy a digital lifestyle in good conscience."<br><br><b><u>How Consumers Can Get Involved with the SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT program:</u></b><br><br>Samsung has developed a comprehensive program to make it easier for consumers to recycle Samsung-branded consumer electronics in the most convenient and safest way, using leading and respected TB&R vendors.  Beginning on October 1, 2008, consumers will be able to engage Samsung and its recycling partners in any of the four ways described below. Regardless of the method, Samsung-branded consumer electronics sold in the United States will be accepted for recycling for no fee through the SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT program.<br><br>1.	<b><u>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT Fixed Drop-off Points in all 50 States:</u></b> Drop off Samsung-branded consumer electronics at a fixed collection point as identified on our website. Samsung-branded home appliance drop-off opportunities will also be available at a growing number of locations specifically described on our website. Non-Samsung-branded consumer electronics will be accepted for a nominal, weight-based fee paid directly to Samsung's contracted recycling partners upon delivery of the e-waste. A list of fixed collection points can be found as of October 1, 2008 at: <a href="http://www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect </a> <br><br>2.	<u><b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT Sponsored TB&R Events in all 50 States:</b></u> Drop off Samsung-branded consumer electronics at recycling events sponsored by Samsung beginning in October 2008. Samsung will schedule these events to make it easier for consumers to recycle their Samsung-branded consumer electronics conveniently and responsibly. Non-Samsung-branded consumer electronics will be accepted for a nominal, weight-based fee paid directly to Samsung's contracted recycler upon delivery of recycled goods. A list of Samsung-sponsored TB&R events can be found as of October 2008 at: www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect <br><br>3.	<b><u>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT TB&R Drives with Retail and Business Partners Across the U.S.: </u></b> <br>"Samsung recently started TB&R programs in conjunction with some of our retailers.  With the SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT program, Samsung is committed to hosting special TB&R drives with our retail and business partners to make it easy for consumers to responsibly recycle their consumer electronics," stated Tim Baxter, executive vice president of sales and marketing for the Consumer Electronics Division. A regularly updated list of recycling drives can be found starting October 2008 at: <a href="http://www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect </a> <br><br>4.	<b><u>Pre-Scheduled / Non-Samsung-Sponsored TB&R Drives with Leading Recyclers:</u></b> Drop off Samsung-branded consumer electronics at a pre-scheduled recycling drive or non-Samsung-sponsored event that our leading recycling partners are conducting, and the Samsung-branded products will be accepted for no fee. Non-Samsung-branded products will be accepted for a nominal weight-based fee paid directly to the recycler upon delivery of the e-waste. A regularly updated list of pre-scheduled recycling drives and non-Samsung-sponsored events conducted by our recycling partners can be found as of October 2008 at: <a href="http://www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect </a> <br><br><b>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT Responsible Recycling Partners</b><br><br>To execute TB&R activities in 50 states, Samsung has directly partnered with leading e-waste recyclers in the United States. <br>-	Chicago-based SIMS Group Limited, which has operations on the Northeast region, the West Coast, the Midwest, and the South.  <br>-	Wisconsin-based CRT Processing LLC, which has operations across the Northeast region, the Midwest, and the Pacific Northwest regions.<br>-	New York-based Eco International LLC, which has operations across the mid-Atlantic, Midwest, and West.<br>-	Minnesota-based JFRC, LLC, which operates in the northern Midwest.<br><br>SAMSUNG RECYCLING DIRECT… Partnering for Success<br><br>Mr. Oh concluded, "As with any program of this magnitude and consumer-centric focus, considerations that include convenience, respect for environment and people, responsible program management, and the highest integrity are absolutely critical for a sustainable success. We at Samsung recognize our colleagues in the consumer electronics industry who have introduced take-back and recycling initiatives in recent months, and we sincerely invite those companies seeking a path to environmental responsibility for them to join us in our commitment to tackle this important issue."<br><br>Additional information about today's announcement and Samsung's environmentally-responsible activities can be found at www.samsung.com/recyclingdirect. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc.</b> <br>Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, is a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. (SEC). SEA markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products, as well as oversees all of Samsung's North American operations including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. As a result of its commitment to innovation and unique design, SEA was ranked #6 in the Electronics Industry segment in Fortune Magazine's "Most Admired Companies 2008," and named as one of Fast Company's "Fast 50 Most Innovative Companies of 2008." Among popular BusinessWeek rankings, SEC ranked #26 in the publication's "Most Innovative Companies of 2008" and #21 in the "100 Best Global Brands" for 2007.  SEC is also a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2007.  Please visit <b>www.samsung.com for more information</b>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd.</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$103.4 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of four main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, and Telecommunication Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Powers Up Charging Stations At Two Major U.S. Airports, Giving Travellers A Chance To Recharge Cell Phones, Laptops And Other Electronic Devices For Free
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>RICHARDSON, Texas - April 30, 2008 Samsung Telecommunications America</b> (Samsung Mobile) today announced charging stations in terminals at LaGuardia Airport (LGA) and Orlando International Airport (MCO). The Samsung Mobile Charging Stations offer travelers the convenience of free re-charging of their mobile phones, laptops and other personal electronics. <br>"The Samsung Mobile Charging Stations are an easy way to reduce some of the stress that can come with traveling for business travelers and vacationers alike," said Bill Ogle, Chief Marketing Officer of Samsung Mobile. "The charging stations are easy to find and simple to use. We expect them to be as big a hit with travelers passing through these major cities as they have been in JFK, LAX and DFW airports." <br>At LaGuardia, 12 8-1/2-foot-tall, pole-like charging stations have been installed inside the boarding areas in the Central Terminal Building (Terminal C) at Gates A-D. Orlando International Airport will offer travelers access to 18 charging stations located on Level Two in four satellite terminals (Airsides' 1-4).<br>Samsung Mobile Charging Stations have four outlets per station, allowing several travelers to re-charge their electronic devices at the same time.  The charging stations are designed to re-charge personal electronics designed for U.S. voltage (i.e., 120 volts). The charging stations are also equipped with a small shelf to hold travelers' mobile phones and other electronic equipment. <br><br>Samsung has installed charging stations at some of the nation's largest airports, including 54 stations at John F. Kennedy International Airport (JFK) and 51 stations at Los Angeles International Airport (LAX), along with eight Samsung Mobile Travel Centers at Dallas/Fort Worth International Airport (DFW). <br>"At Orlando International Airport we continue to look for ways to meet the diverse needs of our passengers.  The complimentary charging stations are an expected customer service amenity for today's travelers with personal electronics," said Renee Spann, Director of Concessions, for the Greater Orlando Aviation Authority. <br>Con Edison is providing the electricity for the charging stations at LaGuardia, and the Orlando Utilities Commission will provide electricity to the charging stations at Orlando International Airport.<br><br><br><br><b>About Samsung Telecommunications America </b><br>Samsung Telecommunications America, LLC, a Dallas-based subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., researches, develops and markets wireless handsets and telecommunications products throughout North America. For more information, please visit www.samsungwireless.com. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$103.4 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.<br><br><b>LaGuardia International Airport </b><br>The Port Authority of New York and New Jersey operates many of the busiest and most important transportation links in the region.  They include John F. Kennedy International, Newark Liberty International, and Stewart International airports; LaGuardia and Teterboro airports; AirTrain JFK and AirTrain Newark; the George Washington Bridge and Bus Station; the Lincoln and Holland tunnels; the three bridges between Staten Island and New Jersey; the PATH (Port Authority Trans-Hudson) rapid-transit system; the Port Authority-Downtown Manhattan Heliport; Port Newark; the Elizabeth-Port Authority Marine Terminal; the Howland Hook Marine Terminal on Staten Island; the Brooklyn Piers/Red Hook Container Terminal; and the Port Authority Bus Terminal in midtown Manhattan.  The agency also owns the 16-acre World Trade Center site in Lower Manhattan.<br><br><b>Orlando International Airport</b><br>Forbes magazine recently named Orlando International one of the 10 most wired airports in the world offering wired and wireless internet access.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                A-VSB Initiative Demonstrates the First end-to-end ATSC-Compatible Mobile Broadcast TV Platform
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>Las Vegas (NAB 2008) - April 14, 2008</b> -The A-VSB Initiative, whose members include Samsung Electronics, MobiTV, Nokia Siemens Networks, Rohde & Schwarz and SES AMERICOM's IP-PRIME®, announced a live demonstration of an end-to-end broadcast mobile TV platform at NAB.  The platform has been proposed to the Advanced Television Systems Committee (ATSC) as an open ATSC Mobile/Handheld (ATSC-M/H) standard.  It includes the A-VSB physical layer and global standard OMA BCAST service layer for mobile broadcasting, showing live local and national content as well as interactivity. NAB attendees can view the platform and mobile devices at the A-VSB Initiative booth (Hall C, Booth 1539) and via a demonstration bus that will circulate outside the convention center (seats can be reserved at the booth).<br><br>The live demonstration at NAB 2008 uses existing Las Vegas transmission infrastructure owned by the Sinclair Broadcasting Group (station KVMY) and Telemundo (station KBLR).  In addition to live local and national programming, interactivity and electronic service guide functionality are also being demonstrated for the first time in an ATSC-compatible mobile broadcast system.   <br><br>A-VSB is a proposed open-standard and backward-compatible enhancement of the existing U.S. digital TV broadcasting system.  It empowers local TV stations' broadcast spectrum to reach mobile audiences on devices such as portable media players, mobile phones, personal computers, and in-vehicle entertainment systems.   A-VSB is the leading proposed standard for mobile broadcast TV under review by the ATSC—the first proposed, the first publicly demonstrated, the first to be implemented in integrated receiver chips, and now, the first to conduct a complete commercial grade end-to-end platform demonstration.  <br><br>The A-VSB platform will deliver programming and interactive applications to consumers on mobile devices "in-band," i.e., through local TV stations' existing transmitters and spectrum.   Consumer trials planned for later in 2008 in one or more U.S. markets will illustrate the business opportunities that A-VSB powered mobile TV can bring to the broadcasting, advertising, wireless, digital media, interactive services, and consumer electronics industries.  As the only commercially-ready, complete and open solution for in-band mobile broadcast TV, A-VSB stands ready to power the commercial launch of mobile broadcast TV services in 2009.  A-VSB is ready for rapid deployment by broadcasters at low capital investment and no cost to buy new spectrum. See the attached fact sheet for technical information about A-VSB.<br>A-VSB Initiative Members and their roles in the NAB demonstration and/or the planned consumer trials are as follows: <br>Samsung Electronics will supply the devices with receiver chips, such as handsets and portable computers, which will be used as the receiving hardware in the trials.<br>Nokia Siemens Networks will be delivering an OMA BCAST 1.0 compliant mobile broadcast TV service platform, that manages the delivery of audio/video/data content, and provides service and content protection in addition to a user friendly Electronic Service Guide.  <br>MobiTV is providing interactive applications such as voting, polling, mCommerce, audience measurement and participation television.  <br>SES AMERICOM's IP-PRIME® is aggregating and encoding the national content, integrating security and a service guide, and providing the satellite delivery backbone to participating broadcast stations.<br>Rohde & Schwarz is providing transmission equipment including broadcast test and measurement, exciters and integration into existing broadcast infrastructure.  This  enables broadcasters to quickly and easily convert their transmission equipment for A-VSB service.<br><br>Samsung: "As the inventor of A-VSB, the key breakthrough enabling the ATSC television system to deliver in-band mobile broadcast TV, Samsung is proud to show the way forward to empower U.S. local TV stations to fully monetize their spectrum with mobile broadcasting," said John Godfrey, Vice President of Government and Public Affairs, Samsung Electronics.  "The A-VSB Initiative demonstration at NAB and the consumer trials planned for later in 2008 will show that we are both technically and commercially ready for a commercial rollout in 2009."<br><br><b>MobiTV: </b><br>"This summer MobiTV will demonstrate a suite of novel applications based on the OMA Rich Media Environment enhancing the conventional mobile broadcast," said Charlie Nooney, CEO for MobiTV. "Through these services MobiTV plans to make interactivity and participation an indispensable part of users' mobile television experience and a viable business model for content providers, broadcasters, and mobile network operators."<br><br><br><b>Nokia Siemens Networks: </b><br> "The use of open global standards is a catalyst for the rapid adoption of new services and technologies", said Ron Freeman, Head of Emerging Markets IPTV & Mobile TV, for Nokia Siemens Networks. "We will provide an open standard OMA BCAST compliant service platform as part of the A-VSB Initiative NAB demonstration and later consumer trials." The Nokia Siemens Networks mobile broadcast TV solution is currently used widely in commercial and trial networks globally and is ready for US deployment in 2009.<br><br><b>Rohde & Schwarz: </b><br>"Rohde & Schwarz is pleased to have an important role in creating this new opportunity for broadcasters", said Eddy Vanderkerken, Director of Sales and Marketing for Rohde & Schwarz Broadcast Products.  "We have been involved in the development of A-VSB from the outset, and are not only committed to bringing transmission products, but also Test & Measurement equipment to the Mobile TV market. We believe that broadcasters are eager to deploy new services, and Rohde & Schwarz is ready to support their goals with equipment that is ready today."<br><br><b>SES AMERICOM:</b><br> "We are firmly committed to open standards and are strongly encouraged by the progress we're making together with the A-VSB Initiative toward bringing mobile broadcast television programming to consumers," said Bryan McGuirk, President, North American Satellite Services, SES AMERICOM. "The migration to digital is leading to a greater appreciation for the power of IP-based content delivery, which is the hallmark of our business.  Together with our A-VSB partners, we look forward to introducing this game-changing platform and service to the consumer market next year."<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics </b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$103.4 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b><br><br><b>About MobiTV </b><br>MobiTV (http://www.mobitv.com), the market maker and leader in the delivery of mobile content and services, develops and offers technology solutions that power an end-to-end managed network for content ingestion, encoding and optimized delivery over mobile and broadband networks. MobiTV's platform technology delivers live television, premium and primetime programming, video-on-demand, satellite and digital music services from top broadcast and cable television networks and major music labels through its carrier and operator partners to more than three million subscribers worldwide. Founded in 1999, MobiTV is a privately held company with headquarters in Emeryville, California.<br><br><b>About Nokia Siemens Networks </b><br>Nokia Siemens Networks is a leading global enabler of communications services. The company provides a complete, well-balanced product portfolio of mobile and fixed network infrastructure solutions and addresses the growing demand for services with 20,000 service professionals worldwide. Nokia Siemens Networks is one of the largest telecommunications infrastructure companies with operations in 150 countries. The company is headquartered in Espoo, Finland. http://www.nokiasiemensnetworks.com. <br> <br><b>About Rohde & Schwarz</b><br>Rohde & Schwarz is an independent group of companies specializing in electronics. It is a leading supplier of solutions in the fields of test and measurement, broadcasting, radio monitoring and radio location, as well as secure communications. Established 75 years ago, Rohde & Schwarz has a global presence and a dedicated service network in over 70 countries. It has approx. 7200 employees and achieved a net revenue of € 1.4 billion (US$ 1.9 billion) in fiscal year 2006/2007 (July 2006 to June 2007). Company headquarters are in Munich, Germany.<br><br><b>About SES AMERICOM 					(www.ses-americom.com)</b><br>An SES company (Euronext Paris and Luxembourg Stock Exchange: SESG), SES AMERICOM is North America's leading satellite company, delivering video, voice and data ubiquitously across the continent, including locations impossible to reach with wired connections. Building on its thirty year heritage in broadcast television, the company's IP-PRIME® solution is the fastest and most cost effective way for operators to bring IPTV service to market. This true turnkey solution comes with transport agreements for almost 300 television channels, including more than two dozen HD channels, and more than 100 digital music channels, letting IP-PRIME operators offer a broad range of diverse programming to their subscribers.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Announces Winners Of Mobile Phone Samaritan Contest
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., Feb. 11, 2008 - Samsung</b>, Presenting Partner of the Beijing 2008 Olympic Torch Relay, is rewarding five Samsung Mobile Phone Samaritans with the opportunity of a lifetime to carry the Olympic Torch during its only U.S. stop this April in San Francisco. <br><br>The Samsung Mobile Phone Samaritan program allows for Samsung to reward individuals who have helped others by using a mobile phone to call for help.  A panel of judges selected five winning entries awarding them with an opportunity to serve as Olympic Torchbearers in San Francisco. <br><br><b>Bill Schmidt</b><br>While on his way home from visiting family in Milwaukee, Bill Schmidt, of Chesterfield, Mo., recalls the terrible weather as the roads went from bad to worse just before an SUV flipped several times. Schmidt's fast reaction to stop, assess the situation and call 911 saved the lives of three passengers and earned him the opportunity to be a Samsung Mobile Phone Samaritan. <br><br>"I saw the car flip and I didn't even think," said Schmidt. "My wife called 911 while I jumped out of my car and ran across the median to help the family."<br><br>Schmidt pulled the mother and daughter free from the car, but the father was pinned. Rather than leaving the father alone in the car, Schmidt laid down on the frozen ground to talk to the man and let him know that help was coming and that his wife and daughter were safe. <br><br><b>Richard Doran </b><br>After using his mobile phone on Sept. 11, 2001, to let his wife know he was alive, NYC Firefighter Richard Doran didn't realize that mobile phones would be an essential tool to link those who were lost to their loved ones on that tragic day.<br><br>Doran plans to dedicate his run carrying the Olympic Torch to memorialize the fallen firefighters from 9/11. "The last 343 steps I take during the Olympic Torch Relay will be in honor of the 343 firefighters that we lost on that tragic day," said Doran. <br><br>While Doran hopes nothing like Sept. 11, will ever happen again, he hopes his story will inspire everyone to keep their contact lists up-to-date in their mobile phones with emergency contacts and next of kin clearly stated. If someone in the emergency field comes across an unconscious person as a result of an accident, they will be able to reach their family in a timely manner.  <br><br><b>Cherice Gerson</b><br>As a busy mom of four kids, Overland Park, Kan., resident, Cherice Gerson, knows the importance of being available to her children whenever they need her. Using their mobile phones, Gerson keeps in constant contact with her children with text messaging. While most of the texts have centered around passing tests and after school plans, one day stands out as the reason Gerson is a Samsung Mobile Phone Samaritan. <br><br>A suspicious stranger was found lurking around the perimeter of her youngest son's middle school and the school was put in lockdown mode. Her son, in a panic, sent a text message to his mom. Gerson quickly responded to her son, offering words of reassurance and the comfort of knowing that his mom was just a text message away. Luckily, the situation passed with no incident and Gerson was even more thankful for mobile phones. <br><br><b>Mark Meyers</b><br>Several years ago, Mark Meyers of Durbin, N.D., heard of a single mother with a degenerative disease struggling to make ends meet. When her phone was shut off, Meyers paid the bill and had the lines reinstated so the woman could keep in touch with her then six-year-old daughter's school. Over the years, Meyers has continued paying the woman's phone bill, as well as getting mobile phones for the mother and daughter once the daughter reached middle school and became more involved in school activities. <br><br>Meyers's generosity towards this family showcases one of the many different ways people can be Mobile Phone Samaritans. Meyers has given this woman and her daughter the gift of communication. <br><br><b>Katie Gosling</b><br>When Katie Gosling was hiking with her dad, James, at Castle Rock State Park in San Francisco, they expected a beautiful, relaxing day. While stopping for lunch on a hillside, the Goslings watched climbers on Goat Rock. Part of Goat Rock features an overhang where climbers have to hang by their arms; one climber lost his grip and fell. Initially he was saved by his rope and harness, but that broke and he plunged headfirst 30 to 40 feet into the rocks. <br><br>James could tell the climber was still alive, but he was bleeding badly. He called for help from his mobile phone and within a few minutes, a helicopter appeared with rangers rappelling down the cliff with a stretcher to carry the climber to safety. Thinking back on the situation, Katie acknowledges that when hiking, it's important to have someone with you and also make sure you have mobile phones with fully charged batteries. <br><br>As a runner herself, Gosling is thrilled with the opportunity to participate in the ultimate race. "The Olympic Torch relay will be unlike any other event I've participated in," said Gosling. "Rather than racing against the other runners, we're going to be sharing the moment together."<br><br>"Each of these individuals is a Mobile Phone Samaritan in very different ways, but they have the same result - helping someone in need," said DJ Oh, President and CEO of Samsung Electronics America.  "They used quick thinking and the use of their mobile phones to help someone out in a critical situation." <br><br>Samsung Electronics has been a Worldwide Olympic Partner in the wireless telecommunications category since 1997 and first sponsored the Olympic Torch Relay in 2004 prior to the Summer Olympic Games in Athens, Greece. Through the years Samsung has consistently sponsored and supported a broad range of sporting events that echo its corporate philosophy, elevate Samsung's brand recognition and demonstrate the company's commitment to responsible corporate citizenship and global friendship. <br><br>For more information about Samsung's Olympic involvement, visit <a href="http://product.samsung.com/torchrelay"> www.samsung.com/torchrelay</a>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics </b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$103.4 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Announces Plans to Integrate Digital Camera and Consumer Electronics Businesses
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>Las Vegas, NV (January 31, 2008)</b> - Samsung today formally announced plans to integrate the digital still camera business of Samsung Opto-Electronics America (SOA), Inc. with Samsung Electronics America's (SEA) consumer electronics business in March of 2008.  The move is designed to leverage existing synergies between the two business units, create new competitive advantages and ultimately enhance the company's overall brand positioning.  The integration announced today is the most recent in a series of initiatives that have fueled Samsung's progress toward becoming one of the world's leading digital imaging companies.<br><br>"Bringing the digital still camera business into the fold of our broader consumer electronics operations is the next logical step in the evolution of our digital imaging business," said <b>Tim Baxter, executive vice president of sales and marketing at Samsung Electronics America</b>.  "Both groups bring inherent strengths and relationships to the table that will allow us to elevate our presence and offer a more comprehensive suite of digital lifestyle solutions to retailers and consumers."  <br><br>Samsung has established some very aggressive goals for the digital imaging business, targeting a number three position among the world's top manufacturers by 2010.  According to company officials, the integration plans announced today will enable the digital camera business to leverage SEA's existing relationships and strengths in the consumer electronics retail channel to help fuel its future growth.  Similarly, the new relationship will enable the camcorder division of SEA to strengthen its presence in the photo specialty channel.  SOA has devoted considerable resources and significantly elevated its position in the photo specialty market since the introduction of its flagship NV Series of high end compact cameras and its GX Series of DSLRs. In addition to the natural synergy created by joining the camera and camcorder businesses, Samsung's #1 position in HDTVs provides a strong foundation to grow awareness and sales of HD imaging products and solutions. <br><br>SAMSUNG's camera business has realized impressive growth in recent years, increasing both sales and market share.  The integration with SEA will bring an infusion of resources in R&D, design, sales and marketing that will drive continued growth and success in the years to come.  <br><br>"We believe this move represents a true win / win scenario," said <b>Tony Sorice, vice president of national accounts for Samsung Opto-Electronics, America, Inc.</b>  "The benefits of this integration are already evident in products like the NV24HD and the HMX20, both of which allow consumers to get the most out of the HD experience and leverage our position as a world leader in HD technology.  Moving forward, we will continue to broaden and deepen our product lines and enhance our position in the digital imaging space."<br><br><b>Samsung Opto-Electronics America, Inc., Ridgefield Park, N.J.</b>, is the U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Techwin Co., Ltd., Sungnam Kyungki-Do, Korea.  Samsung Opto-Electronics markets a full line of auto focus cameras, zoom and digital cameras for the amateur as well as the professional under the Samsung brand name.	<br><br>For full specifications and hi-res images, visit <a href="http://www.samsungcameraUSA.com">www.samsungcameraUSA.com</a>
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Appoints Stan Sands As Vice President Of Cable Sales
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., Jan. 18, 2008</b> - Samsung Electronics America, an established leader and innovator in consumer electronics, proudly announces the appointment of <b>Stan Sands</b> as vice president of Cable Sales, at the company's North American headquarters (NAHQ).  Sands will be responsible for establishing sales strategies, creating promotions and programs for sales expansion, and managing the dedicated sales team.<br><br>Sands joins Samsung with more than 25 years of both international and domestic sales experience in the cable communications industry.  Previously, Sands spent 20 years with Scientific-Atlanta, leaving the company as vice president of Sales. During his time with Scientific-Atlanta, Sands initiated the first international sales effort for the Broadband Division.  He and was eventually responsible for the sales profitability and performance of dedicated sales teams.  Sands most recently served as corporate vice president of Sales for NDS, a conditional access technology developer, where he coordinated and oversaw the sales strategies between North America and Europe.<br><br> "With the declassification of digital encryption codes allowing new suppliers to enter the market, Samsung is now positioned to offer high-performance set-top box and cable solutions to optimize the consumer experience with digital television," said <b>Thomas Rhee, senior vice president of Samsung Electronics' new business development team</b>.  "In our strategic preparation to build Samsung's presence in the cable industry this year and moving forward, we are excited to have Stan's expertise and talent to help aggressively drive sales for Samsung's cable division."<br><br>"Thanks to advances in technology and increasing market need for innovative suppliers, Samsung has a tremendous opportunity in the cable sector," said Sands. "Samsung has already seen some success as a set-top box supplier and intends to grow that success with other cable solutions, including televisions with preinstalled boxes.  I look forward to helping Samsung lead the way as the business continues to evolve."<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc.</b><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, advanced digital consumer electronics, information systems and home appliance products. The SEA organization oversees the North American operations of Samsung including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion. Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Network Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Enters 2008 As HDTV Market Share Leader Two Years Running
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    LAS VEGAS, N.V., January 6, 2008 - Samsung Electronics enters 2008 as the global and US market leader in HDTV.  Moreover, strong sales across its HDTV line catapulted it to the number one position from a revenue stand-point for the first time.  The NPD Group—a recognized authority for reporting consumer buying behavior and product demand within the consumer electronics industry—reported Samsung as the No.1 brand in the U.S. for digital television sales in both units and dollars, commanding more than 18 percent and 23 percent market share, respectively, during the January to November 2007 period. Additionally, it is the best-selling flat panel and micro display brand in the country from a volume and revenue perspective.  As the consumer electronics icon readies its newest lines of LCD, plasma, and DLP HDTVs for exhibition at the 2008 International Consumer Electronics Show, Samsung HDTVs will offer consumers more innovative design features and connectivity technology.  Samsung's HDTV lineup will be on display at Booth #11033 during the International Consumer Electronics Show held at the Las Vegas Convention Center, January 7 through 10.<br><br>"Samsung continues to be dedicated to providing consumers with the best, most cutting-edge technology, blended with superb styling to suit their lifestyles," said Tim Baxter, executive vice president of sales and marketing at Samsung Electronics America. "These numbers are purely a reflection of the fact that we're hitting the mark and consumers are voting for the Samsung brand in one of the hottest consumer spending categories."  <br><br>Leadership<br>Samsung's LCD and plasma HDTVs demonstrate the company's commitment to remain at the forefront of consumer electronics. In 2007, Samsung released a number of revolutionary features to improve picture performance, including the application of LED backlight to its critically acclaimed LCD TVs, and the employment of FilterBright technology to its stunning plasma TV line. This year, Samsung introduces a new line of HDTVs that enhances the use of the TV from a simple video playing device to a command center of a digital entertainment system that pulls content from the Internet, mobile devices and more. <br><br>Samsung continues its dominance in the DLP HDTV category through its concentration on design, performance and lower cost of ownership. The company's technology prowess has allowed it to stay on top with feature innovations like 3D-viewing compatibility and the brightest, long-lasting and energy-saving LED light engines.<br><br>Finally, Samsung is one of the few remaining manufacturers of quality CRT TVs for those looking for the best of a tried-and-true technology. It is because of all these things Samsung is able to offer choice, value and design beyond that of its competition.<br><br>Design<br>Inspired by the clean, modern designs in the automotive and fashion industries, select models of 2008 LCD and plasma HDTVs will bring a "Touch of Color" to consumers.  For the first time, a manufacturing technique, previously used only for smaller A/V devices and luxury car interiors, is now used by Samsung to create a distinctive TV that stands out in a sea of black offerings.  The new look is achieved by infusing a hint of amber coloring to the translucent cabinet to produce a clean, glass-like finish.  The manufacturing process behind this unique design feature is called TOC (Touch of Color).  <br><br>Connectivity<br>Samsung is also redefining the role HDTVs play in the home by integrating a variety of advanced connectivity features into more models than ever.  Many of 2008's entry-level and premium sets have side-mounted HDMI and USB 2.0 ports, enabling consumers to easily connect their digital devices for viewing images and video on their HDTV.  The more advanced models will be able to receive select RSS feeds, as well as streamed Web content and PC files via an optional digital media adaptor, transcending what traditionally has been a "viewing-only" device into a truly interactive media hub.  Additionally, Samsung is building on the success it had debuting the company's first line of 3D-ready DLP TVs last year by expanding the same capability to select plasma HDTV models. <br><br>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. <br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, advanced digital consumer electronics and home appliance products, including HDTVs, home theater systems, MP3 players, refrigerators and laundry machines.  A recognized innovation leader in consumer electronics design and technology, Samsung is the HDTV market leader in the U.S. and is the only manufacturer that produces all four major digital television technologies.  Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG, Microsoft And Teen Music Sensations ALY &amp; AJ Award $2 Million Worth Of Technology AND Software To Schools Through SAMSUNG'S Hope For Education Program
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>Louisiana, Dec. 20, 2007 -</b> Samsung's Hope for Education and Microsoft Corporation, along with teen music sensations Aly & AJ, will present Woodlake Elementary School in Mandeville, La., $200,000 in technology products and software at a special assembly for students, teachers and local dignitaries. Woodlake Elementary School which was and still is affected from Hurricane Katrina in 2005 is this year's grand prize winner in Samsung's Hope for Education fourth annual essay contest. <br><br>Essays were submitted by more than 8,200 schools through students, parents, teachers and principals who wanted to give their community schools a chance to benefit from this unique program.  In addition to Woodlake Elementary School, 30 first-prize winners were selected and will receive $60,000 in technology products and software for their school.  The technology prizes include Samsung's latest, award-winning products, such as Plasma and LCD high definition televisions; Ultra Mobile PCs; multi-function products; Smart Phones; digital camcorders; DVD players, LCD computer monitors, color printers and Microsoft's latest, award-winning software, such as Microsoft Student, Encarta, Office, etc. Those who submitted a winning entry on behalf of a winning school will be awarded a Samsung Ultra Mobile PC with Windows Vista. (For a complete list of winners, please see below.)<br><br>"We are honored and grateful to be selected as the winning school in the Samsung's Hope for Education essay contest," said Woodlake Elementary principal Dr. Jean Kreiger. "The technology and software being donated by Samsung's Hope for Education and Microsoft will provide the teachers of Woodlake Elementary with the most up-to-date education tools which will enhance the learning of our students."<br><br>In addition to the product and technology being donated to Woodlake, a classroom assistant dog will be given to the special education classroom at Woodlake Elementary.  Samsung North America introduced the successful "Friends for Life" program created in Korea to provide financial support for the training of special service animals to assist kids and others who through the use of a dedicated service dog can lead a better life.  <br><br>"With programs like Hope for Education, Samsung and Microsoft have the opportunity to provide the technology and software that not all schools are able to afford," said D.J. Oh, president and CEO, Samsung Electronics America. "With the addition of the classroom assistant dog from "Friends for Life," we are not only helping students better their education in the classroom, but their quality of life as they go about their school day." <br><br>"Microsoft is proud to be a part of Samsung's Hope for Education program - recognizing deserving schools and creating opportunities through technology and software for their students," said Anthony Salcito, general manager of U.S. Education at Microsoft. "The tools we are providing these winning schools will enable students to remain competitive with the rest of the world and further their education while helping bridge the global technology gap."<br><br>Furthering education and reading is an important initiative for sister actresses and singer-songwriters Aly & AJ.  Through Samsung's partnership with their label Hollywood Records, the teen sensations helped launch the 2007 Samsung Hope for Education program this Spring in New York City with a special performance and will be entertaining more than 600 students at Woodlake during their special event.  <br> <br>"We are very proud to be a part of Samsung's Hope for Education program because it provides schools with the tools they need to foster growth and education in students," said Aly.  "Receiving the best education possible has been very important to us, and we applaud Samsung and Microsoft for coming together for the betterment of schools and youth," added AJ.<br><br>The Hope for Education contest was first announced in 2004 at the opening of the Samsung Experience, a unique and creative technology emporium in the Time Warner Center in New York City.  Since the original launch, more than 250 U.S. schools have benefited from over $7 million in Samsung technology and Microsoft software. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., markets a broad range of award-winning, advanced digital consumer electronics, information systems and home appliance products. The SEA organization oversees the North American operations of Samsung including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2005 parent company sales of US$56.7 billion and net income of US$7.5 billion. Employing approximately 128,000 people in over 90 offices in 51 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Appliance Business, Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business and Telecommunication Network Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs.  For more information, please visit www.samsung.com<br>     <br><br><b>About Microsoft</b><br>Founded in 1975 and Headquartered in Redmond, Washington, Microsoft (Nasdaq "MSFT") is the worldwide leader in software; services and solutions that help people, institutions, and businesses realize their full potential. Specifically, in education Microsoft is working closely with worldwide education communities, and has developed technology, tools, programs, and solutions to help address education challenges while improving teaching and learning opportunities.<br><br><b>About Aly & AJ</b><br>There's no limit to what sisters Aly and AJ Michalka can do.  They are actresses, singer-songwriters who play their own instruments, astute business women with multiple product lines, and philanthropists as well.  Their debut album "Into The Rush" sold over a million copies. Their Christmas CD, "Acoustic Hearts of Christmas" was one of the top-selling CDs of the season. Their "Insomniatic" album opened to massive critical acclaim.   Aly and AJ have released songs for many different films including hits such as "No One" that was featured in the motion picture Ice Princess; a rockin' cover of The Lovin' Spoonful's "Do You Believe in Magic;" and a cover of Katrina and the Waves' "Walking on Sunshine" that was featured in the major motion picture Herbie: Fully Loaded. Aly & AJ recently starred in the new MTV movie, "Super Sweet 16," which debuted this past summer. Both girls are filming movies for the big screen.  Aly is set to star in "Will" and AJ is featured in the Peter Jackson directed "The Lovely Bones." In addition, Aly & AJ completed a sold out US headline tour.   <br><br><b>About Hollywood Records</b><br>The Disney Music Group encompasses all of the Walt Disney Studio's recorded music and music publishing operations, including Hollywood Records, Walt Disney Records, Lyric Street Records and Walt Disney Music Publishing. Artists include Aly & AJ, Raven Simone, Vanessa Hudgens, Jonas Brothers and more. For more information, please visit www.hollywoodrecords.com<br><br><b>2007 Samsung's Hope For Education First Prize Winners</b><br><br>Bonne Ecole Elementary School			Slidell, La. <br>Cisco Junior High School			Cisco, Texas<br>Ramer Elementary School			Ramer, Tenn.<br>Roosevelt High School				San Antonio, Texas<br>Brentsville District High School			Nokesville, Va. <br>Cox's Creek Elementary School			Cox's Creek, Ky. <br>Piedmont Middle School			Monroe, N.C.<br>Emma C. Attales Middle School			Absecon, N.J. <br>Memorial High School				St. Mary's, Ohio<br>Lakeland High School				Shrub Oak, N.Y.<br>Woodbine Elementary School			Woodbine, Ga. <br>Wessendorff Middle School			Rosenberg, Texas<br>Avonworth Elementary School			Pittsburgh, Pa. <br>Indian Creek High School			Wintersville, Ohio<br>Mansfield Middle School			Mansfield, La.<br>Grantsburg High School			Grantsburg, Wis.<br>Discovery Elementary School			Brigham City, Utah <br>Deane Bozeman High School			Panama City, Fla. <br>South Pekin Elementary School			South Pekin, Ill.<br>Cucamongo Middle School			Rancho Cucamonga, Calif.	<br>Inkster High School				Inkster, Mich.<br>Hattiesburg High School			Hattiesburg, Miss.	<br>Liberty High School				Liberty, Texas<br>Hendersonville Elementary School		Walterboro, S.C.<br>Tazewell Elementary School			Tazewell, Va.<br>Mt. Vernon High School			Mt. Vernon, Texas<br>Wylie E. Groves School			Beverly Hills, Mich.<br>Glenn Stephens School			Madison, Wis.<br>Salem Lutheran School			Orange, Calif.<br>Magnolia School				Orlando, Fla.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Awards $30,000 Grand Prize Package To The Crossroads School
            </title>
            
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>BALTIMORE - October 30, 2007</b> - Samsung Electronics America, Inc., a global leader in digital technology, today announced The Crossroads School in Baltimore, MD, as the winner of the company's "Be Your School's Hero" contest, which honors one winning school with $30,000 in Samsung's latest innovative technology products. <br><br>Steve Glickman, IT coordinator at The Crossroads School, accepted the award at a press conference held at the school, along with Marc Martin, the school's principal, and Scott Raymond, Vice President of Education of the Living Classrooms Foundation.<br><br>The grand prize package included several of Samsung's award-winning products totaling a value of more than $30,000: color laser printers and multifunction printers including ten CLP-300N color laser printers, one LCD high-definition television, one camcorder, and one DVD-VHS combo player.<br><br>Jay Shears, Samsung's Director of Office Automation, presented the award to The Crossroads School.  "Samsung's commitment to Education is strong. Our hope is to use our leading technology solutions in order to create opportunities for students and help them prepare for the future," said Shears.  "We are proud to provide the technology resources to enhance the learning experience at The Crossroads School and help the deserving student body realize its full potential."<br><br>"The Crossroads School is grateful that Samsung recognizes the importance of technology in the classroom and how it's beneficial to the growth and success of the students at the school," said Steve Glickman, IT Director and teacher at The Crossroads School.  "We look forward to incorporating these new resources into the students' everyday learning and watching them prosper because of this generous donation." <br><br>The Crossroads School is a public, tuition-free charter middle school operated by Living Classrooms Foundation through a contract with the Baltimore City Public School System. The school, which opened its doors in September 2002, draws underserved youth from some of Baltimore's most challenged communities, and currently serves 150 students in sixth through eighth grades. <br><br>The Crossroads School prides itself on being a "school of choice" whereby students, families, and teachers choose to be a part of the Crossroads educational community.  The curriculum focuses on the fundamentals of reading, writing, and math with a hands-on, interdisciplinary approach.  Technology, cooperative learning, critical thinking, and real-world application of knowledge are also considered to be fundamental to the core curriculum.<br><br><b>Editor's Note:</b> To speak with a representative from The Crossroads School, please contact Kristi Betz directly at 410.243.1333 ext 225 or via email at kbetz@weinbergharris.com.<br><br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) markets a complete line of award-winning LCD Monitor products, including professional large format LCD and Plasma displays.  ITD also markets an award-winning line of color and monochrome laser printers and multifunction devices, video security systems and the family of Samsung Q1 Ultra-Mobile Personal Computers (UMPC).  Samsung ITD is committed to supporting the needs of its channel partners in the professional, commercial, corporate, and SOHO markets. Based in Irvine, California, ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC). The SEA organization oversees the North American operations of Samsung including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. Please visit www.samsung.com for more information or call 1-800-SAMSUNG for more information.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2005 parent company sales of US $56.7 billion and net income of US $7.5 billion. Employing approximately 128,000 people in over 90 offices in 51 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Appliance Business, Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business and Telecommunication Network Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.<br><br><b>About Living Classrooms Foundation (www.livingclassrooms.org):</b><br>Living Classrooms Foundation is a non-profit organization, operated for the benefit of the community at large, providing hands-on education and job skills training for students from diverse backgrounds, with a special emphasis on serving at-risk youth.<br><br>The Foundation uses maritime settings, community revitalization projects and other challenging learning environments, and a low staff to student ratio. Our "learning by doing" education programs emphasize the applied learning of math, science, literacy, history, economics, and ecology. Key objectives of all Living Classrooms programs are career development, community service, elevating self-esteem, and fostering multicultural exchange.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Proud To Present Amazing Booth At The 2007 World Cyber Games Grand Finals In U.S.
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>Seattle, Wash., Oct. 2, 2007</b> - Top gamers from around the world will converge in Seattle this week to compete for the title of 2007 World Cyber Game Champion. Samsung is proud to continue its worldwide partnership of the largest global gaming tournament and festival. Throughout the week, Samsung will be hosting various events and competitions at their booth to celebrate their seven years as title sponsor and showcase the "gamer-friendly" products that Samsung has to offer.  <br><br>Samsung will be the exclusive provider of HDTV displays for the Xbox 360 matches, handset provider for Samsung Mobile Challenge and top-rated monitors for the PC matches. Additional exclusive sponsorship categories include cellular handsets, MP3 music players and computer printers.  For more information on sponsorship categories, please see below. <br><br>"Samsung is committed to improving the gaming experience and working with gamers that participate in the World Cyber Games," said D.J. Oh, president and CEO of Samsung Electronics, America.  "We are always looking for opportunities to provide the gamers with top quality products that ensure their gaming experience is even more compelling."<br><br>"We're extremely pleased to have Samsung as a partner as we continue to support the growth of e-Sports from a niche market to a mainstream of entertainment platform," said Michael Arzt, general manager and senior vice-president for ICM USA, organizers of the World Cyber Games USA Championships. "It's a natural fit for the world's best consumer electronics brand to sponsor the premiere e-Sports tournament competition." <br><br>Throughout the week, visitors to the World Cyber Games Grand Finals can stop by the Samsung booth at Qwest Field Events Center to check out the latest and greatest in consumer electronics that will enhance anyone's gaming experience.  Samsung will be hosting a gaming competition where fans will have the opportunity to compete against some of Seattle's local athletes in the sporting video games.<br><br>In addition to competing for cash prizes, WCG champions will be receiving Samsung products. For each first, second and third-place finisher, Samsung will be providing them some new Samsung technology. First place winners in each of the 19 games being played will also receive a Samsung SyncMaster931C monitor.<br><br>With well over 1.5 million players from 74 countries, the World Cyber Games is the gaming world's premier video game tournament. Featuring online and offline events held throughout the world, the World Cyber Games uses a year-long qualifying format similar to the Olympics, where gamers first compete to earn a spot on their respective national teams before playing against the best video game players in the world in e-Sport's most prestigious tournament, the World Cyber Games Grand Final. The WCG 2006 Grand Final in Monza, Italy, broke new ground as more than 24 million people tuned in to watch the competition unfold in real-time, marking the first-ever global, live satellite broadcast for an e-Sports event.  For more information about the World Cyber Games visit: <a href="www.worldcybergames.com">www.worldcybergames.com</a>.<br><br><b>Samsung World Cyber Games Official Sponsorship Categories:</b><br><br><b>1. Monitor </b><br>- SyncMaster 931C monitor selected as official game monitor <br>- LCD monitors will be used for all video games from 2007<br>- 600 931C SyncMaster monitors used as tournament game<br>- SyncMaster Practice Plaza <br>- Monitor donation ceremony at press conference<br><br><b>2. MP3 Player </b><br>- 200 MP3P(model P2, T10) will be used as prizes and VIP gifts<br>- Provided as a prize at the radio promotion<br><br><b>3. Camera </b><br>- WCG official camera<br>- Samsung Camera experience  in photo zone of the exhibition hall<br><br><b>4. Mobile </b><br>- Hold "Samsung Mobile challenge" using Samsung mobile at Samsung booth <br>- Mobile to be designated as Official game from 2008<br><br><b>5. ODD (Optical Disc Drive)</b><br>- New external DVD writer (SE-S204N) <br><br>In addition to products above, Samsung will also provides following items.<br>- <b>PDP</b><br>- 50 PDP will be installed at press center and VIP reception etc for providing information.<br>- <b>Printer</b><br>- 8 Printers will be installed at press center for 500 journalists.<br><br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion. Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Network Business, and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com<br><br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, advanced digital consumer electronics and home appliance products, including HDTVs, home theater systems, MP3 players, refrigerators and laundry machines.  A recognized innovation leader in consumer electronics design and technology, Samsung is the HDTV market leader in the U.S. and is the only manufacturer that produces all four major digital television technologies.  Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.<br><br><br><b>About World Cyber Games</b><br>The World Cyber Games (www.worldcybergames.com) is the premier blue chip global video game tournament and culture festival.  Founded in 2000 to promote global harmony through e-Sports, the WCG has grown steadily ever since. Behind the slogan "Beyond the Game" and with contestants from more than 70 countries expected to participate in this year's event, the World Cyber Games has developed into a true global phenomenon with arguably the largest prize amount at stake. The World Cyber Games prides itself on leading the "Digital Entertainment Culture."
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Electronics And International Cyber Marketing To Make Donation Of 600 PC Monitors And Plasmas To Technology Access Foundation During The  World Cyber Games 2007 Grand Finals
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>Seattle, Wash., Oct. 4, 2007</b> - Samsung Electronics Co.Ltd., a global leader in digital consumer electronics and information technology and International Cyber Marketing (ICM) will be donating 600 SyncMaster 931C monitors and five plasmas to Seattle's Technology Access Foundation.  The announcement will be part of the opening ceremonies of the World Cyber Games 2007 Grand Finals at Qwest Field. <br><br>"We are proud to make this donation and leave something permanent in Seattle following the Grand Finals," said D.J. Oh, president and CEO of Samsung Electronics, America.  "Corporate philanthropy is very important to our organization and with donations like this as well as programs such as Hope for Education, Samsung knows it is helping children exceed in education through technology."<br><br>"The World Cyber Games is thrilled to be a part of Samsung's incredible donation to Seattle's Technology Access Foundation," said Hyoung-Seok Kim, CEO of International Cyber Marketing, organizers of the WCG. "World Cyber Games' partners have a history of contributing to the educational and technological infrastructure of tournament host cities and Samsung has certainly continued this legacy."<br><br>"We are honored that Samsung has chosen our organization to make the monitor donation," said Executive Director and Co-founder Trish Millines Dziko. "We know that these monitors will help the underserved children we teach get more out of their projects with up-to-date technological tools instead of being slowed down by outdated equipment."  <br><br>The Sync Master 931C is a 19-inch TFT LCD monitor that features 97 percent of the NTSC (National Television System Committee) color gamut for CCFL (Cold Cathode Fluorescent Lamp) displays. It provides a dazzling CCFL color range of 97 percent, which allows for optimal graphics and colors for gaming. Additionally, more vibrant, true-to-life images can be created. <br><br>With well over 1.5 million players from 74 countries, the World Cyber Games is the gaming world's premier video game tournament. Featuring on-line and off-line events held throughout the world, the World Cyber Games uses a year-long qualifying format similar to the Olympics, where gamers first compete to earn a spot on their respective national teams before playing against the best video game players in the world in e-Sport's most prestigious tournament, the World Cyber Games Grand Final. The WCG 2006 Grand Final in Monza, Italy, broke new ground as more than 24 million people tuned in to watch the competition unfold in real-time, marking the first-ever global, live satellite broadcast for an e-Sports event.  For more information about the World Cyber Games visit: www.worldcybergames.com.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion. Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Network Business, and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <a href="http://www.samsung.com">www.samsung.com</a><br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc.</b><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, advanced digital consumer electronics and home appliance products, including HDTVs, home theater systems, MP3 players, refrigerators and laundry machines.  A recognized innovation leader in consumer electronics design and technology, Samsung is the HDTV market leader in the U.S. and is the only manufacturer that produces all four major digital television technologies.  Please visit <a href="http://www.samsung.com">www.samsung.com</a> for more <br>information.<br><br><b>About World Cyber Games</b><br>The World Cyber Games (<a href="http://www.worldcybergames.com">www.worldcybergames.com</a>) is the premiere blue chip global tournament and cultural cyber festival in gaming, with well over 1.5 million players from more than 74 countries participating annually. Founded in 2000 and credited with launching the professional careers of many of the planet's top video game players, the World Cyber Games uses a yearlong tournament format, which begins with online, regional and national competitions in each country. National finalists then compete in the ultimate international tournament in e-Sports, The World Cyber Games Grand Final, where each country's best players compete for the largest and most prestigious prize in competitive gaming. The 2007 Grand Final will be held at Qwest Field in Seattle, Washington October 4-7.<br><br><b>About Technology Access Foundation</b><br>The Technology Access Foundation (TAF) prepares underserved children of color for higher education and professional success by providing a rigorous and relevant K-12 curriculum.  TAF makes education a priority in underserved communities. Serving one child at a time, TAF enhances their educational and professional prospects through the delivery of tools for learning in the 21st century.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG Announces New Multi-Year Sponsorship As The Official HDTV Of The NFL
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>Ridgefield Park, N.J., August 24, 2007 </b>- Samsung Electronics America Inc., the market leader in HDTVs, is proud to announce the company will be continuing its successful sponsorship as the Official HDTV of the NFL with a new multi-year sponsorship contract.  The NFL also chose Samsung HDTVs to be installed in select areas of all stadiums as part of the league's recent HDTV upgrade.  For the first time, critical insights can be relayed to the field from the coach's booth based on viewing the game on Samsung High Definition Televisions. <br><br>As America's leader in HDTVs coupled with complimentary source products like next generation DVD Players and Home Theater Systems, Samsung receives several key designations through the NFL sponsorship, including Official HDTV of the NFL and Official Home Theater of the NFL.<br> <br>"We are excited to expand upon our relationship with the NFL after serving as the Official HDTV of the NFL for the past two years," said Tim Baxter, Executive Vice President of Sales and Marketing at Samsung Electronics.  "As the number 1 provider of HDTVs, Samsung strives to bring innovative HDTV technologies that enhance the HD viewing experience for football and sports fans everywhere.  We are proud to be the number 1 pick of the NFL and a part of the most-watched sport in the country." <br><br>"The NFL prides itself in identifying key sponsors to support the continued success and innovation of the sport," said Peter Murray, the NFL's Senior Vice President of Partnership Marketing and Sales.  "We are pleased to expand our relationship with Samsung which over the last two years has contributed greatly to enhancing the high definition viewing experience of football."  <br><br>Samsung's sponsorship of the NFL will be activated in a comprehensive marketing campaign and through Samsung's major retail partners.<br><br><b><u>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc.</u></b><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, advanced digital consumer electronics and home appliance products, including HDTVs, home theater systems, MP3 players, refrigerators and laundry machines.  A recognized innovation leader in consumer electronics design and technology, Samsung is the HDTV market leader in the U.S. and is the only manufacturer that produces all four major digital television technologies.  Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                Exclusive Performance By Grammy Award Winning Alicia Keys Highlights Sixth Annual SAMSUNG Four Seasons Of Hope Annual Charity Gala
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    NEW YORK, June 18, 2007 - Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope, an innovative goodwill program, held its sixth annual celebrity gala to benefit children and families in need tonight at New York'sCipriani Wall Street. This year's event featured "Live with Regis and Kelly" host, Regis Philbin who returned for his third gala to help recognize the charitable efforts of sports, entertainment and political notables, including former NYC Mayor Rudy Guliani,  Joe Torre, Earvin "Magic" Johnson, Wayne Gretzky, Boomer Esiason, Arnold Palmer, and Dan Marino. <br><br>Singer, song-writer, actress Alicia Keys gave a special live performance to raise money for her charity The Alicia Keys Family Foundation, an umbrella organization that provides support to the many non profit groups whose mission statement is devoted to the betterment of the World's children and their families. <br><br>The sold-out event featured a star-studded roster of celebrities from the worlds of sports, entertainment and politics, and included a silent auction of sports memorabilia and other exciting items that will help raise funds for all of the participating foundations and charities.<br><br>"Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope is proud to begin its sixth year on such a positive note raising $1 million for the program's charities and a wonderful performance by Alicia Keys," said D.J. Oh, president and CEO, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. "It is especially exciting and encouraging to see all of our partner corporations and superstars coming together to benefit children and families. Samsung looks forward to being able to support these charitable efforts for years to come."<br><br>A new addition to this year's program was the special delivery of an assistance dog named "Juanita" to an autistic family through the Dan Marino Foundation. Samsung North America introduced the successful "Friends for Life program" created in Korea to provide financial support for the training of special service animals to assist kids and others who through the use of a dedicated service dog lead a better quality of life.  Another dog named Sammy will go to a future family affected by autism and Samsung will be donating a classroom assistant dog to support special education. This dog will be given to the special education teacher/therapist at the grand prize winner of the 2007 Samsung Hope for Education program.<br><br>"Being able to provide additional support to a deserving family tonight was a very special moment," said Dan Marino of the dog donation. "Bringing this program to North America will hopefully help out many more families that have a child afflicted with autism or another illness."<br><br><br>Launched in 2002 by Samsung Electronics America, Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope is an innovative goodwill program dedicated to raising awareness and funds through national retail promotions with Best Buy, Circuit City, Sears and CompUSA.  The retailers have encouraged their customers to donate to the program through sales promotions and sweepstakes. To date, Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope program has raised more than $7.5 million for charity and won recognition for its achievements. <br><br>About Samsung Four Seasons of Hope charities:<br><br>The Dan Marino Foundation. The Dan Marino Foundation is a non-profit organization that provides integrated treatment programs, outreach services and research of chronic illnesses and developmental disabilities in children.<br><br>Joe Torre Safe At Home Foundation Created in 2002 to bring educational programs into schools and develop community awareness surrounding the issue of domestic violence.  <br><br>Arnold Palmer Hospital for Children & Women. Located in Orlando, FL, the hospital offers comprehensive healthcare services for children and women as well as nationally acclaimed specialty programs including the Congenital Heart Institute, Neonatal Intensive Care Unit, the third largest Labor & Delivery department in the nation and the region's only Level I trauma center. <br><br>Boomer Esiason Foundation to Benefit Cystic Fibrosis. Created by Boomer Esiason and his wife in 1993 after their son was diagnosed with cystic fibrosis, the foundation works to raise money to find a cure for the genetic disease. To date, more than $50 million has been raised for the cause. <br><br>The Wayne Gretzky Foundation. The Wayne Gretzky Foundation is dedicated to helping young people exercise and develop positive life skills through ice hockey.<br><br><br>The Magic Johnson Foundation. Founded by Magic Johnson following his retirement from the NBA in 1991, the foundation is committed to improving the quality of life for people residing in urban communities.  <br><br><br>St. Vincent's Catholic Medical Centers. </u> Rudy Giuliani's charitable efforts for St. Vincent's Catholic Medical Centers, one of the NY metropolitan area's most comprehensive health care systems, serving 600,000 people annually. The system includes nursing homes, hospice, substance abuse clinics and EMS services across the city.<br><br><br>For more information about Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope, please visit our Web site at www.fourseasonsofhope.com.<br> <br>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc <br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, advanced digital consumer electronics, information systems and home appliance products. The SEA organization oversees the North American operations of Samsung including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.<br><br><br>
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                Technology Partnership with IBM
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    On May 23, 2007, Samsung Electronics concluded technology partnership with IBM and other three companies. 

- Lisensor : IBM, Infineon, Chartered, and Freescale
- Technology subject to the agreement: 300mm wafer 32nm logic processing technology 

Samsung Electronics will enter into joint technology development with IBM and three other companies, and the development of next-generation 32nm logic processing technology will be completed by 2010. This aims at leading the next-generation logic processing technology standard.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                Cross License Agreement between Samsung Electronics and Microsoft
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    On April 19, 2007, Samsung Electronics and Microsoft reached a cross license agreement for the patented intellectual property.
-	Samsung Electronics expects this cross license agreement will further facilitate the development of differentiated products.
-	Samsung Electronics will be able to use Microsoft's current and future technology patents in computer, set-top box, DVD player, camcorder, TV set, printer, and home appliances.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                SAMSUNG and Microsoft Announce Broad Patent Agreement
            </title>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                    SEOUL, Korea - April 19, 2007 and REDMOND, Wash. - April 18, 2007 -Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. and Microsoft Corp. today announced that the companies entered into a broad patent cross licensing agreement. Samsung Electronics is the largest publisher of United States patents in 2006 and owner of one of the largest U.S. patent portfolios. The companies expect the agreement to accelerate their respective product development  efforts. Microsoft has actively sought patent agreements with a range of companies in an attempt to build bridges with an array of consumer electronics, telecommunications, computer hardware and Linux/Unix platform providers.<br>      <br>Through the agreement, Samsung will obtain access to Microsoft patents that may be practiced in a range of Samsung's existing and future product lines, such as computer products, set-top-boxes, digital media players, camcorders, televisions, printers,  and home appliances. In these product lines, Samsung and its distributors and customers may utilize Microsoft's patents in Samsung's products with proprietary software and Samsung will also obtain coverage from Microsoft for its customers' use of certain Linux-based products.<br><br>Likewise, Microsoft will gain access to Samsung's large patent portfolio relating to digital media and computer related inventions, for its existing and future products. The specific financial terms of the agreement are confidential, but both parties will receive monetary payments compensating them for the value of their portfolios.<br><br>Offering customers elegant, highly desirable products requires advanced scientific research and design inspiration," said Shung Hyun (Peter) Cho, Senior Vice President of the Digital Media R&D Center at Samsung  Electronics. "Patent collaboration agreements like this expand access  to ideas and lead to even more desirable products for our customers.<br><br>We are always looking for new opportunities to work collaboratively  within the industry and Samsung was a natural fit, particularly because of their leadership in the rapidly changing world of digital media technologies,       said Horacio Gutierrez, Vice President of Intellectual Property and Licensing at Microsoft. Companies that collaborate are in the best position to deliver the products and service that their customers demand.<br><br>Today's announcement is the latest in a growing set of agreements that help build bridges across a range of computer hardware, software and telecommunication products from the world's leading companies. In the past twelve months, Microsoft has announced similar agreements with companies such as Novell, NEC, Fuji-Xerox, Seiko-Epson and Nortel.<br><br>        <br>About Samsung<br><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion. Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Network Business, and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information please visit www.samsung.com.<br>
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>
                Teen Music Sensations ALY &amp; AJ To Serve As Spokespeople For 2007 SAMSUNG'S Hope For Education Program
            </title>
            <description>
                
                <![CDATA[
                    RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., April 11, 2007 -- Samsung's Hope for Education, an educational and philanthropic program designed to minimize the technology gap in the educational system today will be partnering with teen music sensations Aly & AJ for its 2007 program. Through a partnership with Microsoft Corporation, Hope for Education will provide more than $2 million in technology and software to K-12 schools in the U.S. that enter an essay competition describing how technology can help improve students' education.  The program, in its fourth year, is a demonstration of the company's unwavering commitment to making a positive difference in the lives of children and youth in supporting education and technology in schools nationwide.

This year's program will launch on April 11, at the Samsung Experience in New York City with a special performance and press conference by sister actresses and singer-songwriters Aly & AJ, who are currently working on a new album that will be released July 10.   Students and teachers from previous winning schools located in the New York Tri-State Area will be invited to attend and meet the teen superstars. 

"We are thrilled to partner with Aly & AJ for the 2007 Hope for Education program. These young women will help Samsung and Microsoft communicate directly to their young fans, many of which attend schools that lack the funding to purchase the kind of technology necessary to keep them competitive with the rest of the world." said D.J. Oh, president and CEO, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. "This year Samsung and Microsoft are further expanding the Hope for Education program to reach and include the Spanish-speaking Hispanic community. By accepting entries in Spanish, we will increase the opportunity to provide relevant and useful tools to support education."
 "We are very excited to be working with Samsung's Hope for Education to help Samsung and Microsoft raise awareness about how important it is to provide public schools with the latest technology and educational tools," said Aly & AJ.  "Receiving the best education possible has been very important to us, and we encourage all of our fans who want to help better their schools' technological resources to enter the essay contest and help bridge the technological gap that many schools face." 

In addition to serving as the program spokeswomen, Aly & AJ will assist the Hope for Education Advisory Council on judging the students' and schools' essays.  The Council is made up of professionals from the academic and editorial communities who are authorities on both education and technology. 

New this year, Samsung's Hope for Education is accepting entries of essays in both Spanish and English. As the 2007 program expands to accept Hispanic entries, so has the Hope for Education Advisory Council.  Ivelisse R. Estrada, senior vice president of corporate and community relations for Univision Communications Inc., and Alberto Vourvoulias-Bush, executive editor of El Diario/La Prensa, along with Darlene Pierce of the America Association of School Administrators will be joining existing Hope for Education Council members from Cornell University, the Wharton School of Business, USA TODAY and TWICE (a consumer electronic trade publication). 

The Hope for Education contest runs through July 22, 2007. Students, parents, teachers and administrators can enter the contest by going to www.hopeforeducation.com and submit a 100-word essay about their school, answering the question: "What is the single most significant benefit that technology can provide in the classroom?"  
   
Schools that submit essays are entered for the opportunity to win either the grand prize of $200,000 in Samsung technology and Microsoft software or one of 30 first prizes of $60,000 in Samsung technology and Microsoft software.  The technology prizes include Samsung's latest, award-winning products, such as Plasma, LCD, and DLP high definition televisions; Ultra Mobile PCs; multi-function products; Smart Phones; digital camcorders;  DVD players, LCD computer monitors, color printers and Microsoft's latest, award-winning software, such as Microsoft Student, Encarta, Office, etc. Anyone who submits a winning entry on behalf of a winning school will be awarded a Samsung Ultra Mobile PC with Windows Vista.

"Microsoft shares Samsung's passion and vision for improving teaching and learning opportunities through the use of technology in the classroom," said Anthony Salcito, general manager of U.S. education at Microsoft. "Through our continued partnership with Samsung, we hope to recognize deserving schools and provide students with the tools that will help them realize their potential and prepare them for a global future." 

The Hope for Education contest was first announced in 2004 at the opening of the Samsung Experience, a unique and creative technology emporium in the Time Warner Center in New York City.  Since the original launch, more than 220 U.S. schools have benefited from over $5 million in Samsung technology and Microsoft software. 
About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. 
<br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA) markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products; and oversees Samsung's North American operations, including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc.  Its parent company, Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., ranks #5 in the 2006 Consumer Electronics segment of the Fortune Magazine "America's Most Admired Companies," and ranks # 20 in the BusinessWeek "The Best Global Brand 100 2006."  Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2006.  Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.

About Samsung Electronics
<br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion.  Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business areas: Digital Media, Telecommunication Network, Semiconductor, LCD, and Digital Appliance.  Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs.  For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.

About Microsoft
<br>Founded in 1975, Microsoft (Nasdaq "MSFT") is the worldwide leader in software; services and solutions that help people and businesses realize their full potential.

About Aly & AJ
<br>Sisters Aly and AJ are actresses, singer-songwriters and guitarists whose album "Into The Rush" sold over a million copies. Their Christmas CD, "Acoustic Hearts of Christmas" was one of the top-selling CDs of the season.  Currently Aly & AJ are working on a new album that will be released July 10 and their worldwide tour will begin in mid-Summer. Aly and AJ have released songs for many different films including hits such as "No One" that was featured in the motion picture Ice Princess; a rockin' cover of The Lovin' Spoonful's "Do You Believe in Magic;" and a cover of Katrina and the Waves' "Walking on Sunshine" that was featured in the major motion picture Herbie: Fully Loaded. In addition to their music, Aly & AJ star in the new MTV movie, "Super Sweet 16," which debuts on July 7.
                ]]>
            </description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
