<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>

        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Launches Mobile Experience Tour  To Showcase Affordable Printing Solutions For Business</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    <b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., March 5, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America, Inc</b>., a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, the world's second-largest manufacturer of laser printer engines, announced the launch of The Samsung Mobile Experience Tour 2009, a 30-city U.S. campaign, sponsored by the Samsung Printing Solutions group.  The program aims to help drive awareness among solution providers and their enterprise customers of the company's cost-effective printing solutions for business.  The centerpiece of the campaign is a customized, 40-foot RV that serves as a mobile showcase for Samsung's printers and other IT products.  The tour launched late January in Tampa, Fla. during Super Bowl XLIII 2009.<br><br>The Samsung Mobile Experience RV carries seven single-function printers and multifunctional printers that offer the fast, high-quality output, seamless plug-and-play connectivity and user-friendliness businesses desire.  These models include the <b>CLX-8380ND, SCX-6555N, CLX-6240FX, SCX-4828FN and SCX-5835FN</b> multifunctional printers, and the CLP-660ND and ML-4050N laser printers.<br><br>"Samsung has always been committed to creating technology that makes sense from an operational, design and budget perspective for our business customers.  This tour shows the collective impact that those elements bring to today's office space," said<b> JH Kim, President of Samsung Electronics America's Information Technology Division</b>.  "The intimacy of the campaign allows customers to interact with printing solutions to help alleviate the guesswork for IT decision makers, which, in turn, helps Samsung and its solution providers strengthen their relationships within the market.  The Samsung Mobile Experience underscores our consistent support for both our end users and solution providers.  It gives them a venue where they can productively engage with one another, and receive real-time feedback to help them work smarter and grow their businesses.<br><br>Intellinetics is one of the solution providers that will have the opportunity to showcase to customers the benefits of integrating their document management technology within Samsung printers.<br><br>"Intellinetics is pleased to work in partnership with Samsung on this campaign, as it not only empowers customers to think in new ways on how to better manage their businesses, but it provides a stage on which providers like us can bring to life our printer solutions," said<b> Matt Chretian, President of Intellinetics</b>.  "These types of innovative programs allow us to connect with the market, which in turn helps to position us as a reliable resource for customers' document management needs."<br><br>As an incentive, a 46-inch Samsung LCD TV will be awarded in a monthly drawing to select customers who complete an online survey.<br><br>For more information on the Samsung Mobile Experience Tour 2009, please contact your local sales representative or E-mail SMET@samsung.com.  Interested parties also can visit the tour's Web site at <a href="http://www.samsungmobileexperiencetour.com" target="_blank"> www.samsungmobileexperiencetour.com</a>. <br><br>Samsung supports customer satisfaction with multiple service and warranty options.  A toll-free technical support line can be accessed by calling 1-800-SAMSUNG - choose option 3 for printers.  For more information on Samsung's full line of professional series laser printers and MFPs, call 1-866 SAM4BIZ or visit <b>www.samsung.com/printer</b>.  <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) is one of the fastest growing IT companies in the U.S., and is committed to serving the IT needs of consumers ranging from the home user to the Fortune 500 elite, and supports the valued solution providers who serve our customers.  Offering innovative solutions and award-winning designs, Samsung ITD presents a complete line of award-winning color- and mono-laser printing solutions, desktop monitors, notebook computers, digital signage solutions and projectors.  Based in Ridgefield Park, N.J., ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com or call 1-800-SAMSUNG</b>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Samsung Showcases Latest Products at  IFA 2007</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    Berlin, Germany — August 30, 2007 — Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., a global leader in consumer electronics and digital technology, unveils its innovative products based on digital technology and imaginative ideas at IFA 2007.<br><br>The new range of products is designed to inspire experiences for a New Home and Mobile Life.  Products showcasing the New Home Life range include the 70" LED LCD TV, the Duo Player, the first BD Home theater system and the smallest color laser printer. Products which highlight the New Mobile Life range include the 3" compact video player and compact HD camcorders. <br><br>Focusing on customers who want to create their own lifestyle, Samsung is displaying its design driven products together with leading furniture companies such as Fritz Hansen of Denmark. The Samsung style zone offers differentiated lifestyle concepts ranging from Minimal Luxury, Retro Modern to Cultural Mix style.<br><br>Dr. Jong Woo Park, President of Samsung's Digital Media Business said "Our innovative products reinforce Samsung's technology and design leadership in the CE industry. Samsung will continue to launch innovative products bringing to consumers not only new lifestyles but also the best technology." <br><br>At IFA 2007, visitors will be able to see and experience a broad portfolio of products for New Home Life and New Mobile Life. Highlights include:<br><br><br>-The new F9 series TVs (52", 70") with new LED Smart lighting technology, known as "local dimming", delivering more vivid colors and ultra-sharp images.<br><br>-Samsung's New Full HD TV F8 line with 100Hz MotionPLUS  technology which eliminates blurring in fast moving pictures. The new lineup comes in elegantly styled glossy black bezel that boast soft, understated lines touched off by Samsung's signature crystal clear glass trim, icy-blue lighting, and the uniquely sophisticated side switches.<br><br>-The BD-UP5000, Samsung's first dual-format High-Definition (HD) optical disc player, supports both Blu-ray and HD-DVD formats as well as their interactive technologies, BD-Java and HDi. Consumers can now enjoy additional studio content such as trailers, director's comments, more elaborate interactive menus and behind the scene footage in any format.<br><br>-The HT-BD2, home theater solution with Blu-ray, offers full compatibility with 24 movie frames per second playback and 1,100 Watts of total output power to keep movie and audio fans satisfied with a sleek and sophisticated component system. <br><br>-The VP-HMX10C delivers the highest level of HDTV picture quality with a 2.7" high resolution touch panel LCD screen and easy-to-use functions.<br><br>-Only 9.9 mm slim, the high-tech mp3 player YP-P2 showcases a high resolution 3" widescreen with <br>Bluetooth 2.0 support.<br><br>-A monitor embedded with simple networking modules, the SyncMaster 220TN enables users to go  online and make video calls when connected to LAN cable even without a PC.<br><br>-A slim, sleek and silent mono laser multifunction printer, the SCX-4500, exudes a sense of luxury while displaying a sense of sensibility.<br><br><br>Widely recognized for its excellence in digital technology, Samsung products were honored with 4 EISA awards: LCD TV (LE40R81B/86BD), HT system (HT-TXQ120), Design Camera (i70) and Mobile Phone (SGH-U700). All of Samsung's EISA award winning products will be on display in the Samsung booth (Hall 20).<br> <br>Please visit Samsung Electronics' stand in Hall 20.<br><br>More information on Samsung at IFA 2007 is available at www.samsung.com/ifapress<br> <br><br> <br><br>About Samsung Electronics<br><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion. Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Network Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs.
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Showcases The Latest Mobile Technologies At CommunicAsia 2007</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    Singapore, June 19th, 2007 - Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., a leading provider of mobile phones and telecom systems, today showcased a total of 53 mobile phones and its latest mobile technologies at CommunicAsia 2007. Key highlights were the Ultra Edition II 12.1 (U700), the slimmest and elegantly designed HSDPA slider, the Ultra Edition II 10.9 (U600) 2.5G slider, and an exciting fashion phone lineup including the SGH-E950, E840, and J600. Samsung also introduced the Mobile WiMAX U-RAS Hub System (HS) and Convergence System (CS) for the first time in the world today.<br><br>Samsung's diverse, innovative and market-leading handsets and technologies, including its brand new Ultra Edition II range and Mobile WiMAX technology, reinforces Samsung's position as a design-led, forward-thinking company that heavily invests in research and development to advance the market and fuel consumer demand for innovative new technologies.<br><br>Mr. Geesung Choi, President of Samsung's Telecommunications Network Business, said :<br>"The introduction of Samsung's new Ultra Edition II range is testament to our strategic focus on the premium segment. In addition, Samsung's vision for the future of mobile technology is increasingly becoming a reality with our successful Mobile WiMAX demonstration, underlining the converged mobile device as the future hub of all communications. With our increased focus on the Southeast Asian market, we will continue to provide a wide variety of mobile phones customized for local needs."<br><br>Key highlights from Samsung at CommunicAsia 2007 include :<br><br>ULTRA EDITION II<br>Building on the runway success of Samsung's Ultra Edition range, launched in July 2006, the Samsung Ultra Edition II embodies the best of advanced technology, revolutionary mobile designs and must-have business and consumer multimedia functions with four of the slimmest, most powerful and best looking handsets in each form factor. The Ultra Edition II range consists of two stylish and functional sliders, the Ultra Edition 10.9 (U600) and the Ultra Edition 12.1 (U700), a metallic clamshell, the Ultra Edition 9.6 (U300), and a candy bar handset, the Ultra Edition 5.9 (U100). Each of these designs offer advanced features such as a 3-megapixel camera and camcorder, high-speed internet connectivity, as well as extensive multimedia and audio capabilities.<br><br>Proving that Samsung truly is at the heart of the consumer's needs, each of these handsets incorporates innovative consumer-driven design elements to improve the user experience, including external multimedia navigation keys for ease of use and a jewel-inspired casing.<br><br>FASHION PHONE LINE UP<br>For design- and style-focused customers, Samsung unveiled three fashion phones reflecting the latest design trends and cutting-edge multimedia features. The SGH-E950 is a powerful 3-megapixel camera phone equipped with an improved, unique touch navigation user interface, while the SGH-E840, with its minimalist and futuristic design, boasts a super slim frame at just 10.6mm and a glossy, mirror-like surface. The SGH-J600 comes with an affordable 1.3-megapixel camera in a variety of vivid, lively colours.<br><br>MOBILE WIMAX<br>Samsung today also unveiled the latest mobile convergence devices ready for Mobile WiMAX technology. Samsung conducted live demonstrations of Mobile WiMAX, including various applications such as push-to-all, IP TV, and more. At this year's CommunicAsia, Samsung proudly showcased the newly developed U-RAS Hybrid System (HS) and Converged System (CS), which offer more cost-effective system installation and maintenance by reducing the size of Mobile WiMAX Base Stations (U-RAS) and enlarging the coverage of Base Stations (U-RAS).<br><br>Learn more about Samsung's mobile technology and handsets at www.samsungcommunicasia2007.com and visit us at Hall 3, Stand 3L3-01 at CommunicAsia, Singapore.<br><br>About Samsung Electronics<br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion. Employing approximately 138,000 people in over 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Network Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs.<br>For more information, please visit www.samsung.com <br>
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Unveils Its Total Kitchen Solution And Cooks Up A Promotion With Disney&amp;#8226;PIXAR At KBIS</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    LAS VEGAS - May 8, 2007 - Samsung Electronics, an innovator in home appliances, further cements its commitment to the home appliance industry by unveiling a Total Kitchen Solution, featuring two new product offerings.  With its launch of the Electric Range and Dishwashers in the US market, the company now offers consumers a total suite of kitchen appliances, which includes over-the-range microwave ovens and the highest-rated refrigerators in the J.D. Power and Associates customer satisfaction survey. 
Samsung's new kitchen and laundry solutions will be showcased at the 2007 Kitchen and Bath Industry Show (K/BIS), May 8-10 in Las Vegas.  The Samsung booth (#C5613) will feature a 2-story "open house" that will highlight the advantages of Samsung's new VRT&#153; (Vibration Reduction Technology) Washing Machine.  Visitors can experience Samsung design and innovation in the kitchen and in laundry, as well as enjoy cooking demonstrations by well-known culinary expert, teacher and chef Lee Anne Wong, recently featured on Bravo's Top Chef. 
In addition, Samsung collaborates with Disney&#8226;Pixar on a promotion surrounding the launch of the company's French Door Refrigerator and the studio's new animated movie, Ratatouille, which is set in Paris.  At Samsung's booth, spectators can watch trailers of the movie in a Ratatouille-themed vignette that highlights Samsung's new Total Kitchen Solution.  
"Samsung is committed to developing high performing, beautifully designed home appliance products.  Consumers can now fully experience Samsung's kitchen solutions with the launch of its new line-up of free-standing electric ranges and dishwashers," said James Politeski, vice president of sales and marketing for the home appliance division at Samsung Electronics America.  He added, "The Samsung brand has become synonymous with innovation and our new line of home appliance products demonstrates how Samsung technology and design improves the way you cook and clean."
New Products from Samsung
"	The French Door Refrigerator offers bigger space and better storage with 26 cu. ft. of space.  Samsung's TWIN Cooling System&#153; allows each cabinet to be individually controlled and sealed - to help ensure optimum humidity and no mixture of odors between compartments.  The Energy Star refrigerators are currently available at a MSRP ranging from  $1,499 to $1,899.
    The Electric Range features AirVection&#153; technology for a professional baking experience at home, and SteamQuick&#153; technology for easy clean-up without scrubbing.  The new line-up has the largest capacity oven in the market at 5.7 cu. ft. and will be available in the 3rd quarter at a MSRP ranging from $899 to $1,299.
    The over-the-range microwave ovens come in a range of designs that match Samsung's suite of kitchen appliances.  The line-up consists of product offerings with 1.8 cu. ft of space, and sensor cooking.  Samsung's new line-up will be available in the 3rd quarter at a MSRP ranging from $248 to $348.
    Samsung's new line of Dishwashersis stylish and quiet, and available in matching finishes with other Samsung products in the Total Kitchen Solution.  The new products contain innovative features, such as a digital leakage sensor and fan-driven condensation-type drying system.  The products will be available in the fourth quarter of 2007 at a MSRP ranging from $699 to $999. 
    The VRT&#153; Washing Machine features advanced Vibration Reduction Technology which reduces the vibration and noise caused by unbalanced loads during the spin cycle of conventional front-loading washers.  The extra-large capacity laundry machines also include SilverCare&#153; technology which is a great option for removing odor-causing bacteria from colors and delicates in cold water without bleach.  It helps keep garments looking their best by minimizing fading and the tattering effects of hot water.  The VRT Washing Machine is currently available in Tango Red, Onyx Blue, Stratus Gray and Neat White at a MSRP ranging from $1,299 to $1,399.
Disney&#8226;Pixar Alliance
<br>Samsung is excited to support the theatrical release of the animated feature film, Ratatouille, from Walt Disney Pictures and Pixar Animation Studios.  Directed by Academy Award&reg;-winner Brad Bird ("The Incredibles"), Ratatouille is the hilarious tale of a rat named Remy who dreams of becoming a great chef despite his family's wishes and the obvious problem of being a rat in a decidedly rodent-phobic profession.  Samsung's collaboration with Disney&#8226;Pixar will include a national promotion tour that features Samsung's home appliance and plasma TV products and a sweepstakes beginning in May.  Ratatouille opens in theaters nationwide on June 29, 2007.
About Samsung Electronics America, Inc.

 
Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA) markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products; and oversees Samsung's North American operations, including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc.  Its parent company, Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., ranks #5 in the 2006 Consumer Electronics segment of the Fortune Magazine "America's Most Admired Companies," and ranks # 20 in the BusinessWeek "The Best Global Brand 100 2006."  Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2006.  Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.

About Samsung Electronics

 
Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion.  Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business areas: Digital Media, Telecommunication Network, Semiconductor, LCD, and Digital Appliance.  Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs.  For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.
Download Images
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG New VRT Front Loading Laundry Machine Turns Cleaning Clothes Into A Quiet Affair</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    LAS VEGAS - May 8, 2007 - Samsung Electronics, an innovator in home appliances, combines "style, stealth, and substance" with its new VRT™ Front Loading Washing Machine.  The VRT washer features a Samsung technological breakthrough called Vibration Reduction Technology that reduces the vibration and noise from unbalanced loads during the spin cycle of conventional front-loading washers.  The quietest washer with unbalanced loads, it will operate quieter on the second floor or near closets where consumers need it most.  The new VRT Washing Machine can be seen at Samsung's booth (#C5613) at the 2007 Kitchen and Bath Industry Show (K/BIS), May 8-10 in Las Vegas.<br><br>True to its commitment to stylish design, Samsung offers the VRT Washing Machine in an assortment of colors for the design-minded consumer.  It is now available in Tango Red, Onyx Blue, Stratus Gray and Neat White.  Stacked on top of one another or placed side-by-side on pedestals, the VRT washing machine and paired dryer can be easily integrated as an attractive focal point to any living environment.<br>"In tests involving unbalanced loads, Samsung's VRT machines proved to have both the lowest vibration and noise level of the front-loading washers tested," said Jeff Armstrong, Senior Marketing Manger of Home Appliance. "Many consumers are first-time front load washing machine purchasers and typically are unaware of the vibration and noise issues of conventional front-loading machines.  Samsung has a compelling solution to this common annoyance for consumers and provides them with a stylish design to complement their homes." <br>While the washer reduces noise and vibration, it does not skimp on power with a 1,300 RPM maximum spin speed during final spin and achieving better than 2.3 MEF, which is designated by the Department of Energy as "Tier 3," the highest level of Energy Star. <br>VRT washers also feature Samsung's SilverCare™ technology - a new option for cleaning delicate and colored fabrics.  SilverCare removes odor causing bacteria in cold water without bleach.  It helps keep garments looking their best by minimizing the fading and tattering effects of hot water, and can save energy when compared to standard hot water washing.<br>With an extra-large capacity of 3.8 cu. ft., the VRT Washing Machine can handle everything from a single pair of jeans to a king size comforter.  <br>Samsung's VRT Washing Machine is currently available at an MSRP of $1,299 for the Neat White model and $1,399 for the colored models.<br>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. <br><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA) markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products; and oversees Samsung's North American operations, including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc.  Its parent company, Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., ranks #5 in the 2006 Consumer Electronics segment of the Fortune Magazine "America's Most Admired Companies," and ranks # 20 in the BusinessWeek "The Best Global Brand 100 2006."  Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2006.  Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.<br><br>About Samsung Electronics <br><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion.  Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business areas: Digital Media, Telecommunication Network, Semiconductor, LCD, and Digital Appliance.  Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs.  For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.<br><br> Download Images<br><br><br><br><br><br><br>
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Unveils Its Total Kitchen Solution And Cooks Up A Promotion With Disney-PIXAR At KBIS</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    LAS VEGAS - May 8, 2007 - Samsung Electronics, an innovator in home appliances, further cements its commitment to the home appliance industry by unveiling a Total Kitchen Solution, featuring two new product offerings. With its launch of the Electric Range and Dishwashers in the US market, the company now offers consumers a total suite of kitchen appliances, which includes over-the-range microwave ovens and the highest-rated refrigerators in the J.D. Power and Associates customer satisfaction survey. <br>Samsung's new kitchen and laundry solutions will be showcased at the 2007 Kitchen and Bath Industry Show (K/BIS), May 8-10 in Las Vegas. The Samsung booth (#C5613) will feature a 2-story "open house" that will highlight the advantages of Samsung's new VRT™ (Vibration Reduction Technology) Washing Machine. Visitors can experience Samsung design and innovation in the kitchen and in laundry, as well as enjoy cooking demonstrations by well-known culinary expert, teacher and chef Lee Anne Wong, recently featured on Bravo's Top Chef. <br><br>In addition, Samsung collaborates with Disney-Pixar on a promotion surrounding the launch of the company's French Door Refrigerator and the studio's new animated movie, Ratatouille, which is set in Paris. At Samsung's booth, spectators can watch trailers of the movie in a Ratatouille-themed vignette that highlights Samsung's new Total Kitchen Solution. <br><br>"Samsung is committed to developing high performing, beautifully designed home appliance products. Consumers can now fully experience Samsung's kitchen solutions with the launch of its new line-up of free-standing electric ranges and dishwashers," said James Politeski, vice president of sales and marketing for the home appliance division at Samsung Electronics America. He added, "The Samsung brand has become synonymous with innovation and our new line of home appliance products demonstrates how Samsung technology and design improves the way you cook and clean."<br><br>New Products from Samsung<br><br>" The French Door Refrigerator offers bigger space and better storage with 26 cu. ft. of space. Samsung's TWIN Cooling System™ allows each cabinet to be individually controlled and sealed - to help ensure optimum humidity and no mixture of odors between compartments. The Energy Star refrigerators are currently available at a MSRP ranging from $1,499 to $1,899.<br><br>The Electric Range features AirVection™ technology for a professional baking experience at home, and SteamQuick™ technology for easy clean-up without scrubbing. The new line-up has the largest capacity oven in the market at 5.7 cu. ft. and will be available in the 3rd quarter at a MSRP ranging from $899 to $1,299. <br>The over-the-range microwave ovens come in a range of designs that match Samsung's suite of kitchen appliances. The line-up consists of product offerings with 1.8 cu. ft of space, and sensor cooking. Samsung's new line-up will be available in the 3rd quarter at a MSRP ranging from $248 to $348.<br><br>Samsung's new line of Dishwashersis stylish and quiet, and available in matching finishes with other Samsung products in the Total Kitchen Solution. The new products contain innovative features, such as a digital leakage sensor and fan-driven condensation-type drying system. The products will be available in the fourth quarter of 2007 at a MSRP ranging from $699 to $999. <br><br>The VRT™ Washing Machine features advanced Vibration Reduction Technology which reduces the vibration and noise caused by unbalanced loads during the spin cycle of conventional front-loading washers. The extra-large capacity laundry machines also include SilverCare™ technology which is a great option for removing odor-causing bacteria from colors and delicates in cold water without bleach. It helps keep garments looking their best by minimizing fading and the tattering effects of hot water. The VRT Washing Machine is currently available in Tango Red, Onyx Blue, Stratus Gray and Neat White at a MSRP ranging from $1,299 to $1,399.<br>Disney-Pixar Alliance<br>Samsung is excited to support the theatrical release of the animated feature film, Ratatouille, from Walt Disney Pictures and Pixar Animation Studios. Directed by Academy Award®-winner Brad Bird ("The Incredibles"), Ratatouille is the hilarious tale of a rat named Remy who dreams of becoming a great chef despite his family's wishes and the obvious problem of being a rat in a decidedly rodent-phobic profession. Samsung's collaboration with Disney-Pixar will include a national promotion tour that features Samsung's home appliance and plasma TV products and a sweepstakes beginning in May. Ratatouille opens in theaters nationwide on June 29, 2007.<br><br>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc.<br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA) markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products; and oversees Samsung's North American operations, including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. Its parent company, Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., ranks #5 in the 2006 Consumer Electronics segment of the Fortune Magazine "America's Most Admired Companies," and ranks # 20 in the BusinessWeek "The Best Global Brand 100 2006." Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2006. Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.<br><br>About Samsung Electronics<br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion. Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business areas: Digital Media, Telecommunication Network, Semiconductor, LCD, and Digital Appliance. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.<br>
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Combines Performance, Style and Culinary Cachet With Its New Kitchen Solutions</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    LAS VEGAS - MAY 8, 2007 - Samsung Electronics, an innovator in home appliances, brings to the US market a Total Kitchen Solution that delivers professional results to the home. Already a successful manufacturer of refrigerators, laundry machines and microwave ovens, Samsung will launch a line of French Door refrigerators, electric ranges and dishwashers. The entire suite of Samsung home appliance products can be seen at booth #C5613 during the 2007 Kitchen and Bath Industry Show (K/BIS), May 8-10 in Las Vegas. <br>Samsung innovation and styling will drive the company's 2007 kitchen appliance products to the forefront. The free-standing electric ranges feature AirVection™ technology - a patented 3 fan convection system for more even cooking and energy efficiency. In addition, Samsung's TWIN Cooling System™ technology is included in the company's first line of French Door refrigerators to help ensure optimum humidity and no mixture of odors between compartments.<br><br>"The Samsung brand is known for its breadth of offerings to consumers and we are excited to now offer consumers a complete line of kitchen appliances," said James Politeski, Vice President of Sales and Marketing for the home appliance division at Samsung Electronics America. "We have taken the performance and style consumers have grown to know and expect from Samsung products and applied it to the entire kitchen with the introduction of our French Door refrigerators, electric ranges and dishwashers."<br><br>The complete 2007 Samsung Total Kitchen Solution line of products includes:<br><br>French Door Refrigerators<br>After achieving the highest rating for refrigerators in the J.D. Power and Associates customer satisfaction survey for the past two years, Samsung now offers consumers the beauty and functionality of a full line of French Door refrigerators. The two side-by-side refrigerator doors offer consumers a wide open space, making it perfect for storing large platters and lots of leftovers. An optional external ice and water dispenser or internal water dispenser give added convenience. The bottom freezer contains two shelves, making it adaptable to any need. In total, Samsung's French Door refrigerator offers 26 cu. ft. of space. <br><br>The French Door refrigerators feature Samsung's Twin Cooling System™, which allows each cabinet to be individually controlled and sealed to help ensure optimum humidity and no mixture of odors between compartments. The CoolSelect Pantry™, a fridge within a fridge, also allows the consumer to select the temperature of the drawer depending on need - warmer for vegetables and cooler for cold cuts. Surround Airflow technology lets air circulate through multiple outlets at every shelf level. Samsung's new French Door refrigerators are Energy Star approved. <br><br>The standard model (RF265AA) is now available at a MSRP ranging from $1,499 to $1,799. The step-up model (RF266AA) includes an internal water dispenser and is available at a MSRP ranging from $1,599 to $1,899. The top-of-the-line model (RF267AA) comes with the added convenience of the external ice and water dispenser and will be available in July at a MSRP ranging from $2,199 to $2,499. All models come in stainless steel, stainless platinum, black and white.<br><br>Electric Ranges<br>Samsung's Electric Ranges are designed for the discriminating consumer who seeks professional baking performance at home. The product comes with the largest oven capacity in the market at 5.7 cu. ft. and SteamQuick™ technology - a Samsung innovation that uses steam to quickly clean the oven in only 25 minutes. The electric range line also features Samsung's AirVection&3153; oven technology - a patented three fan convection system to help ensure even cooking. <br><br>Samsung's electric ranges will be available in the fall. The standard model (FTQ3521W) will be offered in white, black and stainless/black and carry a MSRP of $899 (white and black) and $999 (stainless/black). The stainless steel professional model (FTQ386LU) will carry a MSRP of $1,299. <br><br>Microwave Ovens<br>To complement the new line of free-standing ranges, Samsung is also introducing matching over-the-range microwave ovens. The over-the-range microwave ovens have a cavity size of 1.8 cu. ft., operate at a powerful 1,100 watts and feature a 400 CFM ventilation fan - the strongest in the industry. Nine sensor cooking selections help provide great cooking results at the touch of a finger. Offered in black, white, and stainless steel/black combination, the standard model (SMH7185) will be available from this fall for a MSRP of $249 (black or white) and $299 (stainless steel and black combination). The full stainless steel top-of-the-line model (SMH7187) will be available from this fall for a MSRP of $349.<br><br>Dishwashers<br>Samsung's new line of dishwashers offers consumers quiet performance that is in style with the white, black and stainless steel finishes of other Samsung products in the Total Kitchen Solution. A host of Samsung innovations are included to make this first line of dishwashers an attractive but high-performing addition to Samsung's home appliance collection.<br><br>The front door panel of the dishwasher has a 6-layer insulation system which dampens the noise produced by water spray. A digital leakage sensor, located at the bottom of the machine, helps prevent leakage and water overflow. The fan-driven condensation-type drying system uses residual heat from the warm water inside the tub and a fan at the same time for more efficient and faster drying.<br><br>Front-control models and integrated-control models are available. The front-control DMR57 is available in white, black and stainless steel at a MSRP of $699 (white and black) and $799 (stainless steel). The integrated-control DMR77 is available in white, black and stainless steel at a MSRP of $899 (white and black) and $999 (stainless steel). All dishwashers will be coming to market in the fourth quarter of 2007. <br><br>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. <br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA) markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products; and oversees Samsung's North American operations, including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Semiconductor Inc., Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. Its parent company, Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., ranks #5 in the 2006 Consumer Electronics segment of the Fortune Magazine "America's Most Admired Companies," and ranks # 20 in the BusinessWeek "The Best Global Brand 100 2006." Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2006. Please visit www.samsung.com for more information. <br><br>About Samsung Electronics <br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion. Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business areas: Digital Media, Telecommunication Network, Semiconductor, LCD, and Digital Appliance. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.<br>
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG, STMicroelectronics and Metalink Unveil Wireless High-Definition IPTV Set-Top Box at CeBIT</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    Seoul, Korea; Geneva, Switzerland; and Yakum, Israel, March  19 , 2007 - Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies ; STMicroelectronics (NYSE: STM), the leader in set-top box chips ; and Metalink Ltd. (NASDAQ: MTLK), a provider of high-performance wireless and wireline broadband communication silicon solutions, today announced their collaboration to launch a revolutionary set-top box, which supports high-definition (HD) TV quality based on 802.11n wireless IPTV standard, at CeBIT in Hanover, Germany, March 15-21, 2007. CeBIT is the world's largest trade fair showcasing digital IT and telecommunications solutions for home and work environments.<br><br>  <br><br>  Samsung's SMT-H6155 is specifically designed for the delivery of HD IPTV over wireless LAN. It is equipped with the STi7109 chipset providing the HD video decoding technology from STMicroelectronics , and Metalink 's 802.11n WLAN Plus Ô chipset enabl ing the wireless delivery of multiple HD video streams throughout the home.<br><br>  <br><br>  "Our customers have shown great demand for high-definition multimedia contents via IPTV and the ability to facilitate content using Wireless LAN," said HEE-WON PARK , Vice President of Samsung's STB Development Group. "We believe that Samsung's SMT-H6155, equipped with STMicroelectronics' decoder and Metalink's 802.11n chipsets, will satisfy our consumers as a top-of-the-line set-top box for HD IPTV. The SMT-H6155 will be a product that consumers can come to trust and believe in as it represents Samsung's highest standard for quality."<br><br>  <br><br>  "Samsung is a global leader in set-top box products and a major customer of ST," commented Christos Lagomichos, Corporate Vice President, Home Entertainment Group General Manager at STMicroelectronics. "We are happy that our market leading HD decoder in cooperation with Metalink's WLAN Plus  allows us to provide Samsung with the most innovative and robust solution in the market today. This platform demonstrates the capability of ST's advanced decoders, such as the STi71xx family, which allows the set-top box to become a core multimedia appliance in the home network, for both operator and retail markets."<br><br>      <br><br>"We are proud to work together with set-top box global market leaders Samsung and STMicroelectronics," said Tzvika Shukhman, Metalink's chairman and CEO. "This cutting-edge product, embedding our WLAN Plus  technology, represents an important milestone in making ‘service provider grade' HD video networking over wireless LAN a reality. " <br><br>      <br><br>      To see a live demonstration of the solution please visit Samsung booth , D60 at Hall 26. <br><br>      <br><br>      Mike Arden, Principal Analyst, Broadband and Multimedia Research at ABI Research, noted: "STMicroelectronics holds the leading market share for STB decoders, and Samsung is the leading STB vendor in Asia-Pacific and second worldwide. Together, these companies will be in a strong position to capture market share in the IPTV STB market, which will grow from 4.7 million units shipped in 2006 to 41.2 million units shipped in 2011." <br>    <br><br><br>  About Samsung Electronics<br><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income of US$8.5 billion. Employing approximately 138,000 people in 124 offices in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Network Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com<br>    <br><br><br>  About STMicroelectronics <br><br> STMicroelectronics is a global leader in developing and delivering semiconductor solutions across the spectrum of microelectronics applications. An unrivalled combination of silicon and system expertise, manufacturing strength, Intellectual Property (IP) portfolio and strategic partners positions the Company at the forefront of System-on-Chip (SoC) technology and its products play a key role in enabling today's convergence markets. The Company's shares are traded on the New York Stock Exchange, on Euronext Paris and on the Milan Stock Exchange. In 2006, the Company's net revenues were $9.85 billion and net earnings were $782 million. Further information on ST can be found at www.st.com.<br><br><br>  About Metalink <br><br> Metalink Ltd. (NASDAQ: MTLK) is a leading provider of high performance wireless and wireline broadband communication silicon solutions. Metalink's WLAN and DSL technologies are designed to enable true broadband connectivity in every home, and its products revolutionize the broadband experience by facilitating the convergence of telecommunication, networking and entertainment. Metalink's WLAN Plus ™ is a high-throughput, 802.11n-draft-compliant wireless LAN technology optimized for the networked home entertainment environment. Featuring advanced MIMO technology and full support of QoS, and operating in both 2.4GHz and 5GHz bands, WLAN Plus  enables multi-room networking of multiple high-definition video streams. In addition, Metalink offers a broad range of symmetric DSL and VDSL products used by operators as a cost-effective network upgrade to support triple-play services. Headquartered in Yakum , Israel , the company has subsidiaries in Atlanta (US), South Korea , and Japan as well as an office in China. Further information is available at http://www.metalinkbb.com    <br>  <br><br><br>  About Samsungs STB. <br><br> The SMT-H6155 is a hybrid set-top box that combines IP and DVB-T (Digital Video Broadcasting - Terrestrial) reception capabilities. It fully supports the delivery of HD contents over the IP network, and enables various interactive functions like VoD and IP multi-casting. The cutting-edge SMT-H6155 combines MPEG-4 AVC/H264/C1 capabilities on a single chipset produced using STMicroelectronics' SoC platform, and supports Wireless Digital Video home Networking using 802.11n.  <br>    <br><br><br>  About STMicroelectronics' STi7109<br><br> The STi7109 is a single-chip MPEG-4 AVC and VC-1 decoder that embeds all the major functions of a set-top box in a single device, including a high-performance CPU, video-decoding circuitry, a wide range of peripheral devices, advanced connectivity features and support for emerging security standards.<br><br><br>  About Metalink's WLANPlusTM<br><br> The WLAN Plus  family consists of the company's MtW8170 baseband device and the MtW8150 radio frequency integrated circuit (RFIC). A combination of features enables Metalink's WLAN Plus  family to deliver multiple HDTV streams to any location within a radius of 100 feet, while maintaining full QoS performance. Innovative packet-aggregation techniques boost media access control (MAC) efficiency with double the effective throughput of other solutions. The inclusion of 2x3 real Multiple-In Multiple-Out (real MIMO) technology further improves throughput and QoS, and the use of sophisticated channel-bonding and antenna-loading techniques in the 5 GHz frequency band provide critical additional video-distribution performance.<br><br> <br><br> The WLAN Plus  chipset also includes a full implementation of an integrated lower and upper MAC, reducing dramatically the required processing power and memory allocation from the host application processor. This simplifies the integration with consumer electronics devices and reduces the total product cost. Additionally, Advanced Low Density Parity Check (LDPC) forward error-correction (FEC) coding significantly boosts coverage range and signal robustness as compared to previous approaches. The chipset also fully supports 802.11i security features and the 802.11e QoS standard, both of which are critical for high-priority voice and video services.  <br><br>
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Strengthens its Mobile Leadership at 3GSM</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    Barcelona,  February 12th, 2007 - Samsung  Electronics Co., Ltd., a leading provider of mobile phones and telecom systems,  underlines its commitment to the telecommunications industry by showcasing an  extensive portfolio of mobile handsets and technology at this year's 3GSM World  Congress in Barcelona.
<br>      
<br>      Diverse, innovative and market-leading handsets and  technologies, including a brand new Ultra Edition II range and the first  European demo of Mobile WiMAX, further strengthen Samsung's position as a  design-led, forward-thinking company that heavily invests in research and  development to advance the market and fuel consumer demand for innovative new  technologies.
<br>      
<br>      Samsung's design-driven, premium multimedia handsets are  epitomized in its Ultra Edition II and Ultra Special ranges, which will be  available during the first half of this year. Whilst its involvement in Europe's first mobile WiMAX demonstration, due to be  showcased by Samsung and partners, illustrates Samsung's dedication to mobile  technology leadership and investment in market-leading standards.
<br>      
<br>      Geesung Choi, President  of Samsung's Telecommunication Network Business, said:
<br>        "It is always  exciting to be part of such an important industry event, particularly because it is my first time attending as the President of  Samsung's Telecommunication Business. Our strategic focus on  premium line-ups will be further enhanced this year by the introduction of our  new Ultra Edition II and Ultra Special ranges. In addition, the realization of  Samsung's vision for future mobile technology is clearly supported with our  Mobile WiMAX demonstration, putting converged, mobile device at the hub of all  communications. In 2007, you will see a continued commitment from myself and  Samsung to listen to and respond to the needs of our customers even more  closely and ensure we are producing devices that further enhance lifestyles,  whether at work or at play."
<br>        
<br>        The new announcements at 3GSM World Congress include:
<br>        

          
        ULTRA EDITION II
<br>        Building on the  runaway success of Samsung's Ultra Edition range, launched in July 2006, the  Samsung Ultra Edition II embodies the best of rapidly advancing technology,  revolutionary mobile designs and must-have business and consumer desired  multimedia functionality to create four of the slimmest, most powerful and best  looking handsets in each form factor. The Ultra Edition II range consists of two  stylish and functional sliders, the Ultra Edition 10.9 (U600) and the Ultra  Edition 12.1 (U700), a metallic clamshell, the Ultra Edition 9.6 (U300), and a  candy bar handset, the Ultra Edition 5.9 (U100). Each of these designs offer  advanced features such as 3 megapixel cameras and camcorders, high-speed internet  connectivity, extensive multimedia and audio capabilities. Proving that Samsung  truly is at the heart of consumer needs, each of these handsets incorporates  innovative consumer driven design elements to improve the user experience,  including external multimedia navigation keys for ease of use and jewel  inspired casing, which enhance both the experience and appearance of using  these handsets.
<br>        
<br>        ULTRA SPECIAL LINE UP
<br>        Featuring  unrivaled design, these latest handsets have been created to bring a superior  range of multimedia experiences to consumers. The tender touch of Samsung's F700  keypad and its masses of multimedia functionality, including a 5 mega-pixel  camera and 7.2 Mbps High Speed Downlink Packet Access (HSDPA), make this the  easiest to use multimedia handset on the market. Samsung's F520 boasts an innovative dual slider design and full internet  browsing to ensure a truly connected and enriched mobile multimedia experience.  Last but by no means least, Samsung's F510 builds on the success of the  F500 but also supports DVB-H standard, showcasing Samsung's innovative dual  face design concept, with full handset functionality on one side that can be  rotated to reveal a full LCD screen for viewing purposes and to take crystal  clear photos with 2 megapixel camera on the back.
<br>        

  
        MOBILE WIMAX
<br>        Samsung will  showcase the latest in mobile convergence devices ready for Mobile WiMAX  technology at this year's 3GSM conference. This follows Samsung and  Sprint-Nextel's partnership last August to work together on the US  carrier's major 4G wireless initiative, which will adopt the Mobile WiMAX (IEEE  802.16e TDD OFDMA) technology standard. Samsung, and other Sprint-Nextel's 4G  vendors, will conduct live demonstrations of Mobile WiMAX, including  applications such as push-to-all technology. Samsung's new Mobile WiMAX  devices, the SPH-P9000 and the SPH-M8100, will be used at the demonstration,  allowing visitors to personally experience Mobile WiMAX technology. The P9000  is a true Mobile WiMAX convergence device, which enables wireless broadband  access and voice communications, while the M8100 is the first commercially  available Mobile WiMAX PDA device. The capabilities of this new mobile WiMAX  technology will be exclusively showcased through the use of a USB dongle in the  demonstration at 3GSM World Congress, meaning users can access Mobile WiMAX and  HSDPA services by connecting the USB dongle to a notebook.
<br>        
<br>        Learn more about Samsung's mobile technology and handsets at www.samsung3gsm2007.com and visit us  at Hall 8, Stand 8B127 at 3GSM World  Congress, Barcelona.
<br>        
<br>        About Samsung Electronics
<br>        Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in  semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence  technologies with 2006 parent company sales of US$63.4 billion and net income  of US$8.5 billion. Employing approximately 138,000 people in over 124 offices  in 56 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital  Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Network  Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest  growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital  TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. 
        
<br>        
<br>        For more information, please visit, 
     www.samsung.com
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Receives 12 CES Innovations Awards For 2007</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    LAS VEGAS - January 8, 2007 - Samsung Electronics, one of the world's fastest growing consumer electronics brand has won 12 International CES Innovations 2007 Design and Engineering Showcase Awards. 
<br>        
<br>        Samsung once again demonstrates its worldwide leadership in Consumer Electronics, Information Technology, and Telecommunications by winning coveted CES honors for innovation across a broad range of technologies.  Samsung's award-winners include three handheld cellular phones, two Plasma HDTVs, two digital audio players, two Home Theater-in-a-Box systems, a multifunction color laser printer, an ultra-Mobile PC, and a cutting edge washing machine. All of Samsung's Innovations Awards-winning products will be on display during the 2007 International CES, January 8-11, in the Samsung booth #11033 in the Central Hall of the Las Vegas Convention Center, as well as in the Innovations Pavilion.
<br>        
<br>        &quot;Samsung strives to consistently blaze a trail, to lead the Consumer Electronics industry in product design and engineering innovation. Therefore, we are extremely pleased and proud that 12 of our pillar products for 2007, in a variety of categories, have been recognized by the esteemed CEA judges,&quot; said Jong-Yong Yun, Vice Chairman and CEO of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd.  &quot;These prestigious awards reinforce Samsung's ongoing efforts to bring to market the most groundbreaking technologies and products that enrich the lives of our customers.&quot;
<br>      
Samsung's winning products for 2007 include: 

  
          
<br>          &quot;Honoree&quot; Awards:HP-T5054 50&quot; Plasma HDTV
          HP-T5064 50&quot; Plasma HDTV with Multi Media Center
<br>          
          Samsung K5 portable digital audio player
          Samsung K3 Portable digital audio player
          Zeus WF327XAB [washing machine]
          HT-X250 600-Watt Home Theater System
          HT-TXQ120 1000-Watt Home Theater System
          Q1P Ultra Mobile PC
          CLX-3160FN color multifunction printer
          Samsung SCH-i760 phone 
          Samsung SGH-a727 phone
          Phone to be announced on Monday, January 8th          
          
          As a widely renowned consumer technology awards, CES began in 1989.  The prestigious Innovations Design and Engineering Awards recognize achievements in product design and engineering. It is sponsored by CEA, the producer of the International CES, the world's largest consumer technology tradeshow, and endorsed by the Industrial Designers Society of America (IDSA), the voice of industrial design, committed to advancing the profession through education, information, community and advocacy.
<br>            
<br>          The CES Innovations Awards, now in its ninth year, salutes consumer technology products that exhibit superiority in design and engineering. Journalists, engineers, industrial designers and industry experts make the product evaluations as the awards are based on several criteria including value, aesthetics, innovation and contribution to quality of life. Sponsored by the Consumer Electronics Association (CEA) with the endorsement of the Industrial Designers Society of America (IDSA), these awards have become an industry standard in honoring the best technology of today.
<br>          
<br>          Innovations honoree products are featured on www.CESweb.org/Innovations, where you can see a list of product categories, as well as each product name, manufacturer information, designer, description, photo and URL.
<br>          
<br>          Samsung at ICES 2007
<br>        To see Samsung Electronics' complete ICES 2007 product lineup, please visit the company's booth (#11033) located in the Central Hall of the Las Vegas Convention Center. For more information on specific products, please visit Samsung Electronics' ICES press site at www.samsung.com/icespress.
      About Samsung Electronics
<br>      Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2005 parent company sales of US$56.7 billion and net income of US$7.5 billion. Employing approximately 128,000 people in over 120 offices in 57 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Appliance Business, Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business and Telecommunication Network Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG&#039;S 2007 CES Product Overview</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    -	46&quot; LCD TV: Samsung' s new LCD TV, LNT4661 has a new elegant design with high-gloss finish, chrome plating, hidden bar speakers and swivel stand. It also supports Full HD resolution (1080P) with advanced connectivity for a brilliant quality picture.
<br>      
<br>      -	&quot;50&quot; Plasma TV - The 50&quot; plasma applies the industry's leading innovative performance enhancements into a distinctive design. It boasts outstanding picture quality enhanced with Samsung's exclusive Filterbright technology.
<br>      
<br>      -	56&quot; Slim DLP TV with LED light source: LED delivers a bright clear picture and removes the need for a bulb which makes the set more energy and cost efficient. It sustains a premium picture with expressive color and depth, in a beautiful slim design DLP TV.
<br>      
<br>      -	226BW - Meeting the highest technical requirements for Windows Vista Premium Logo certification, the 22&quot; SyncMaster 226BW delivers stunning image quality and precision with 2ms video response and 3000:1 dynamic contrast ratio in a glossy piano-black design.  The Premium Logo, unlike basic certification, is reserved only for products proven to deliver a superior end-user experience when used with the Windows Vista operating system.
<br>      
<br>      -	BD-P1200 Blu-ray Player: The BD-P1200 builds on the success of the first generation Blu-ray player by introducing a new IP processor (HQV), adding Dolby Digital plus, and adding an ethernet connection. The HQV (Hollywood Quality Video) chipset delivers pixel based, motion adaptive processing that sets a new standard in video quality. The BD-P1200 also introduces Ethernet capability to take full advantage of future upgrades.
<br>      
<br>      -	HT-TXQ120 Home Theatre System: Samsung's premiere home theatre system, the HT-TXQ120 has an HDMI input and output with 1080p up conversion for incredible picture quality on high definition displays, a USB Host for versatility in connecting other USB compatible products, and 1000W output power for boosting an amazing home entertainment listening experience.
<br>      
<br>      -	YP-T9B MP3 Player: Take the ultra-slim, ultra portable YP-T9B MP3 player with you everywhere. Revel in its sound quality and advanced technological features like Bluetooth connectivity. The YP-T9B is packed with features. It's an MP3 player, an FM radio, a voice recorder and an MPEG4 video player. YP-T9B's capabilities mean you can enjoy a personal world of music every time, everywhere.
<br>      
<br>      -	Samsung CLX-3160FN Color Laser Multifunction Printer: The CLX-3160FN offers color printing and quiet operation and is ideal for users with demanding print, scan, fax, and copy needs that lack the space for bulky machinery. Due to its high-performance value coupled with its compact design, the CLX-3160FN was named a 2007 CES Innovation Honoree.
<br>      
<br>      -	UMPC Ultra Mobile PC: This product is the first of a totally new category and form factor of PC, a truly ultra-mobile unit weighing just 1.7 pounds. A companion PC, the Q1 allows users to have PC capabilities at their fingertips anytime, anywhere. The Q1 provides users with an innovative way to combine PC functionality, full multimedia support and wireless connectivity in an ultra-mobile platform.
<br>      
<br>      -	A-VSB Technology: A technology invented by Samsung to add portable and mobile TV capability to North American digital TV broadcasting. A proposed open standard that broadcasters can implement at a low cost, A-VSB will soon let consumers enjoy TV in their car, on their laptop and on handheld devices anywhere they go.
<br>      
<br>        Samsung at ICES 2007
<br>        To see Samsung Electronics' complete ICES 2007 product lineup, please visit the company's booth (#11033) located in the Central Hall of the Las Vegas Convention Center. For more information on specific products, please visit Samsung Electronics' ICES press site at www.samsung.com/icespress.
<br>        Executive sound bites are available at http://samsung.feedroom.com
<br>        
<br>        About Samsung Electronics
<br>      Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2005 parent company sales of US$56.7 billion and net income of US$7.5 billion. Employing approximately 128,000 people in over 120 offices in 57 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Appliance Business, Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business and Telecommunication Network Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Cements Leadership In Enabling Rich Digital Experiences With Dazzling Array Of Offerings At CES 2007</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    LAS VEGAS - January 7, 2007 - Samsung Electronics transforms the CES 2007 show into a kaleidoscope of rich digital experiences, unveiling an exciting range of products and demonstrations that span numerous product areas including displays, digital music, printers and mobile television. All of this can be seen at Samsung's booth at Central Hall 3, Booth #11033.
<br>      

Full details, high-resolution images and downloadable videos can be found at www.samsung.com/icespress. This year's announcements reinforce Samsung's continued global leadership and track record of innovation and design in markets such as displays, digital music players and home theater.
<br>      
<br>      &quot;Our commitment to high performing, beautifully designed products has ushered in a digital renaissance that has set the tone for the 21st century,&quot; said Jong Yong Yun, Vice Chairman &amp; CEO of Samsung Electronics. &quot;This year is no different as our news at CES focuses on our ongoing efforts to create richer digital experiences for our users both in and out of the living room.&quot;
<br>      

Among the highlights of Samsung's CES 2007 announcements:
<br>      
<br>      &quot;Full-HD&quot; LCD TVs continue flat-panel leadership
<br>        In 2006, Samsung became the No. 1 vendor worldwide in revenue for flat panel televisions. Building on that leadership, the company's latest premium LCD TVs (40-, 46- and 52-inches) boast even higher picture quality, new features and elegant product designs. All three models in the new lineup provide full high-definition (1,920 by 1,080 pixels) resolution, about twice as high as the standard high-definition specification (1,366 by 768 pixels, 1,080i), and support full-HD Blu-ray disc players.
<br>        
<br>        An increasing variety of multimedia products are now full-HD enabled, and the world's leading contents makers are producing more of their multimedia contents in the full-HD format.  Therefore, Samsung's new LCD TVs will help to accelerate TV viewers' transition to full-HD.
<br>        
<br>        A-VSB: First step toward mobile broadcast TV
<br>        One of the centerpiece demonstrations of CES 2007, Samsung will announce its innovative path into mobile television, one of the long sought-after arenas n the North American market. A-VSB is a technology proposed to ATSC (the Advanced Television Systems Committee which approves broadcast standards) that improves current TV signal reception performance and also allows the broadcast signal to be clearly received by both mobile and stationary television devices.
<br>        
<br>        Samsung is working closely with Rohde &amp; Schwartz and Sinclair Broadcasting Group to develop this standard, which provides broadcasters with an enormous opportunity with minimal investment since the standard works with existing broadcast equipment. The A-VSB TV signal of A-VSB can also be received by conventional LCD TVs without any problem.
<br>        

Samsung believes that this technology will have a significant influence on the portable and live mobile TV markets in the United States. In February 2009, all broadcasters will be required to cease analog broadcasts in favor of digital.  A-VSB is a potential solution to provide a sound transition for broadcasters with limited operational expenses. More than anything, however, A-VSB will help the North American market take the first critical steps to achieving the type of portable and mobile TV currently enjoyed in Korea.
<br>        
<br>        &quot;Experience Sharing&quot; drives MP3 evolution
<br>        Samsung has taken MP3 players beyond their traditional functionality to enable Experience Sharing. In 2006, Samsung introduced the K5 digital audio player, which featured a built-in speaker. In 2007, Samsung will launch the K3, which will feature a mobile speaker for dynamic music sharing.
<br>        

Breaking new ground in both form and functionality, the K5 is the first Samsung digital audio player to use OLED technology. The display and navigational array are smooth to the touch with sparkly ice blue adaptive graphics. The menu and navigation system is simple to use and add to the product's appeal. Another most requested travel function is an alarm clock which the K5 sports, allowing consumers to wake up to their favorite songs rather than a jolting alarm clock buzz.
<br>        

Samsung will also release its revolutionary digital device in the United States market: the T9B (Model Name: YP-T9B), an ultra slim, ultra portable MP3 player that amazingly packs in a complete portfolio of multimedia features and application.  The T9B MP3 player features a bluetooth wireless stereo that provides hands-free enjoyment within 10 meters and features advanced remote control functions on the headsets including play, pause, seek and volume.
<br>        
<br>        Next-generation Blu-ray
<br>        Building upon the successful launch of its BD-P1000 first-generation Blu-ray player in June 2006, Samsung will launch its BD-P1200 series of second-generation, new and improved Blu-ray players for the home entertainment industry in 2007.
<br>        

Staying ahead of the cutting-edge optical media industry, Samsung's BD-1200 Blu-Ray player will feature storage capacity that is 5X larger than DVDs. Blu-ray offers outstanding performance with the ability to play back high definition video and multi-channel sound. The BD-P1200 player enables customers to enjoy the best audio and video quality available today, and is equipped with the Hollywood Quality Video (HQV) processor, a powerful unit similar to ones used by Hollywood studios in production.
<br>        
<br>        With the HQV processor, the BD-P1200 player offers increased picture quality by refining image projection, even from non Blu-ray formats. HDMI boosts the quality of the sound (via 7.1-channel Dolby Digital Plus) and color.
<br>        
<br>        Award-winning CLX-3160 marks entry into global laser MFP market
<br>        The world's second-largest laser printer manufacturer introduce its first compact color laser multi-function printer (CLMFP) to the global market, the CLX-3160 Series, marking its entry into the market. As a reflection of its significance, the CLX-3160 series was named a 2007 CES Innovations Award Honoree in the Mobile/Home Office Category.
<br>        

As Samsung's first CLMFP, the compactness and versatility of the CLX-3160 series make it the ideal choice for SMB and small workgroups' printing needs. The series offers two different models: The 3-in-1 CLX-3160N (Print-copy-scan) and the 4-in-1 CLX-3160FN (Print-copy-scan-fax). It prints four pages per minute color and 17 pages black and white in Letter size, fast enough for day-to-day document printing with occasional color printing.
<br>        

In addition, Samsung's patented NO-NOISTM technology allows a 30% reduction in size and a 33% reduction in weight over its competitors. The CLX-3160FN model operates at a lower noise level than a standard multi-pass machine and offers outstanding convenience of maintenance, through easier toner changing, and less troublesome paper handling.
<br>        
<br>        Home Theater experience is transformed
<br>        The launch of Samsung's HT-X250 and HT-TXQ120 home entertainment systems matches impressive performance with equally appealing aesthetics, such as a variety of features like versatile multimedia playback and instant entertainment with USB Host Play function. The HT-TXQ120 and the HT-X250 systems transform any living room into the ultimate home theater.
<br>        

The HT-X250 and the HT-TXQ120 home entertainment systems offer not only superb sound and industry-leading features, but a new gorgeous design that perfectly complements Samsung's eye-catching flat-panel televisions. These latest home entertainment systems incorporate an integrated DVD player/receiver to create a fully integrated digital multimedia entertainment center.
<br>        

USB Host Play function, an exclusive Samsung feature, enables various multimedia files to be played without the need for a PC, including DivX, MP3, DVD Audio, WMA, CD-R/RW and DVD-R/RW and jpegs. This ability saves time for the customer, and provides them with a supreme entertainment experience.
<br>        
<br>        Monitors provide a new &quot;Vista&quot;
<br>        The Samsung 19-inch SynchMaster 931BW, 20-inch SynchMaster 206BW and 22-inch SynchMaster 226BW wide-screen monitors displayed at CES 2007 are now certified as &quot;Windows Vista Premium.&quot; Microsoft will release its new Windows Vista software upgrade in early 2007, and the &quot;Windows Vista Premium logo&quot; mark means that the monitors fully support the features of the Window Vista™  operation system.
<br>        
<br>        Samsung and Microsoft worked closely together, and Microsoft's Windows Vista Industrial Design Toolkit was applied from the initial design stage. Today, Samsung and Microsoft enjoy an excellent relationship that can lead to a lasting global partnership. The companies are currently planning joint marketing programs for various events worldwide.
<br>        
<br>        All three of the new SynchMaster monitor models come in high-gloss, piano-black casings for added elegance. The Digital Visual Interface (DVI) terminal provides High-bandwidth Digital Content Protection (HDCP) for real-time TV or DVD viewing. Thus, the monitors can be connected to various other audiovisual products.
<br>        
<br>        LED DLP TV - Better quality longer
<br>        The new Samsung HL-T5087S, HL-T5687S and HL-T6187S DLP TVs are as slim as a flat panel model but with improved picture quality. The new TVs are equipped with an LED backlight and provide a resolution of 1,920 by 1,080 pixels (1080p)-twice the picture quality of a standard high definition TV (1,280 by 720 pixels, 720p).
<br>        

The ultra-wide color gamut (NTSC 140 percent) is also 140 percent better than conventional models, providing a richer, more diverse range of tones. A contrast ratio of 10,000:1 results in remarkable images. The lifecycle of an LED backlight is approximately 4 times longer than that of lamps, eliminating the need to replace the lamps. The image quality will not deteriorate over time and the product contains no mercury, reducing its impact on the environment.
<br>        

For more powerful connectivity, Samsung's new LED DLP TVs has WISELINK™ which offers music (MP3) and photo (JPEG) playing via USB connection and has 3 HDMI which simultaneously connect three devices with full HD signal transmission.
<br>        
<br>        Ultra Mobile PC Q1P SSD: &quot;Solid&quot; Innovation Continues
<br>        After introducing a new category and form factor for PCs in 2006 with the release of the Q1 UMPC (Ultra Mobile PC), Samsung extends its leadership in the global computer market at CES 2007 with the announcement of the Q1P SSD Ultra Mobile PC. The revolutionary device is the first UMPC of its kind to use an SSD solid state flash memory-based hard drive in place of a conventional rotational media-based hard drive.
<br>        
<br>        The Q1P SSD is the most powerful UMPC model available today.  Fueled by an impressive 32GB of SSD (solid-state NAND) flash memory, as opposed to the traditional 1.8&quot; Hard Drive found in the earlier Q1 models, the Q1P SSD model is ideal for those applications that require a no-compromise, high-performance mobile computing solution that can operate in diverse conditions.
<br>        

The Q1P SSD UMPC is designed for optimum performance.  With the SSD-enabled model, boot time is 25-50 percent faster than systems that employ a traditional hard drive.  Overall system performance is significantly enhanced, as the SSD is capable of reading 300 times faster (53 MB/s) and writes 150 percent faster (28 MB/s) than models with typical hard drives.  With its departure from the traditional hard drive, the Q1P SSD UMPC is equipped to withstand twice the impact of the hard-drive-enabled model and its battery life is also improved, as it requires less power to run the flash-based SSD hard drive.
<br>        
<br>        The Q1P SSD UMPC will be on display along with its predecessors, the Q1 and the Q1P, a 2007 CES Innovation Honoree.
<br>        
<br>        Samsung at ICES 2007
<br>        To see Samsung Electronics' complete ICES 2007 product lineup, please visit the company's booth (#11033) located in the Central Hall of the Las Vegas Convention Center. For more information on specific products, please visit Samsung Electronics' ICES press site at www.samsung.com/icespress.
<br>        Executive sound bites are available at http://samsung.feedroom.com.
      
      About Samsung Electronics
<br>      Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2005 parent company sales of US$56.7 billion and net income of US$7.5 billion. Employing approximately 128,000 people in over 120 offices in 57 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Appliance Business, Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business and Telecommunication Network Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Receives 12 CES Innovations Awards For 2007</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    Ridgefield Park, NJ - Samsung Electronics, one of the world's fastest growing consumer electronics brand has won 12 International CES Innovations 2007 Design and Engineering Showcase Awards.  
 
Samsung once again evinces why the company is a worldwide leader in Consumer Electronics, Information Technology, and Telecommunications, winning coveted CES honors for innovation across a broad range of technologies.  Samsung's award-winners include three handheld cellular phones, two Plasma HDTVs, two digital audio players, two Home Theater in a Box systems, a multifunction color laser printer, an ultra-Mobile PC, and a cutting edge washing machine. All of Samsung's Innovations Awards-winning products will be on display during the 2007 International CES, January 8-11, in the Samsung booth 11033 in the Central Hall of the Las Vegas Convention Center, as well as in the Innovations Pavilion.
 
"Samsung strives to consistently blaze a trail, to lead the Consumer Electronics industry in product design and engineering innovation. Therefore, we are extremely pleased and proud that 12 of our pillar products for 2007, in a variety of categories, have been recognized by the esteemed CEA judges," states 
DJ Oh, President, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. "These prestigious awards reinforce Samsung's ongoing efforts to bring to market the most groundbreaking technologies and products that enrich the lives of our customers."

Samsung's winning products for 2007 include: 

"Honoree" Awards:
        HP-T5054 50" Plasma HDTV
        HP-T5064 50" Plasma HDTV with Multi Media Center
       Samsung K5 portable digital audio player
       Samsung K3 Portable digital audio player
      Zeus WF327XAB [washing machine]
        HT-X250 600-Watt Home Theater System
        HT-TXQ120 1000-Watt Home Theater System
        Q1P [ultra-Mobile PC]
        CLX-3160 color multifunction printer
    +Three Innovative Cellular Phones from Samsung to be unveiled 
@ CES 2007

As a widely renowned consumer technology awards, CES began in 1989.  The prestigious Innovations Design and Engineering Awards recognize achievements in product design and engineering. It is sponsored by CEA, the producer of the International CES, the world's largest consumer technology tradeshow, and endorsed by the Industrial Designers Society of America (IDSA), the voice of industrial design, committed to advancing the profession through education, information, community and advocacy.

The CES Innovations Awards, now in its ninth year, salutes consumer technology products that exhibit superiority in design and engineering. Journalists, engineers, industrial designers and industry experts make the product evaluations as the awards are based on several criteria including value, aesthetics, innovation and contribution to quality of life. Sponsored by the Consumer Electronics Association (CEA) with the endorsement of the Industrial Designers Society of America (IDSA), these awards have become an industry standard in honoring the best technology of today.
Innovations honoree products are featured on  www.CESweb.org/Innovations, where you can see a list of product categories, as well as each product name, manufacturer information, designer, description, photo and URL.


About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. 
<br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, advanced digital consumer electronics, information systems and home appliance products. The SEA organization oversees the North American operations of Samsung including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. Please visit www.samsung.com  for more information.

About Samsung Electronics
<br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2005 parent company sales of US$56.7 billion and net income of US$7.5 billion. Employing approximately 128,000 people in over 90 offices in 51 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Appliance Business, Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business and Telecommunication Network Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Brings Sporting Edge to IT and Technology At GITEX for the 15th Asian Games Doha 2006</title>
            <description>			

                <![CDATA[
                    Dubai, 20th November, 2006  - With the opening ceremony of the 15th Asian Games Doha 2006 less than 2 weeks away, Samsung Electronics further initiated its commitment as a Prestige Partner of the Games by announcing an exciting mixture of partnership related activities at GITEX in Dubai - one of the top 3 IT exhibitions in the world.
<br>        
<br>        &quot;As one of the biggest annual IT and telecoms exhibitions, with over 3,000 exhibitors from more than 60 countries worldwide, GITEX seems an appropriate venue to bring attention to our activities for the 15th Asian Games,&quot; said Mr. Gyehyun Kwon, Vice President and Head of Worldwide Sport Marketing and Global Communications of Samsung Electronics. &quot;We have a long history of supporting sporting events and are proud to be associated with the 15th Asian Games Doha 2006,&quot; continued Kwon.
<br>        

As part of the 15th Asian Games booth at GITEX, Samsung will be highlighting its strong commitment to promoting sports all across the globe while delving into the exciting activities it has planned for Doha 2006, the first event of its kind in the region. This will be done by a unique photo exhibition which will display inspirational moments in the history of world sports. Samsung will also provide an exclusive range of postcards containing a combination of photos from the exhibition as well as photo opportunities with Orry, the official mascot for the 15th Asian Games.
<br>        

As a Prestige Partner of the 15th Asian Games, Samsung's partnership includes exclusivity in the audio/visual, white goods and mobile phone categories. Since 1986, Samsung has been a sponsor of the Asian Games. This year, Samsung takes on the role of exclusive multi-category Prestige Partner with an assorted combination of activities and VIK offerings in the audio/ visual equipment, household appliances and mobile phone categories for use at both the Games' competition and non-competition venues throughout Doha. The products will total 8,189, consisting of 3,549 A/V (TV, Video Camera and DVD/VCR Combo), 2,772 mobile phones, and 1,868 household appliances (Fridge, Washer and Microwave).
<br>        

Samsung will also provide other interactive sponsor activities during the 15th Asian Games which will include:
<br>        

The Samsung Lounge will act as a media centre and the base of information sharing and interview coordination. It will consist of a catering area, product showcase, free internet station and free dial access from Samsung's latest mobile phones.
<br>        

The Samsung Digital Gallery will comprise a unique display of some of the most technologically sophisticated products in the world with zones dedicated to various categories within Samsung's expertise, such as digital media, lifestyle and mobile, among others.
<br>        
<br>        Samsung will once again have the honor of selecting the Asian Games' Most Valuable Player (MVP) by awarding the most deserving athlete with the Samsung MVP Award, continuing the tradition it started in Bangkok in 1998 of honoring athletes who strive for excellence, competition and unity. The MVP award ceremony will form part of the Closing ceremony, and will be presented to one MVP and four finalists who will be selected by a distinguished committee and an accredited media poll.
<br>        
<br>        About Samsung and Sports Sponsorship
<br>        For almost 20 years, Samsung has been a dedicated supporter of major sporting events across Asia and the world. Samsung is a long-time supporter of the Asian Games, beginning as a local sponsor of the Seoul 1986 Asian Games and continuing as a local sponsor for the Hiroshima 1994 Asian Games.  Samsung's full commitment to the Asian Games started from 1998 participating as an official partner of the Bangkok Asian Games and as a multi-category sponsor in the Busan Asian Games in 2002.
<br>        

Samsung highlights sports sponsorship as a platform to raise brand awareness and build a reputation for excellence in corporate citizenship. Samsung's extensive support of sports, including the Asian Games, is based on its corporate values that celebrate peace, encourage friendly competition and promote unity among people of all cultures.
<br>        
<br>        About Samsung Electronics
<br>      Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2005 parent company sales of US$56.7 billion and net income of US$7.5 billion. Employing approximately 128,000 people in over 120 offices in 57 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Appliance Business, Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business and Telecommunication Network Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com
<br>
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>
    
        <item>
            <title>SAMSUNG Electronics Exhibits an Array of High-tech Products at KES 2006</title>
            <description>			
                <![CDATA[
                    Seoul , Korea  - October 17, 2006 - Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., a market leader in consumer electronics and IT equipment, is bolstering its brand image by showcasing state-of-the- products and technologies at Korea Electronics Show 2006. This year marks the 37 th running of, Korea 's largest electronics industry event, which is being held at the Korea International Exhibition Center (KINTEX) in Ilsan October 17-21. 
    The 1,155m 2 Samsung booth, the show's most spacious, is where you can see the latest offerings items from the Samsung Digital Appliance, Digital Media, Semiconductor and Telecommunication Network Business Divisions. 
    Sophisticated mobile phones on display include the Ultra Edition series sold Korean market and led by the Ultra Edition 6.9 (SPH-V9900), which at 6.9mm is the thinnest handset developed to date. Filling out the lineup are the slim clamshell Ultra Edition 9.9 (SCH-V900) and multimedia powerhouse Ultra Edition 12.9 (SCH-B630) with a 3M-pixel camera.&nbsp;At the same time, Samsung is exhibiting such cutting-edge innovations as a LCD TV (LN52M71BD) with full-high-definition resolution, the world's first commercial Blu-ray disc player (BD-P1000), home-use color laser printers, the world's smallest and lightest color laser printer (CLP-300). 
    Appliances seen at the booth include the 4-door Zipel Quatro refrigerator (SRM688SAWT) is independent freezer and refrigerator units. Last but not least is the nano-silver drum washing machine (SEW-HK149ATA) that can sanitize laundry and suppress the growth of bacteria. 
    Jong-Yong Yun, Vice Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of Samsung Electronics , said, "We are taking part in the KES to introduce products that demonstrate our latest technologies and most elegant designs. In the process, our position as the digital convergence leader is becoming ever stronger. We will continue to find new ways to help shape and enhance consumers' lifestyles by providing the products and technologies that they want." and "Samsung will focus on the show as Korea Electronics Show is gobally becoming influencial based on developing Korean IT techonology." added. 
    At KES this year, visitors will be able to see and experience an extensive portfolio of Information Technology, Telecommunications and Digital Appliance. Highlights include: 
     Mozel LCD TV (LN52M71BD) - The Mozel LCD TV, with powerful LED backlight, received EISA's prestigious "Video Innovation Award." This TV has high-definition picture quality and an industry-leading contrast ratio of 10,000:1. 
<br>      
<br>       LCD Monitor (SyncMaster 971P) - The SyncMaster 971P lets users focus better on the screen images by covering half of the unique "S" shaped stand, giving the impression that the monitor is floating in the air. 
<br>      
<br>       BD Player (BD-P1000) - The world's first commercial Blu-ray disc player allows consumers to take full advantage of high-definition displays, playing content at native 720p, 1080i and even 1080p video resolutions.&middot; 
<br>      
<br>       &nbsp;MP3P (YP-T9) &nbsp;- The T9 is an ultra-slim, ultra-portable MP3 player with Bluetooth support for using wireless headphones. Numerous other features include the FM radio, voice recording, MP3/WMA/OGG support, photo and text viewing, and two full-color 3D games onboard. 
<br>      
<br>       Color Laser Printer (CLP-300) - The CLP-300 is the world's smallest and lightest color laser printer. The CLP-300 series are the perfect color printing solution for home and small office users. 
<br>      
<br>       Ultra Mobile PC ( Q1) - &nbsp;The world's first "ultra-mobile PC" weighs in at just 777g while providing all the functions available found of today's digital devices. Full PC functionally guarantees mobility everywhere at any time. 
<br>      
<br>       Zipel Quatro Refrigerator (SRM688SAWT) - This refrigerator features four separate compartments with adjustable temperature settings. It keeps the odors, temperature, and humidity in one compartment from affecting foods in the others and enhances storage flexibility. 
<br>      
<br>       Nano-silver Drum Washing Machine (SEW-HK149ATA) - Samsung's drum washing machine uses the disinfectant and antibiotic properties of nano-silver to eliminate 99.99% of the bacteria in the laundry load. It also coats the clothes with antibacterial protection that lasts for up to a month. 
<br>      
<br>       32Gb NAND Flash Memory - This is the world's first NAND flash memory to incorporate the charge trap flash (CTF) architecture. It utilizes a record 40-nanometer design technology and provides 32-Gb data storage density.&nbsp;
<br>      
<br>       Ultra Edition 6.9 SPH-V9900&nbsp;- This mobile handset comes loaded with a 2M-pixel camera, MP3 player, and numerous multimedia features in the world's thinnest profile of 6.9mm. With a variety of colors to choose from, the V9900 is guaranteed to impress with its distinct design and functions. 
<br>      
<br>       Ultra Edition 9.9 SCH-V900&nbsp;- Ultra Edition 9.9 is a brand new clamshell that is only 9.9 mm thick. It truly redefines the meaning of "slim clamshell," with all-in-one multimedia features such as a 2M-pixel camera, Bluetooth &reg; support, and music player. 
<br>      
<br>       Ultra Edition 12.9 SCH-B630&nbsp;- The SCH-B630 has an ultra-slim (12.9mm) design with a picture-perfect 3M-pixel camera, music player, and all of today's business features. The powerful B630 is also equipped with S-DMB capability, Bluetooth &reg; support, and an external memory slot, breaking new ground in mobile phone functionality and fun. 
<br>      
<br>       World's First 10 Megapixel Cameraphone SCH-B600&nbsp;- The SCH-B600 captures consumers hearts with a 10 megapixel camera function. Additional features such as Satellite-DMB, music player, and other multimedia functions truly makes this an unique World's First 10 megapixel cameraphone. 
<br>      
<br>       World's First 8GB HDD Phone SCH-B570&nbsp;- With an astounding built-in 8GB Hard Drisk Drive , the B570 is the perfect companion for music lovers. The World's first 8GB HDD mobile phone is also equipped with Satellite-DMB function, 5.1 channel stereo sound, and GPS feature. 
<br>      
<br>       Slim QWERTY Smartphone SGH-i320N&nbsp;- Featuring a full QWERTY keypad, the slim i320N is a slim Windows Mobile 5.0 Smartphone with a 11.5mm depth. Bluetooth&reg; support, 1.3 Megapixel camera, file viewer, and Music player makes the i320N the perfect mobile for work and play. 
<br>      
<br>      Please visit Samsung Electronics at stands Hall 5. 
    


  About Samsung Electronics

  
     Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2005 parent company sales of US$56.7 billion and net income of US$7.5 billion. Employing approximately 128,000 people in over 120 offices in 5 7 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Appliance Business, Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business and Telecommunication Network Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones, and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com
                ]]>					
            </description>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>


