<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>

		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Introduces New Slim Touch Of Color LCD Monitors</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., May 07, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America</b>, a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, the number one worldwide brand of LCD display products, today announced the release of its 70 Series Monitors: the <b>P2070, P2370 and  P2370HD</b>.  These slim LCD monitors, with screen depths of 30 mm (1.18 inches) for the P2070 and P2370 and 65.5mm (2.58 inches) for the P2370HD and Touch of Color (ToC™) design, are the latest release of Samsung's high performance displays.<br><br>"The 70 Series offers our customers a sophisticated-looking LCD monitor with the performance capability of our televisions," said <b>J.H. Kim, President of Samsung Electronics America's Information Technology Division</b>.  "The 70 Series is the new standard as more people upgrade their monitors for additional uses, like watching television programs and playing video games."<br><br>The 70 Series Monitors are ideal for office applications and entertainment with its dynamic contrast ratio (50,000:1) for deep, rich colors, while the 2ms (GTG) video response time minimizes blurring for watching sports and fast-moving gameplay.  The crystal-like bezel frame with ToC™ reduces the reflection of light and glare.  The glossy stand offers a polished design, while the clear, crystal-like acrylic neck gives the illusion the monitor is floating. <br><br>Samsung's Startlight Touch Controls integrate the On Screen Display (OSD) buttons into the bezel for a seamless look and feel, eliminating obtrusive buttons on the front or sides on the panel.  Gently touching any of the buttons illuminates the controls which automatically disappear after a set period of time, minimizing distractions.  <br><br>The P2370 offers full HD 1080p resolution (1920x1080) for optimized viewing of HD content.  For full HDTV capability, the P2370HD builds on the 1080p capabilities of the P2370 with the addition of a HDTV tuner, integrated speakers with SRS TruSurround HD(r) and remote control.  In addition, the P2370HD also has HDMI and component inputs for additional connections such as Blu-Ray, set-top boxes and game consoles providing users with a display that is ready for work and play.<br><br>"The 70 Series is a great monitor for someone looking a full range of color, sharpness and response.  It also has an added benefit for those concerned about the environment.  We were sensitive to the impact computers monitors have on the environment and have developed a manufacturing process for the 70 Series that would minimize this," said <b>Tony Yu, Display Product Manager of Samsung Electronics America's Information Technology Division</b>.  <br><br>The 70 Series offers a suite of eco-conscious features including reduced energy consumption, requiring about a third less power to operate compared to typical monitors of similar size.  The ToC manufacturing process eliminates harmful paints and sprays, increasing the monitors' recyclability.  The slim footprint also dramatically reduces transportation costs and requirements for a smaller carbon footprint.<br><br>P2070 \ P2370 \ P2370HD LCD Monitors<br>-	Thin 30mm screen depth (65.5mm  - P2370HD)<br>-	High contrast ratio of 50,000:1<br>-	Full HD 1080p (1920x1080) resolution (1600x900 - P2070)<br>-	Fast 2ms (GTG) video response time (5ms - P2370HD)<br>-	Reduced power consumption<br>-	Touch of Color (ToC™) technology <br>-	VOC-free Crystal-like bezel frame to help reduce glare <br>-	Starlight Touch Controls<br>-	Built-in 1080p digital HDTV tuner;  5ms (GTG) video response time and HDMI input (P2370HD)<br><br>All monitors are available through Samsung resellers and distribution channels, which can be located by calling 1-800-SAMSUNG or by visiting www.samsung.com.  Samsung Power Partners receive special promotions, lead referrals, training and technical support, as well as collateral and marketing materials. To find out more about becoming a Samsung Power Partner, visit <a href="http://www.samsungpartner.com" target="_blank">www.samsungpartner.com</a>. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) is one of the fastest growing IT companies in the U.S., and is committed to serving the IT needs of consumers ranging from the home user to the Fortune 500 elite, and supports the valued channel partners who serve our customers.  Offering innovative solutions and award-winning designs, Samsung ITD presents a complete line of award-winning color and mono-laser printing solutions, desktop monitors, notebook computers, digital signage solutions and projectors.  Based in Ridgefield Park, N.J., ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com or call 1-800-SAMSUNG</b>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Announces New Mini Notebooks</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., April 23, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America</b>, a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, a global leader in digital media and digital convergence technologies, today announced the <b>N110 and N120</b> as the newest additions to their mini notebook lineup.  The N110 and N120 are both currently available through Samsung.com and online retailers with an MSRP of $469 and $459, respectively. <br><br>"Our mini notebooks represent Samsung's desire to offer high quality, mobile focused solutions that create user value with important features such as design, ergonomics and battery life," said <b>J.H. Kim, President of Samsung Electronics America's Information Technology Division</b>.  "With the addition of the N110 and N120, we have expanded our lineup with enhanced battery life, multi-media speakers and a larger keyboard and touchpad.  These key features will satisfy the needs of users looking for audio video capabilities, while also supporting the road warriors needing extended battery life."<br><br>The N110 mini notebook's compact design, 10.27'' (W) x 1.19'' (H) x 7.3'' (D), is lightweight, only 2.78 lbs, and capable of being stowed in a briefcase or travel bag.  Despite its size, the N110's keyboard has an ergonomic-friendly 93% full-size keyboard and a 10" LED SuperBright© Glossy Backlit Display, along with a 6-cell (5900mAh) lithium battery providing battery life up to 9 hours of continuous use.  With a 1.6GHz processor, 1GB of RAM and 160GB hard drive, this mini notebook is functional for browsing the internet and software applications. <br><br>The N120 mini notebook caters to those looking for a richer multimedia experience.  While also compact, 10.71'' (W) x 1.71"' (H) x 7.4"' (D), and weighing only 2.8 lbs, the N120 features the convenience of a 97% full-size keyboard with trackpad, along with a 6-cell (5200mAh) lithium battery providing battery life up to 6 hours of continuous use.  Its SRS 2.1 channel system, featuring two 1.5 watt stereo speakers and a dedicated subwoofer offers a high quality sound and integrated 1.3 megapixel digital motion camera provides video-conferencing capabilities.<br><br><b>N110 Notebook</b><br>-	Dimensions:  10.27'' (W) x 1.19'' (H) x 7.3'' (D)<br>-	Intel® Atom™ Processor N270 (1.60GHz, 533MHz, 512KB) <br>-	Genuine Windows XP Home (SP3) operating system<br>-	1GB (DDR2 / 1GB x 1) of memory<br>-	10.1" WSVGA (1024 x 600) SuperBright© Glossy  Backlit Display<br>-	160GB (5400 rpm SATA) HDD<br>-	802.11b/g, Bluetooth 2.0 + Enhanced Data Rate<br>-	10/100 RJ45 Ethernet<br>-	3-in-1 Card Reader (SD, SDHC, MMC), <br>-	Three (3) USB 2.0 ports<br>-	Headphone-out,/Mic in; Integrated Mic<br>-	VGA Out (15-pin, D-sub)<br>-	1.3 Megapixel Web Camera<br>-	Six-cell (5900mAh) Lithium ion battery for up to 9 hours of use <br>-	3 W Stereo Speaker (1.5 Watt x 2 )<br>-	One-Year International Collect and Return Warranty<br><br><b>N120 Notebook</b><br>Includes almost all features of the N110 except for the following:<br>-	Dimensions:  10.71'' (W) x 1.71'' (H) x 7.4'' (D),<br>-	3 W Stereo Speaker (1.5 Watt x 2 ) with Subwoofer<br>-	Six-cell (5200mAh) Lithium ion battery for up to 6 hours of use<br>-	97% Full-size keyboard <br>All mini notebooks are available through Samsung resellers and distribution channels, which can be located by calling 1-800-SAMSUNG or by visiting www.samsung.com.  Samsung Power Partners receive special promotions, lead referrals, training and technical support, as well as collateral and marketing materials. To find out more about becoming a Samsung Power Partner, visit <a href="http://www.samsungpartner.com" target="_blank"> www.samsungpartner.com</a>. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) is one of the fastest growing IT companies in the U.S., and is committed to serving the IT needs of consumers ranging from the home user to the Fortune 500 elite, and supports the valued channel partners who serve our customers.  Offering innovative solutions and award-winning designs, Samsung ITD presents a complete line of award-winning color and mono-laser printing solutions, desktop monitors, notebook computers, digital signage solutions and projectors.  Based in Ridgefield Park, N.J., ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com or call 1-800-SAMSUNG</b>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Debuts New Kitchen Appliances That Save Consumers Time And Energy</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J. - April 22, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America Inc</b>., a market leader and award-winning innovator in consumer electronics and home appliances, today unveiled new electric ranges as part of its expanding kitchen line. The<b> FTQ387</b> electric range features one of the industry's quickest boil elements, designed to help consumers save time. Additional products announced include feature-rich over-the-range microwave ovens and an energy-efficient dishwasher.<br><br>"This year we are introducing a number of innovative products to our expanding kitchen line that exemplify what Samsung appliances stand for: helping our consumers in their everyday lives, offer best-in-class value and address common issues," said<b> James Politeski, vice president of Home Appliance sales and marketing at Samsung Electronics America</b>. "From our highly rated over-the-range microwave ovens, to our energy-efficient dishwashers, our products go beyond their given tasks and offer solutions to the consumer. Our new ranges even save consumers time by offering a fast boil time and 20-minute steam clean cycle. "<br><br><b>FTQ387 and FTQ353 Electric Ranges</b><br>Samsung's new electric ranges, the FTQ387 and FTQ353, offer a large 5.9 cu. ft of oven space, giving consumers the power to cook large meals with greater ease. The ranges feature a ceramic glass cooking surface with five fast-heating burners. The Samsung SteamQuick ™ cycle uses the power of steam to save time, energy and money by cleaning the oven in just 20<br>minutes. Simply press the button, wait 20 minutes and wipe down the oven. No harsh cleaners or long cycles needed.<br><br>For incredible performance and cooking convenience, the FTQ387 also includes a fast boil element, which can boil a pot of water nearly six minutes faster than traditional 6"/9" burners, so consumers can spend less time waiting. For even baking and roasting performance, both FTQ387 and FTQ353 combine an 8-pass hidden bake element, a 6-pass broil element, a 3-fan convection system and tight temperature control. Additionally, the FTQ387 features True (or European) three-fan convection cooking, glass touch controls and a vibrant two color display.<br><br>The FTQ387 and FTQ353 both feature a 600W warming drawer with three temperature settings to simplify cooking larger meals, and contoured metal knobs with position indicators. The FTQ387 electric range with fast boil element is available now in stainless for $1299, while the FTQ353 electric range is available now in stainless for $999.99 and white and black for $899.99.<br><br><b>SMH9207, SMH9187 and SMH9151 Over-the-Range Microwaves</b><br>To compliment the new line of ranges, Samsung also introduced three new over-the-range microwave ovens. The stainless SMH9207 features 2.0 cu. ft of interior space, 1150 watts of power, sensor cooking, a 400 CFM ventilation fan and controls on the bottom of the door. The SMH9187 features 1.8 cu. ft of space, sensor cooking, a 400 CFM ventilation fan and 1100 watts of power, while the SMH9151 offers 1.5 cu. ft of space, a 220 CFM ventilation fan and 1000 watts of power.<br><br>All three over-the-range microwave ovens are designed to match seamlessly with the full line of Samsung home appliances, in a stylish and attractive design. The powerful ventilation system quickly and quietly removes any food odor, while the vents remain hidden to provide a finished, sleek look. Handy features such as removable chrome racks allow for multiple level or two-tier cooking for added cooking convenience.<br><br>The SMH9207 will be available in stainless in June 2009 for $399.99. The SMH9187 is available now in stainless for $299.99 and black and white for $279.99. The SMH9151 is available now in stainless for $199.99, black and white at for $179.99.<br><br><b>DMR78 Dishwasher</b><br>The new energy-efficient DMR78 dishwasher is a stylish model featuring an easy-to-use stainless handle that mirrors the same design as Samsung's ranges and refrigerators, as well as integrated touch sensor controls for a sleek look. The DMR78 is one of the quietest dishwashers in its class thanks to the six-layer door insulation and advanced motor insulation systems. It also features a concealed base for the motor, which significantly cuts back on the noise.<br><br>The DMR78 is also Energy Star® qualified and uses only 289 kWh/year. Added features of the DMR78 include a hard food disposer to eliminate the need to prewash dishes, hidden heating element, six wash cycles, auto clean sensor and three spray wash arms.<br><br>The DMR78 dishwasher is available now in stainless steel for $899.<br><br>Samsung Electronics America's press releases, video content and product images are available at <a href="http://www.samsung.com/newsroom" target="_blank"> </a>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc.</b><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, digital consumer electronics and home appliance products, including HDTVs, home theater systems, MP3 players, digital imaging products, refrigerators and washing machines. A recognized innovation leader in consumer electronics design and technology, Samsung is the HDTV market leader in the U.S. Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> for more information.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Launches The Most Energy Efficient Full Size Front Load Washer</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J. - April 22, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America Inc</b>., a market leader and award-winning innovator in consumer electronics and home appliances, today unveiled the new WF419 high efficiency front load Vibration Reduction Technology (VRTTM) steam washer. As the most efficient front load full size washer in its class, the ENERGY STAR qualified WF419 provides advanced energy savings, water conservation and the option to wash and sanitize clothes in cold water for even more efficient operation.<br><br>"We are proud to introduce our most energy efficient washer to date, setting the industry standard in wash performance," said<b> James Politeski, vice president of Home Appliance sales and marketing at Samsung Electronics America</b>. "At Samsung, we are committed to delivering appliances that consumers are proud to buy, while also enhancing their lives by saving time, money and energy. Our new washer provides consumers with the quality and features they are looking for, such as our acclaimed VRT™, which allows installation of washers in more convenient areas in the home, including the second floor."<br><br><b>WF419 Front Load Washer</b><br>The new Samsung WF419 front load washer goes beyond the ENERGY STAR qualifications and provides increased energy and water savings. Operating at 109 kWh/year, the low power consumption coupled with the large capacity of 4.3 cu. ft., makes the WF419 truly energy-efficient. It rates 127 percent better than federal energy standards, providing savings and<br>reducing the total number of loads that consumers have to run. In addition, the WF419 provides increased water conservation. Consumers will save money by using up to 70 percent less water than comparable top-loading washing machines.<br><br>Not only is the Samsung WF419 gentle on the environment, but it is also gentle on clothes. The WF419 offers advanced features for easier washing. For example, it delivers powerful cleaning results by injecting steam to help loosen dirt. The WF419 also features an ActivFresh cycle that cleans and freshens clothes in cold water without the use of bleach and hot water, providing energy savings of up to 92 percent compared to traditional hot water sanitation. It has the added benefit of keeping the interior drum clean. Finally, it offers consumers 12 preset wash cycles and seven options for their every laundry need.<br><br>Much like the current industry-leading and award-winning WF448, the WF419 is designed to be liberated from the basement to more convenient living spaces. For example, the WF419 features Samsung's acclaimed VRT feature, which reduces noise and vibrations commonly associated with front load washers by using ball bearings to counter occasional load imbalances. VRT provides the quietest maximum spin speeds in its class with an unbalanced load. The WF419 is especially quiet by using the direct drive motor, which eliminates noises commonly experienced on belt drive motors, even at the maximum spin speed of 1200 RPMs. These innovative features, coupled with the WF419's stylish chrome trim design, make this washer ideal for laundry rooms on second floors or those close to living areas.<br><br>The WF419 is available in May for $1,199. A matching dryer is offered in gas and electric, as well as optional pedestals and stacking kits.<br><br>Samsung Electronics America's press releases, video content and product images are available at <a href="http://www.samsung.com/newsroom" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/newsroom</a>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc.</b><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, digital consumer electronics and home appliance products, including HDTVs, home theater systems, MP3 players, digital imaging products, refrigerators and washing machines. A recognized innovation leader in consumer electronics design and technology, Samsung is the HDTV market leader in the U.S. Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> for more information.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Extends Refrigerator Line To Include Industry-First Dual Ice Maker</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J. - April 22, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America Inc.</b>, a market leader and award-winning innovator in consumer electronics and home appliances, today announced new additions to its growing refrigerator line, including the industry's first dual ice maker refrigerator that allows consumers to enjoy more than one and a half times the ice production of their current models. Additional new offerings for Spring 2009 include new counter-depth models.<br><br>"Samsung is dedicated to creating solutions that enable efficiency in the home, and we've designed our new refrigerators to directly address this need of our consumers," said<b> James Politeski, vice president of Home Appliance sales and marketing at Samsung Electronics America</b>. "Our new refrigerators are extremely energy efficient, feature best-in-class design and include advanced technology such as our Twin Cooling system and the industry-first dual ice maker, which makes entertaining at home an easy feat."<br><br><b>RFG298 and RF268 French Door Refrigerators with Dual Ice Maker</b><br>The Samsung RFG298 and RF268 French Door Refrigerators feature the industry's first dual ice maker. An external filtered water and ice dispenser is located in the refrigerator and an additional ice maker is in the freezer. The dual, independently operated, ice makers do not take away from the interior capacity of the refrigerators and can be turned on and off. They offer the problem-solving benefit of increasing the ice making ability of the refrigerator when consumers need it, which is ideal for families and home entertaining.<br>The 28.5 cu. ft. RFG298 also boasts the largest storage capacity in a French Door Refrigerator with a standard footprint, offering an extra 3 cu. ft. of space over standard French Doors. This extra large interior is achieved through an advanced process that reduces the size of the interior insulation while creating more useable room. The RF268 also offers a spacious interior at 26 cu. ft., allowing consumers more storage room over standard French Doors, meaning less trips to the grocery store.<br><br>The RFG298 will be available in May in stainless ($2,999), platinum ($2,899), black ($2,699) and white ($2,699). The RF268 will be available in June in stainless ($2,499), platinum ($2,399), black ($2,199) and white ($2,199).<br><br><b>RFG238 and RFG237 Counter-Depth French Door Refrigerators</b><br>The RFG238 and RFG237 are Samsung's new counter-depth French Door Refrigerators, which are designed to create an integrated look in any kitchen. Both counter-depth refrigerators fit flush with cabinets to create more workable space in the kitchen while still providing a large 23 cu. ft. of interior room, which is 2 cu. ft. more than typical counter depth models.<br>The RFG238 French Door also adds in Samsung's innovative dual ice maker, providing an added convenience for entertaining at home. The RFG237 French Door features an external filtered water and ice dispenser. The RFG237 also features internal LED lighting, which is brighter and more energy-efficient than traditional lighting.<br>The RFG237 will be available in May in stainless for $2,899. The RFG238 will be available in stainless for $2,999 in Fall 2009.<br><br><b>RF217 and RF197 Bottom-Mount Refrigerators</b><br>Samsung's RF217 and RF197 are designed to fit in more compact kitchens. At just 33 inches wide, both refrigerators are still packed with features, including an automatic filtered ice maker<br>in the freezer, door alarm and gallon door bins. The RF217 offers 19.8 cu. ft. of storage capacity, while the RF197 has 18 cu. ft.<br>The RF217 will be available in May for $1,399 in platinum and $1,199 in white. The RF197 will also be available in May for $1,299 in platinum and $1,099 in white.<br>All of Samsung's new refrigerators feature the company's Twin Cooling System™, a technology that independently cools the refrigerator and the freezer to maintain the proper humidity levels in each compartment and prevent odor transfers between storage areas. In addition, they are equipped with Samsung's EZ-Open Handle™, which allows the freezer to glide open effortlessly.<br><br>True to Samsung's commitment to increasing energy efficiency in the home, the entire line of French Door Refrigerators complies with Energy Star® standards.<br>In addition, Samsung has been named by J.D. Power in the 2008 Home Appliance Study as the brand ranked highest in customer satisfaction for Side-by-Side/French Door Refrigerators. Samsung excelled in the areas of performance, ease of use, styling/feel, and operational features. This marked the fourth year in a row that Samsung has received the prestigious customer satisfaction award from J.D. Power for refrigerators.<br><br>Samsung Electronics America's press releases, video content and product images are available at <b>www.samsung.com/newsroom</b>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc.</b><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning, digital consumer electronics and home appliance products, including HDTVs, home theater systems, MP3 players, digital imaging products, refrigerators and washing machines. A recognized innovation leader in consumer electronics design and technology, Samsung is the HDTV market leader in the U.S. Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> for more information.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Electronics Presents New Line Of Data Projectors</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., April 14, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America</b>, a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, today announced the release of its family of data projector products.  The P Series (Portable), L Series (LCD), D Series (Data), and A Series (A/V) are a combination of technical innovations that enhances the brightness, color, and accuracy of the projected picture while providing the functionality needed for academic, corporate, professional or home use.  The entire line of projectors strives to have the best Front of Screen performance in alignment with our TV, Pro Display and Monitor products. <br><br>"Samsung's Data Projectors focus on what customers are looking for - accurate Front of Screen performance, unique contemporary designs, almost silent operation, and connection flexibility," said <b>Mr. JH Kim, President, Information Technology Division, Samsung Electronics America Inc</b>.  "Our new line of Data Projectors complements our award winning Desktop Displays and powerful Large Format Displays, rounding out our full line of IT visual display offerings."<br><br>The Samsung family of Data Projectors is ideal for those searching for high performance in color and brightness with low operating noise.  For impromptu presentations or mobile applications, the compact design of the P Series (P400) makes the ultraportable projector lightweight, less than 2 pounds, with best-in-class brightness, 150 ANSI lumens, from an LED light source, and standardized audio/video connections.<br><br>For educational use or corporate environments, such as classrooms and conference rooms, the Samsung L Series (L220 & L300) are complete stand alone multimedia projectors capable of providing sharp color-rich images and sound from any AV or PC source, including HDMI (L300 only). While the L Series' 3 Chip technology enhances picture quality through realistic color reproduction, its built-in speakers offers stereo sound output to run media-rich video applications without additional audio support. <br><br> For larger venues, such as auditoriums and lecture halls, the D series (D300 & D400) uses DLP technology to offer higher brightness in dark or lighted conditions and versatile connectivity, including HDMI.    <br><br>For the home theater enthusiast or professional who demands the highest quality picture, the A Series (A400, A800 & A900) offers a full movie experience.  The A Series creates a vibrant picture with wide-screen resolution, an expanded color palette, and increased color brightness by 50%.  The A800 and A900, known as the "Joe Kane Signature Series", utilizes the Digital Light Processing (DLP) optical engine to offer 1080p Full HD resolution enabling viewers to watch movies as the director intended. Joe Kane is a veteran of the home theater industry and recognized as one of this country's leading HD experts.<br><br>"We've taken our expertise in displays and technology offering to give our projectors excellent picture quality.  Every aspect of the projector, from the exterior to the AV inputs and sound system, was designed to maximize the viewing experience," said <b>Tom Grau, Sr. Product Marketing Manager, Projectors at Samsung Electronics' Information Technology Division</b>. "As we expand our line of Data Projectors, we are launching a family of strategic offerings for growing market segments that leverage our brand's heritage for superior display performance." <br><br>Samsung's picture quality and brightness is a direct result of significant R&D invested to produce projectors based on either DLP® (Digital Light Processing) or 3LCD optical engines, which provide a higher quality picture and richer colors for displaying presentations, pictures and video in their natural colors.  With brightness levels up to 4000 lumens, the projectors can be use in either a dark classroom or well-lit auditorium.  The L-series projectors' shorter throw enables it to be placed in the center of a classroom or training room and provide the display and audio performance for the entire audience to experience.  The solid construction of the L Series, D Series and A Series allows them to run quietly at a range of 26 to 32 dB.   <br><br><br>All Data Projectors are available through Samsung resellers and distribution channels, which can be located by calling 1-800-SAMSUNG or by visiting www.samsung.com.  Samsung Power Partners receive special promotions, lead referrals, training and technical support, as well as collateral and marketing materials. To find out more about becoming a Samsung Power Partner, visit <b>www.samsungpartner.com</b>. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) is one of the fastest growing IT companies in the U.S., and is committed to serving the IT needs of consumers ranging from the home user to the Fortune 500 elite, and supports the valued channel partners who serve our customers.  Offering innovative solutions and award-winning designs, Samsung ITD presents a complete line of award-winning color and mono-laser printing solutions, desktop monitors, notebook computers, digital signage solutions and projectors.  Based in Ridgefield Park, N.J., ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com or call 1-800-SAMSUNG</b>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Introduces World&#039;s Narrowest Bezel Technology On Large Format LCD</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., April 03 2009 - Samsung Electronics America</b>, a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, the number one worldwide brand of professional Large Format LCD display products, today launched the <b>460UT, 460UTn and 460UTn-UD Series</b>, a 46" LCD Professional Display with a super-narrow bezel space measuring a mere 2.4 mm (right and bottom) of the screen and 4.3 mm (left and top).  With such a thin bezel, tiling multiple units of these displays creates only 7.3 mm between the live screen areas. The displays are built to deliver an almost seamless video wall solution with one of the smallest bezel spaces on a commercial LCD product. The 460UT Series is also compatible with Samsung's exclusive patented Interlocking Display Solution, Samsung ID2, which allows system integrators to easily align and build video walls with perfect matching bezels in three directions.  <br><br>Developed with Samsung's renowned front-of-screen performance and technology leadership, the 460UT Series delivers up to 700 nits of brightness, a 1366 x 768 resolution and contrast ratio of 3000:1 creating a vivid and detailed viewing experience.  It also has full connectivity, to ensure compatibility with a range of video and PC applications and a built-in video wall processor with natural view mode to account for the very slim bezels.  Accessibility is also addressed with the removable back panel providing easier access to the control board and PC slot.  This top-of-the-line professional display also features Samsung's exclusive DID panel technology to help support users who require 24/7 continuous operation.<br><br>The 460UTn also features a built-in network PC running Microsoft Windows XP-embedded, and Samsung's exclusive MagicInfo™ content management and delivery software providing users with an easy tool to manage content over a network.  The UT Series will be available in April.  <br><br>The 460UTn-UD offers a software solution for the creation of a video wall (up to 250 displays) running in real-time from a single PC, while processing information from up to 125 PC sources.  The software provides the flexibility to manipulate content by zooming in and out or switching and dragging images.  <br><br>"The 460UT Series is a true example of how Samsung continues to expand its leadership role in the digital signage market.  The monitor's fluid, uninterrupted images afforded by its unique super thin bezel is unmatched when combined with its back-end access and is a rich offering for system integrators by reducing downtime and lost productivity," said<b> J.H. Kim, President of Samsung Electronics America's Information Technology Division.</b>  "The 460UT is the ultimate video wall display offering.  I am confident this technology will be in demand for some time, and continue to evolve as users' needs become more sophisticated and complex."<br><br>The 460UT Series' state-of-the-art video wall technology reclaims space from old video cubes, while streamlining video wall design with the Samsung ID (Interlocking Display) solution.  With the footprint savings, accessibility and integrated features like the network PC and MagicInfo Pro content management and delivery software, this Series revolutionizes how system integrators design and build video walls.<br><br><b><u>460UT, 460UTn and 460UTn-UD LCD Displays</u></b><br>-	Super-narrow 2.4 mm (R & B sides) or 4.3 mm (L & T sides) bezel area <br>-	Samsung DID panel technology for 24/7 continuous operation<br>-	Up to 700 nits of brightness<br>-	Integrated network PC with Samsung's exclusive MagicInfo™ Content Management & Delivery solution (460UTn only)<br>-	UD (Ultra Definition) Software allows for the creation of a video wall (up to 250 displays) running from a single PC with flexibility to manipulate content in real-time (460UTn-UD only)<br>-	1366 x 768 resolution<br>-	3-year, on-site parts/labor warranty<br>-	3000:1 contrast<br>-	8 ms Response Time<br>-	Full PC- and video-connectivity<br><br>All monitors are available through Samsung resellers and distribution channels, which can be located by calling 1-800-SAMSUNG or by visiting <b>www.samsung.com</b>.  Samsung Power Partners receive special promotions, lead referrals, training and technical support, as well as collateral and marketing materials. To find out more about becoming a Samsung Power Partner, visit <a href="http://www.samsungpartner.com">www.samsungpartner.com</a>. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) is one of the fastest growing IT companies in the U.S., and is committed to serving the IT needs of consumers ranging from the home user to the Fortune 500 elite, and supports the valued channel partners who serve our customers.  Offering innovative solutions and award-winning designs, Samsung ITD presents a complete line of award-winning color and mono-laser printing solutions, desktop monitors, notebook computers, digital signage solutions and projectors.  Based in Ridgefield Park, N.J., ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  For more information, please visit www.samsung.com or call 1-800-SAMSUNG.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Launches Its Latest Network-Ready,Mono Laser Multifunctional Printer For Workgroups</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, NJ, March 10, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America, Inc</b>., a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, the world's second-largest manufacturer of laser printer engines, announces the addition of their new high-speed monochrome laser multifunctional printer designed for workgroups.  The<b> SCX-5835FN</b> is an affordable copy/print/scan/fax monochrome laser printer with an estimated street price of $1,099, and is available today through all of Samsung's valued Channel Partners.   <br>                        <br><b>Unique Design, Network-Ready and Feature-Rich</b><br>The easy-to-use workgroup printer prints up to 35 pages per minute, and its robust, professional look allows it to fit easily into any office network, and all while working quickly and quietly.  Along with its adaptable design and compact size, the Samsung SCX-5835FN is network-ready, and has an array of scan options and unique security features.   Users can scan full color documents to a network, USB drive or an E-mail account.  Security and jobs can also be managed directly from the bright 7-inch, monochrome touchscreen interface.  For instance, users can send a confidential job to the SCX-5835FN, and it will store it until released via password from the touchscreen.  Large jobs can be printed during off hours to increase security and printer availability.  Jobs may be accessed via codes and the queue rearranged for maximum efficiency.  <br><br>The SCX-5835FN is compatible with document management software for applications in education, government and healthcare, offering industry-leading, bundled security and solutions capabilities.  The system also allows organizations to control printing costs through included management utilities.  The SCX-5835FN has an estimated low $0.0159 cost per page.<br><br>"Samsung understands the needs of today's workgroup users, of whom are the inspiration for our new SCX-5835FN and professional series line of office solutions," said <b>Ken Colby, Director of Printer Product Marketing for Samsung Electronics America, Inc</b>.  "Not only does this feature-rich printer provide professional quality and functionality, but it's also a complete document management solution that allows users to copy, print, scan and fax faster and more cost-effectively than ever -- all in a compact footprint."<br>Samsung SCX-5835FN<br>-	35 ppm speed<br>-	7-inch monochrome touch screen interface<br>-	80,000-page monthly duty cycle   <br>-	1,050-sheet capacity paper tray <br>-	80GB hard drive supporting advanced document management features<br>-	Up to 1200 x 1200 dpi effective output<br>-	Duplex Printing<br>-	50-page Duplex ADF<br>-	1 year parts and labor, next day on site warranty<br><br>Samsung supports customer satisfaction with multiple service and warranty options.   There is also a toll-free technical support line at 1-800-SAMSUNG, choose option 3 for printers.  For additional information on Samsung's full line of professional series, laser printers and MFPs call<b> 1-866 SAM4BIZ or visit www.samsung.com/printer</b>.  <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) is one of the fastest growing IT companies in the U.S., and is committed to serving the IT needs of consumers ranging from the home user to the Fortune 500 elite, and supports the valued channel partners who serve our customers.  Offering innovative solutions and award-winning designs, Samsung ITD presents a complete line of award-winning color- and mono-laser printing solutions, desktop monitors, notebook computers, digital signage solutions and projectors.  Based in Ridgefield Park, N.J., ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com or call 1-800-SAMSUNG</b>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Launches Mobile Experience Tour to Showcase Affordable Printing Solutions for Business</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Samsung Electronics America, Inc</b>., a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, the world's second-largest manufacturer of laser printer engines, announced the launch of The Samsung Mobile Experience Tour 2009, a 30-city U.S. campaign, sponsored by the Samsung Printing Solutions group. The program aims to help drive awareness among solution providers and their enterprise customers of the company's cost-effective printing solutions for business. The centerpiece of the campaign is a customized, 40-foot RV that serves as a mobile showcase for Samsung's printers and other IT products. The tour launched late January in Tampa, Fla. during Super Bowl XLIII 2009. <br><br>The Samsung Mobile Experience RV carries seven single-function printers and multifunctional printers that offer the fast, high-quality output, seamless plug-and-play connectivity and user-friendliness businesses desire. These models include the <b>CLX-8380ND, SCX-6555N, CLX-6240FX, SCX-4828FN and SCX-5835FN </b>multifunctional printers, and the CLP-660ND and ML-4050N laser printers. <br><br>"Samsung has always been committed to creating technology that makes sense from an operational, design and budget perspective for our business customers. This tour shows the collective impact that those elements bring to today's office space," said <b>JH Kim, President of Samsung Electronics America's Information Technology Division</b>. "The intimacy of the campaign allows customers to interact with printing solutions to help alleviate the guesswork for IT decision makers, which, in turn, helps Samsung and its solution providers strengthen their relationships within the market. The Samsung Mobile Experience underscores our consistent support for both our end users and solution providers. It gives them a venue where they can productively engage with one another, and receive real-time feedback to help them work smarter and grow their businesses. <br><br>Intellinetics is one of the solution providers that will have the opportunity to showcase to customers the benefits of integrating their document management technology within Samsung printers. <br><br>"Intellinetics is pleased to work in partnership with Samsung on this campaign, as it not only empowers customers to think in new ways on how to better manage their businesses, but it provides a stage on which providers like us can bring to life our printer solutions," said <b>Matt Chretian, President of Intellinetics</b>. "These types of innovative programs allow us to connect with the market, which in turn helps to position us as a reliable resource for customers' document management needs." <br><br>As an incentive, a 46-inch Samsung LCD TV will be awarded in a monthly drawing to select customers who complete an online survey. <br><br>For more information on the Samsung Mobile Experience Tour 2009, please contact your local sales representative or E-mail SMET@samsung.com. Interested parties also can visit the tour's Web site at <a href="http://www.samsungmobileexperiencetour.com" target="_blank">www.samsungmobileexperiencetour.com</a>. <br><br>Samsung supports customer satisfaction with multiple service and warranty options. A toll-free technical support line can be accessed by calling 1-800-SAMSUNG - choose option 3 for printers. For more information on Samsung's full line of professional series laser printers and MFPs, call 1-866 SAM4BIZ or visit <b>www.samsung.com/printer.</b> <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division </b><br><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) is one of the fastest growing IT companies in the U.S., and is committed to serving the IT needs of consumers ranging from the home user to the Fortune 500 elite, and supports the valued solution providers who serve our customers. Offering innovative solutions and award-winning designs, Samsung ITD presents a complete line of award-winning color- and mono-laser printing solutions, desktop monitors, notebook computers, digital signage solutions and projectors. Based in Ridgefield Park, N.J., ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC). For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com or call 1-800-SAMSUNG.</b> <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd </b><br><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Launches 1.5 Terabyte &#034;EcoGreen&#034; F2EG Hard Disk Drive</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>SAN JOSE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd</b>., a world leader in digital consumer electronics and information technology, today announced its new <b>EcoGreen F2EG hard disk</b> that delivers a massive 1.5TB of capacity with 500GB per disk. With increased recording density and reduced number of disks, the EcoGreen F2 drive is more power efficient by supporting a capacity up to 1.5TB with 3 disks. <br><br>"Lower platter count means less power to start the motor, less power to continuously spin the motor and a lighter head-stack which takes less power to seek," said<b> Andy Higginbotham, director of HDD sales and marketing for the Samsung Semiconductor Storage Division</b>. "With fewer heads and disks, the F2EG hard drive has a lower probability of head-disk failures, enabling customers to build more reliable systems." <br><br>As hard disk capacity increases from an increased number of disks, so does power consumption. However, Samsung's F2EG drive offers low power consumption by using EcoTriangle™, a low-power, low-heat, low-noise operation technology. With its advanced design and fewer components, the F2EG drive is 40% lower in power consumption in idle mode and 45% lower in reading/writing mode than competitive drives. Samsung's Eco-Triangle™ technology offers more energy efficient and high performance hard drive options to manufacturers of home media PC, external HDD, set-top box, and personal NAS. <br><br>In addition to the European Union (EU)'s Restriction of the Use of Certain Hazardous Substances in Electrical and Electronic Equipment (RoHS) Regulations, Samsung's F2EG drive complies with many other environmental regulations. <br><br>Samsung's EcoGreen F2EG drive, which is suitable for both external hard disks and desktop PC, incorporates 500GB/1TB/1.5TB capacity, 16MB/32MB buffer memory, and 3.0 gigabytes per second (Gbps) Serial Advanced Technology Attachment (SATA) interface. The F2EG hard drive, employing advanced PMR technology, achieves greater aerial density and improves transfer performance as well. <br><br>The F2EG family of drives is currently being shipped to major OEM businesses. The 1.5TB HDD is available at $149.00 MSRP. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics </b><br><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Introduces Pair of 12 Mega-Pixel, 24mm Ultra-Wide Angle Compact Digital Cameras</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J--Samsung Electronics America</b> today unveiled two new 12 mega-pixel compact digital cameras boasting 24mm ultra-wide angle Schneider lenses. Samsung's new TL320 raises the bar for innovation in the digital imaging industry as it is the world's first digital camera to feature a three-inch AMOLED screen with HVGA resolution. The new HZ15W, Samsung's second mega-zoom, point-and-shoot digital camera, offers consumers one of the most powerful lenses on a compact point-and-shoot with an impressive focal length of 24-240mm (35mm film equivalent). <br><br><b>The TL320 </b><br><br>The new TL320 goes above and beyond traditional compact point-and-shoot digital cameras, offering an impressive list of features that set the camera apart from the competition. The TL320 features a Schneider lens, renowned for quality and trusted by professionals worldwide, and offers consumers a more versatile 24mm ultra-wide angle focal length paired with a powerful 5x optical zoom. <br><br>Utilizing the same advanced technologies found in its revolutionary AMOLED televisions, Samsung was able to incorporate a three-inch, 460,000-dot HVGA AMOLED screen in the new TL320, the largest AMOLED screen on a digital camera to date. In comparison to a traditional TFT-LCD screen, the TL320's AMOLED consumes less power and offers a higher contrast ratio of 10,000:1, producing darker black levels, more vibrant colors, and a brighter display which can easily be viewed outdoors and even in direct sunlight. Additionally, unlike a TFT-LCD, the TL320's AMOLED screen has the ability to display images that can be reviewed at any angle, while fully maintaining the same color gamut. <br><br>Samsung's new TL320 also offers advanced high-definition video recording at a resolution of 720p, as well as HDMI connectivity through the use of a cradle to view one's video and photos in HD clarity on an HDTV. The camera's 5x optical zoom can be used while recording, and because the camera utilizes H.264 compression (a codec for high-definition video that yields three times the recording length than that of MJPEG video) users can record HD video for longer periods of time with the TL320. <br><br>For added stability and blur-free images, Samsung has outfitted the TL320 with both Optical and Digital Image Stabilization. The shooter has the option of simply using Optical Image Stabilization or choosing Dual Image Stabilization, combining the strengths of Optical and Digital Image Stabilization. <br><br>For the more advanced user who prefers to have more control over camera settings, the TL320 offers aperture priority, shutter priority, full manual shooting, as well as Samsung's unique Advanced Picture Mode. Much more precise than simple white balance presets, Advanced Picture Mode gives users the ability to fine tune color tones before image capture by adjusting the color temperature from 2,800-10,000K, in 100K increments, or by manually configuring the camera's color space shift. <br><br>For users looking for simplicity when it comes to taking digital images, the TL320 offers a comprehensive suite of automatic controls designed to help them capture better images with ease, including the camera's Smart Auto mode. When selected, Smart Auto will automatically choose from one of the TL320's 11 scene modes, determining which best suits the environment the user may be shooting in. For example, the TL320's Smart Auto feature will automatically set the camera to its Landscape scene mode if the user is taking an image of a mountain range, and then switch gears and automatically select the Portrait scene mode if the user proceeds to take an image of an individual. No manual interaction is required. <br><br>In addition to Smart Auto, the TL320 also incorporates Samsung's proprietary Smart Album program. Smart Album is useful tool which allows users to easily search for a specific image they have saved on their memory card. Smart Album automatically organizes the user's digital images and gives them the ability to narrow their search based on specific criteria. Users can quickly sort by the date or week the image was taken, the overall color tone, as well as whether they're searching for portraits or specific file types, including photos, videos, or voice memos. <br><br>Users can also take advantage of the TL320's Face Detection, Blink Detection, Smile Shot, and Beauty Shot technologies. Designed to help capture better portraits and group shots of family and friends, Face Detection technology detects up to nine faces and automatically adjusts focus and exposure to ensure better composition and image quality. Smile Shot automatically triggers the TL320 to take a photo only when the camera detects smiles on the subjects' faces, and Blink Detection will automatically fire two consecutive shots if the camera detects that a subject's eyes are closed. Beauty Shot is a unique functionality which will automatically enhance and balance skin tones as well as remove blemishes. <br><br>Featuring a brushed stainless steel finish, the TL320 is as stylish as it is advanced. The camera offers a compact form factor highlighted by two analog dials found on top of the TL320's body. The two dials give the TL320 a retro look and provide users with the ability to quickly glance down at the camera for an approximate readout of remaining battery life and memory capacity. <br><br><b>The HZ15W </b><br><br>The step up model from the HZ10W introduced in January at CES 2009, the 12 mega-pixel HZ15W offers consumers one of the most powerful lenses on a compact point-and-shoot digital camera, featuring a 24mm ultra-wide angle Schneider lens coupled with a generous 10x optical zoom. For blur-free images, especially when using the HZ15W at its maximum zoom, Samsung includes both Optical and Digital Image Stabilization. Optical Image Stabilization can be used independently or shooters can choose Dual Image Stabilization, which combines the strengths of Optical and Digital Image Stabilization. <br><br>Like the HZ10W, the HZ15W puts high-definition video recording in the palm of users' hands. With the HZ15W, consumers have the ability to record high-definition video at a resolution of 720p, and utilize the camera's full 10x optical zoom. Samsung also incorporates H.264 compression and offers consumers true HDMI connectivity, which allows the camera to be connected directly to an HDTV without the need for a cradle. Additionally, the HZ15W's ultra-clear, three-inch LCD screen is sure to turn heads and gives consumers the ability to easily frame their shots and review their images and video in any condition, even in direct sunlight. <br><br>Designed for a range of consumers, including entry-level photographers and advanced amateurs, the HZ15W offers a variety of shooting modes, including Manual. The camera's Manual shooting mode allows users to manually configure settings such as shutter speed, aperture, exposure, and ISO values. Similar to the TL320, the HZ15W also features a highly-intuitive suite of automatic controls designed to help improve one's ability to take great digital images. The camera's advanced automatic shooting options include Face Detection, Smile Shot, Blink Detection, Beauty Shot, as well as Smart Auto, which automatically selects the appropriate scene mode for the user, and Smart Album, which simplifies the process of searching for an image saved on a memory card. <br><br><b>The Samsung HZ15W will be available in March 2009 at an MSRP of $329.99 </b><br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, is a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. The company markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products, as well as oversees all of Samsung's North American operations including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. As a result of its commitment to innovation and unique design, the company was ranked #6 in the Electronics Industry segment in Fortune Magazine's "Most Admired Companies 2008," and named as one of Fast Company's "Fast 50 Most Innovative Companies of 2008." Among popular BusinessWeek rankings, the company ranked #26 in the publication's "Most Innovative Companies of 2008" and #21 in the "100 Best Global Brands" for 2007. Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is also a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2007. Please visit <b>www.samsung.com </b>for more information.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Mobile and Paramount Digital Entertainment Collaborate to Offer Bundled Movie Content-Loaded Memory Card with Purchase of Samsung Delve™ from Alltel Wireless</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>DALLAS--Samsung Telecommunications America</b>, (Samsung Mobile) a leading mobile phone distributor in the U.S., and Paramount Digital Entertainment today announced the availability of a 2G microSD card pre-loaded with the Mission Impossible Trilogy with the purchase of a Samsung <b>Delve™</b> from Alltel Wireless. This is the first time that Samsung Mobile and Paramount Digital Entertainment have worked together to bundle full-length feature films(s) to add promotional value to its mobile products, without creating a price impact on its carrier partners or consumers. <br><br>"We are excited to bring an action-packed movie series like the Mission Impossible Trilogy to people who buy the Samsung Delve," said <b>Bill Ogle, Chief Marketing Officer for Samsung Mobile</b>. "When you combine this incredible content with the Delve's full set of powerful features, it's easy to stay entertained and connected no matter where you are." <br><br>The microSD card is available with the purchase of the Delve from February 20 through April 16, from participating Alltel Wireless retail stores and authorized dealers. <br><br>Alltel Wireless customers who purchase the Delve can send in a mail-in redemption card to receive the microSD within four to six weeks. For more information on the Alltel promotion and the Samsung Delve please visit www.samsung.com/missionexcitement or www.samsungwireless.com. <br><br><b>About Samsung Telecommunications America </b><br>Samsung Telecommunications America, LLC, a Dallas-based subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., researches, develops and markets wireless handsets and telecommunications products throughout North America. For more information, please visit <a href="http://www.samsungwireless.com" target="_blank"> www.samsungwireless.com</a>. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics </b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solution. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit<b> www.samsung.com</b>. <br><br><b>Paramount Digital Entertainment </b><br>Paramount Digital Entertainment (PDE) is a division of Paramount Pictures Corporation. PDE develops and distributes filmed entertainment across worldwide digital distribution platforms including online, mobile and portable devices, videogames, virtual worlds and emerging technologies. <br><br>Paramount Pictures Corporation (PPC), a global producer and distributor of filmed entertainment, is a unit of Viacom (NYSE: VIA, VIA.B), a leading content company with prominent and respected film, television and digital entertainment brands. The company's labels include Paramount Pictures, Paramount Vantage, Paramount Classics, MTV Films and Nickelodeon Movies. PPC operations also include Paramount Digital Entertainment, Paramount Famous Productions, Paramount Home Entertainment, Paramount Pictures International, Paramount Licensing Inc., Paramount Studio Group, and Worldwide Television Distribution. <br><br><b>Alltel Wireless </b><br>Alltel Wireless continues to be an industry-leader, providing choice and flexibility with its exclusive "My Circle" feature, giving customers unlimited, free calling to and from any five, 10 or 20 numbers on any network, including a combination of home phone, office or wireless numbers located anywhere in the U.S. Alltel Wireless was also the first to offer Anytime Plan Changes, giving customers the flexibility to change their calling plans at any time, without extending their contract. For more information, please visit <b>www.alltel.com</b>.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Collaborates With Solutions Provider To Embed Intelligent Device Management Software Into Its Multifunctional Printer Lineup</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., Feb. 24, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America, Inc.</b>, a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, the world's second-largest manufacturer of laser printer engines, announces their collaboration with leading solutions provider <b>MWA Intelligence, Inc. (MWAi) </b>to help businesses easily streamline print operations in an effort to minimize downtime and increase productivity.<br><br>Samsung will embed MWAi's IDM™ technology into the firm's lineup of monochrome and color laser multifunctional printers to enable remote device monitoring from any location.  In addition, Samsung has integrated their print management solution CounThru™, with MWAi's IntelliDashboard™, a reporting tool that monitors consumables, service alerts and meters.  These new technologies allow site, account and facilities managers and IT staff to more effectively oversee copy/print equipment across their businesses.<br><br>The Samsung/MWAi solution will be showcased at the Information Technology Education & Exposition (ITEX) 2009 held <b>March 18 - 19 in Las Vegas, Nevada</b>.<br><br>Samsung's CounThru™ software is a print services management and accounting solution that helps managers to remotely monitor activity, and calculate and help manage costs for their fleet of printers. This solution also allows customers to customize settings to help satisfy their unique needs.<br><br>MWAi's IntelliDashboard solution provides customers the scalability needed to adapt to evolving work environments, and has web-based technology so that printers can be monitored from a centralized point, whether on or offsite.  The solution also provides sophisticated drill-down capability for advanced device management and metrics gathering. <br><br>"Our collaboration with MWAi will help us provide robust printing device management solutions for enterprise customers," said <b>Mr. JH Kim, President, Information Technology Division, Samsung Electronics America Inc.</b>  "Samsung's commitment to develop innovative business solutions, along with the addition to MWAi's leading-edge device management capability, will help to support our continued growth in the office equipment marketplace."<br><br>"Samsung is to be commended for its proactive approach to meeting the needs of their growing customer base in North America," Mr. Stramaglio said.  "End users expect accurate billing that does not require their involvement, while dealers require the timely acquisition of meter reads, real-time consumable levels and service information to operate most effectively."<br><br>The relationship between Samsung and MWAi will address the growing demand for more efficient office equipment by offering embedded solutions that allow for remote asset management and workforce automation.<br><br>Samsung supports customer satisfaction with multiple service and warranty options.   There is also a toll-free technical support line at <b>1-800-SAMSUNG</b>, choose option 3 for printers.  For additional information on Samsung's full line of professional series, laser printers and MFPs call<b> 1-866 SAM4BIZ</b> or visit <a href="http://www.samsung.com/printer" target="_blank">www.samsung.com/printer</a>.  <br><br><br><b>About MWA Intelligence, Inc.</b><br>MWA Intelligence, Inc. offers leading-edge technologies, world-class customer service and expertise in the office equipment and utilities vertical markets. We deliver comprehensive solutions to companies in need of remote asset management and improved service standards. MWA Intelligence has developed a platform-independent approach to asset, service and mobile workforce management that is flexible and scalable to accommodate company's unique requirements and grow as your business model evolves. Our solutions drive greater customer satisfaction and profit to the bottom line. For more information, please visit www.mwaintelligence.com.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) is one of the fastest growing IT companies in the U.S., and is committed to serving the IT needs of consumers ranging from the home user to the Fortune 500 elite, and supports the valued channel partners who serve our customers.  Offering innovative solutions and award-winning designs, Samsung ITD presents a complete line of award-winning color- and mono-laser printing solutions, desktop monitors, notebook computers, digital signage solutions and projectors.  Based in Ridgefield Park, N.J., ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  For more information, please visit www.samsung.com or call <b>1-800-SAMSUNG</b>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Extends Popular SL-Series With Four New Models</title>
			<description>			
						

				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J. - February 17, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America</b> today extended its popular SL-Series with the introduction of four new models, comprising two 12.2 mega-pixel and two 10 mega-pixel digital cameras. Stylish and advanced, the new SL-Series models elevate the stature of the user-friendly family of digital cameras, allowing consumers to experience higher-end features and performance at more affordable price points.   <br><br><b><u>The SL820 and SL620</u></b><br>	Samsung's new 12.2 mega-pixel SL820 and SL620 offer users large three inch LCD screens and powerful 5x optical zooms. With the SL820, users have access to a 28mm wide angle lens, while the SL620 offers a standard 35mm lens. Both the SL820 and SL620 are paired with Optical and Digital Image Stabilization to help reduce blur caused by hand movements.  Shooters have the option of simply using Optical Image Stabilization, ideal for well lit environments, or choosing Dual Image Stabilization and combining the strengths of Optical and Digital Image Stabilization. <br><br>	A first for Samsung's SL-Series, the new SL820 offers consumers high-definition video recording at a resolution of 720p, as well as HDMI connectivity, allowing the camera to be connected to an HDTV through a cradle for reviewing footage and photos. The camera also utilizes H.264 compression, an advanced codec that allows users to record video for longer periods of time. The SL620 offers users advanced MPEG-4 video recording at a resolution of 640x480. For added versatility, with both the SL820 and SL620, consumers can use the cameras' 5x optical zooms and Optical Image Stabilization while recording video.<br><br>	The new SL820 and SL620 offer an array of automatic controls, including Samsung's Smart Auto mode. When selected, Smart Auto will automatically choose from one of the cameras' 11 scene modes, determining which best suits the environment the user may be shooting in. For example, if the user is taking a photo of a mountain range, Smart Auto will automatically select the Landscape scene mode. If the user then proceeds to take photo of an individual, Smart Auto will switch to the Portrait scene mode - no manual interaction is required.<br><br>	In addition to Smart Auto, the SL820 and SL620 also feature Samsung's proprietary Smart Album program. In addition to Smart Auto, the SL202 features Samsung's Smart Album program. Smart Album is useful tool which allows users to easily search for a specific image they have saved on their memory card. Smart Album automatically organizes the user's digital images and gives them the ability to narrow their search based on specific criteria. Users can quickly sort by the date or week the image was taken, the overall color tone, as well as whether they're searching for portraits or specific file types, including  photos, videos, or voice memos.<br><br> 	Other automatic features found on the SL820 and SL620 include Face Detection, Blink Detection, Smile Shot, and Beauty Shot. Designed to help capture better portraits and group shots of family and friends, Face Detection technology detects up to nine faces and automatically adjusts focus and exposure to ensure better composition and image quality. Smile Shot automatically triggers the SL820 and SL620 to take a photo only when a smile is detected on the subjects' faces, and Blink Detection will automatically fire two consecutive shots if a subject's eyes are closed. Beauty Shot is a unique functionality which will automatically brighten and even out skin tones as well as remove blemishes.<br><br><b><u>The SL202 and SL30</u></b><br>Ideally suited for families and entry-level shooters looking for an easy-to-use digital camera, the 10 mega-pixel SL202 and SL30 present users with a range of features that will help them effortlessly capture digital images without having to worry about becoming entrenched in technical specifications or terminology. The SL202 and SL30 offer consumers a quality Samsung lens with a 3x optical zoom, as well as Digital Image Stabilization to help reduce blurry images. <br><br>	The SL202 boasts a stylish, compact design which is accentuated by an elegant, brushed metal finish. Powered by a rechargeable Li-Ion battery, the SL202 gives users the ability to record high quality MJPEG video at VGA resolution with a frame rate of 30fps. The video, along with photos, can be reviewed on the SL202's 2.7 inch LCD screen. Furthermore, the camera's advanced movie mode will allow users to pause and then resume recording video without having to save the clips as individual files. <br><br>	When it comes to snapping digital images, the new SL202 does a bulk of the work for the user thanks to a host of advanced automatic features, including Samsung's new Smart Auto mode and Smart Album program. Other automatic controls found on the SL202 include Face Detection, Blink Detection, Smile Shot, and Beauty Shot. <br><br>	For added convenience, the SL30 is powered by easily available, AA alkaline batteries, assuring end-users that they can find a replaceable power source no matter where they may be.  Like the SL202, the SL30 also offers users MJPEG, VGA video recording, Face Detection, which detects up to nine faces and automatically adjusts focus and exposure, as well as Beauty Shot, which automatically enhances subjects' skin tones. Photos and videos can be reviewed on the camera's 2.5 inch LCD screen.<br><br>The SL820 will be available in May 2009 at an MSRP of $279.99.<br>The SL620 will be available in March 2009 at an MSRP of $199.99.<br>The SL202 will be available in March 2009 at an MSRP of $149.99<br>The SL30 will be available in March 2009 at an MSRP of $99.99<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, is a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. The company markets a broad range of award-winning consumer electronics, information systems, and home appliance products, as well as oversees all of Samsung's North American operations including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc. As a result of its commitment to innovation and unique design, the company was ranked #6 in the Electronics Industry segment in Fortune Magazine's "Most Admired Companies 2008," and named as one of Fast Company's "Fast 50 Most Innovative Companies of 2008." Among popular BusinessWeek rankings, the company ranked #26 in the publication's "Most Innovative Companies of 2008" and #21 in the "100 Best Global Brands" for 2007.  Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd. is also a top patent holder, ranking second overall in the U.S. in 2007.  Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> for more information.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Memoir™ Makes Official Debut at Mobile World Congress 2009</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>BARCELONA, Spain--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Samsung Telecommunications America</b> (Samsung Mobile) and T-Mobile USA, along with photographer and model Helena Christensen today officially unveiled the Samsung Memoir™, a touch-screen phone with an impressive 8-megapixel camera for premium imaging functionality, to be available exclusively through T-Mobile USA beginning February 25, 2009. <br><br>Christensen was the first to gain hands-on experience with the Memoir, using it as her official phone and camera to shoot images during her travels around New York and Barcelona. "As a photographer it was great for me to be the first to try the Memoir and to really experience everything it is capable of doing," said Christensen. "It's very important that my mobile phone also double up as a great camera, that way I always have my camera on hand to capture images at any moment. That's what a big part of photography is about." Christensen shared her images exclusively at the Memoir unveil event this evening in Barcelona. <br><br>The Memoir is designed to bring a high-quality digital imaging experience to the convenience of your mobile phone. The built-in 8-megapixel camera comes equipped with best-in-class digital imaging features, including Xenon flash, CMOS auto focus and 16x digital zoom. Accessing the Memoir's camera menu, users can adjust the brightness and flash, change the default destination of images, select a timer and zoom in or out. In addition, the Memoir's camera: <br><br><li>Allows users to set special effects on an image, including black and white, sepia, negative and watercolor; <br><li>Features blink detection, face detection, anti-shake to reduce blur, and geo-tagging, which records coordinate information of where the user is at the time the picture is taken into the image files; <br><li>Provides optimal settings for a variety of shooting situations to help capture the best possible image, including portrait, landscape, night, sports, party/indoor, beach snow, sunset, dawn, fall color, fireworks and backlight; <br><li>Automatically changes the white balance using the setting appropriate for the light source, including daylight, incandescent, fluorescent or cloudy; <br><li>Features five different shooting modes, including single, continuous, panorama, smile shot and mosaic. <p><br>Users can also record video for up to 60 minutes depending on the resolution format. The Memoir allows users to even create customized slideshows of their images with music and different transitions. With the TV-out feature, users can share custom slideshows, video or images on a television for everyone to enjoy. The Memoir's proximity sensor works to automatically adjust the backlight when using the phone's camera in different environments, as well as lock the LCD screen when brought to the user's ear when making or receiving calls. <br><br>The Memoir features Samsung's TouchWiz™ user interface, including two new widgets that give one-touch access to information and entertainment. The online weather widget connects to The Weather Channel automatically for updated weather information and forecasts in the user's city. The camera widget provides instant access to the user's pictures and camera functionality such as slideshow, as well as their favorite online photo sharing resource, including flickr®, Kodak Gallery®, Photobucket and Snapfish. With full HTML web browsing capabilities and T-Mobile's 3G network, users can also download images or videos and instantly make updates to social networking sites. In addition, the Memoir features a music and video player, as well as multiple messaging capabilities, full touch virtual QWERTY keypad with haptic feedback and Assisted GPS. <br><br>The Memoir will be exclusively available through T-Mobile USA beginning February 25, 2009. For more information and to see Christensen's images taken with the Memoir visit, www.samsung.com/newsroom. <br><br>T-Mobile's 3G coverage available in select markets. Samsung Memoir also works on T-Mobile's 2G network. <br><br><b>About Samsung Telecommunications America</b> <br>Samsung Telecommunications America, LLC, a Dallas-based subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., researches, develops and markets wireless handsets and telecommunications products throughout North America. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsungwireless.com</b>. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Company </b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solution. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com.</b>
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>Samsung Joins Global Initiative to Drive Development of LTE, 4G and Other Ultra-High Bandwidth Networks</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>BARCELONA, Spain--(BUSINESS WIRE)</b>--At the GSMA Mobile World Congress tradeshow and exhibition today Samsung Telecommunications America (Samsung Mobile) announced its participation in the ng Connect Program, a new multi-industry initiative which will drive the development of next generation broadband services based on Long Term Evolution (LTE) and other ultra-high bandwidth technologies. <br><br>Samsung is an experienced leader in developing and delivering personal broadband solutions, including significant investments in technology for 4G LTE and Mobile WiMAX networks and devices. Samsung will work with Alcatel-Lucent and other members of the ng Connect Program initiative to deliver new and exciting end-to-end home solutions and 4G ecosystems. <br><br>"Samsung's strength in communications and consumer electronics positions Samsung as the leader in convergence solutions that will benefit users in home, business, and mobile personal broadband use," said<b> Tom Jasny, vice president of broadband and network systems for Samsung Mobile</b>"This initiative is a powerful first step toward improving user experiences in and outside the home or office." <br><br><b>About Samsung Telecommunications America </b><br><br>Samsung Telecommunications America, LLC, a Dallas-based subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., researches, develops and markets wireless handsets and telecommunications products throughout North America. For more information, please visit www.samsungwireless.com. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics </b><br><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>. <br><br><b>About the ng Connect Program </b><br><br>The ng Connect Program is an industry organization committed to the development and rapid deployment of the next generation of broadband services based on Long Term Evolution (LTE) and other ultra high bandwidth technologies. Founded in 2009, the ng Connect Program is supported by leading network, consumer electronics, application and content providers including 4DK Technologies, Inc., Alcatel-Lucent, Buzznet, Connect2Media, dimedis, FISHLABS, QNX, SIGNEXX, Total Immersion, TuneWiki and Words & Numbers. For more information on the ng Connect Program, please visit: www.ngconnect.org.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>Samsung Mobile And T-Mobile USA Introduce Best-in-Class 8-Megapixel Camera Phone</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>DALLAS & BELLEVUE, Wash.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Samsung Telecommunications America </b>(Samsung Mobile) and T-Mobile USA, Inc., today announced the upcoming availability of the Samsung Memoir™, a full touch-screen mobile phone equipped with an 8-megapixel camera and premium multimedia features, placing it among the highest quality imaging phones available in the U.S. <br><br>The Memoir, available exclusively from T-Mobile, is designed to look and feel like a customer's current point-and-shoot digital camera. The built-in 8-megapixel camera with Xenon flash, 16x digital zoom and five shooting modes empower customers to capture exceptional photos and videos from their phone — whether they're on the go, on a vacation or just hanging out around the house. <br><br>The touch-screen phone, enabled by Samsung's TouchWiz™ user interface and powered by T-Mobile's high-speed 3G network, makes sharing photos easy. Samsung's new photo widget allows customers to post images taken with the Memoir directly to their favorite online photo sharing source, such as flickr®, Kodak® Gallery, Photobucket and Snapfish. <br><br>"With the 8-megapixel Samsung Memoir, T-Mobile customers can capture and share little slices of life in all their vibrant brilliance," said <b>Denny Marie Post, chief marketing officer, T-Mobile USA</b>. "With the ability to share photos at your fingertips, the Memoir helps make those connections more meaningful by their immediacy." <br><br>The Memoir's full-touch virtual QWERTY keypad and multiple messaging capabilities, including text, multimedia messaging, instant messaging and e-mail, make staying connected quick and easy while on the go. The Memoir is complete with a music and video player and built-in Assisted GPS navigation, which allows customers to utilize location-based services including turn-by-turn directions. For hands-free use, the Memoir features stereo Bluetooth® technology, speakerphone and voice-activated dialing. <br><br>"This is the camera phone that will make people want to leave their digital camera at home," said<b> Bill Ogle, Chief Marketing Officer for Samsung Mobile</b>. "When you combine the Memoir's imaging capabilities, customizable menus and music player, not only is it a great phone, but the entertainment possibilities are unlimited." <br><br>T-Mobile's 3G coverage available in select markets. Samsung Memoir also works on T-Mobile's 2G network. See coverage maps at T-Mobile.com <br><br>Model number: <b>SGH-t929 </b><br><br><b>About Samsung Telecommunications America </b><br><br>Samsung Telecommunications America, LLC, a Dallas-based subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., researches, develops and markets wireless handsets and telecommunications products throughout North America. For more information, please visit <a href="http://www.samsungwireless.com" target="_blank">www.samsungwireless.com</a>. <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics </b><br><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$103.4 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of five main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, Telecommunication Business and Digital Appliance Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>. <br><br><b>About T-Mobile USA, Inc. </b><br><br>Based in Bellevue, Wash., T-Mobile USA, Inc. is the U.S. operation of Deutsche Telekom AG's Mobile Communications Business, and a wholly owned subsidiary of T-Mobile International, one of the world's leading companies in mobile communications. By the end of the third quarter of 2008, 127 million mobile customers were served by the mobile communication segments of the Deutsche Telekom group — more than 32 million by T-Mobile USA — all via a common technology platform based on GSM, the world's most widely used digital wireless standard. T-Mobile's innovative wireless products and services help empower people to connect to those who matter most. For more information, please visit www.t-mobile.com. T-Mobile and the magenta color are federally registered trademarks of Deutsche Telekom AG.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Introduces Mono Laser Printer To Help Increase Workgroup Productivity</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., Jan. 29, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America, Inc.</b>, a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, the world's second-largest manufacturer of laser printer engines, today introduced the <b>ML-2855ND</b> mono laser printer with network-ready connectivity designed to increase workgroup productivity, with print speeds of up to 30 ppm, a 400MHz processor and 64MB memory (expandable to 192MB max.).  The model is now available at an MSRP of $357.99.<br><br>In addition to time savings, the ML-2855ND printer's built-in duplex printing and Samsung's TonerSave™ feature, offers one of the lowest Total Cost of Operation rates in its class.<br><br>"Our ML-2855ND model offers an immediate value-add for small- and medium-sized businesses seeking an affordable workgroup printer with the same superior performance, durability and reliability that all successful businesses rely on in today's competitive market," said <b>Ken Colby, Director of Product Management, Printers, at Samsung Electronics' Information Technology Division</b>.  "The addition to our printer lineup is a show of how Samsung continues to innovate so that our products remain relevant to our users' needs in the face of ever-evolving business challenges."<br>The model's high-quality laser printing ensures crisp, clean smudge-free printing, and has a 50,000-page monthly duty cycle to ensure reliability.  With user-friendliness in mind, the ML-2855ND printer allows for fast and hassle-free toner replacement, and has compass navigation and a 2-line LCD display for simple, quick access to a variety of functions, alerts and messages.<br><br>The model's compact form-factor offers space-saving benefits and makes it attractive for any office setting.  The unit also prints silently at a mere 50dBA to help reduce unnecessary noise.<br> <br>The ML-2855ND printer is equipped with a 250-sheet cassette and 50-sheet multipurpose tray.  An optional 250-sheet cassette offers a total capacity of 550 sheets.<br><br><b><u>Samsung ML-2855ND</u></b><br><br>The ML-2855ND mono laser printer is an affordable solution for small- and medium-sized businesses seeking superior performance, durability and reliability.<br><br>-	Compact form-factor<br>-	400MHz processor<br>-	64MB memory (expandable to 192MB max)<br>-	50,000-page monthly duty cycle <br>-	Fast 30 PPM print speeds<br>-	First print out time less than 8.5 secs<br>-	Built-in duplex printing functionality <br>-	Compass navigation<br>-	2-line LCD display <br>-	Silent printing at 50dBA<br>-	Network-ready connectivity<br>-	250-sheet cassette and 50-sheet multipurpose tray; an optional 250-sheet cassette for a total capacity of 550 sheets<br>-	Up to 1200 x 1200 dpi effective output<br>-	Hi-Speed USB 2.0 interface<br>-	Windows 2000/XP/Vista compatibility<br><br>Samsung supports customer satisfaction with multiple service and warranty options.  A toll-free technical support line can be accessed by calling 1-800-SAMSUNG - choose option 3 for printers.  For more information on Samsung's full line of professional series, laser printers and MFPs, call 1-866 SAM4BIZ or visit www.samsung.com/printer.  <br><br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) is one of the fastest growing IT companies in the U.S., and is committed to serving the IT needs of consumers ranging from the home user to the Fortune 500 elite, and supports the valued channel partners who serve our customers.  Offering innovative solutions and award-winning designs, Samsung ITD presents a complete line of award-winning color- and mono-laser printing solutions, desktop monitors, notebook computers, digital signage solutions and projectors.  Based in Ridgefield Park, N.J., ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com or call 1-800-SAMSUNG</b>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Introduces Affordability To Wireless Printing Technology While Increasing Workgroup Productivity</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J., Jan. 29, 2009</b> - The rising use of wireless printing is largely due to the significant flexibility it offers, enabling users on the same network to conveniently print from anywhere. Whether printing from a desktop at home, the office or from different mobile devices, including laptops or handheld PDAs, wireless connectivity is making it easier for workers to be productive and effective at their jobs. In addition, wireless printing saves valuable time and space by eliminating the clutter caused by cables and wires.<br><br>To deliver the same value and flexibility to its customers, Samsung Electronics America, Inc., a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, the world's second-largest manufacturer of laser printer engines, today introduced a new line of wireless printers - the <b>CLX-3175FW, ML-1630W </b>and <b>SCX-4500W</b>.  Equipped with integrated 802.11b/g wireless connectivity, the models offer the space- and time-saving benefits that workgroups require to remain successful.  Along with their convenient, wireless capability, the models' compact, sophisticated design is suited to the most distinctive tastes.  The CLX-3175FW, ML-1630W and SCX-4500W models are now available at an MSRP of $642.99, $285.99 and $428.99 respectively.<br><br>"Our new wireless printer lineup shows Samsung's desire to create products that makes conducting business simple for workgroups, without the hassle of wires and limitations that hard-wired printers impose," said <b>Ken Colby, Director of Product Management, Printers, at Samsung Electronics' Information Technology Division</b>.  "The CLX-3175FW, ML-1630W and SCX-4500W models offer the plug-and-play connectivity and unobtrusive design that today's users expect from Samsung."<br><br><b>Small, Sleek and Silent Solutions</b><br><br>The CLX-3175FW is a wireless color laser 4-in-1 solution that allows for printing, copying, scanning and faxing, all in an elegantly-designed, matte-black cabinet for any office setting.  The model is equipped with high-speed USB 2.0 and Ethernet for instant plug-and-play capability.  <br><br>Reported as one of the smallest, network-ready laser printers in the world, the ML-1630W model has a high-style glossy piano black finish, buttonless soft-touch sensor panels with blue LED indicators, and its 45 dBA ranks it as one of the quietest printer in the world.  <br><br>The ultra-compact SCX-4500W wireless laser multi-function printer is known to be one of the smallest network-ready laser printer/copier/color scanners in the world.  Similar to the ML-1630W model, the printer has a high-style glossy piano black finish that adds a touch of class to any environment.<br><br><b><u>Samsung CLX-3175FW</u></b><br><br>-	Network Ready Connectivity <br>-	Integrated 802.11b/g<br>-	Ethernet 10/100 Base TX<br>-	Print, copy, scan and fax<br>-	Laser printouts are crisp, sharp and smudge-free<br>-	Print speeds of up to 17ppm (in letter) (mono) / Up to 4ppm (in letter) (color) <br>-	Print resolution of up to 2,400 x 600 dpi effective output<br>-	Copy speeds of up to 17ppm (in letter) (mono) / Up to 4ppm (in letter) (color) <br>-	Copy resolution of up to 600 x 600 dpi<br>-	Scanner capability with Windows 2003 / XP / Vista <br>-	Scanner resolution of up to 4,800 x 4,800 dpi (enhanced)<br>-	Scan to USB, Email and Client (PC)<br>-	Fax speed of 33.6 Kbps with G3 compatibility and MH, MR, MMR and JBIG compression <br>-	Powerful 360MHz process and 128MB of memory<br>-	20,000 page monthly duty cycle<br>-	Paper input capacity of 150 sheets<br>-	Scan to and print from a USB Flash Drive<br>-	Hi-speed USB 2.0 interface <br>-	2-Line LCD<br>-	Exclusive NO NOIS print engine technology with less than 48 dBA printing<br>-	Smart Panel monitors toner level <br>-	Matte-black cabinet finish<br>-	Consumables<br>-	Average continuous black cartridge yield: 1,500 standard pages<br>-	Average continuous yellow/magenta/cyan cartridge yield: 1,000 standard pages<br>-	Imaging unit: approx. 24,000 pages (mono)/6,000 pages (color)<br>-	Waste Toner Container: approx. 10,000 pages (mono)/2,500 pages (color)<br>-	Model# CLT-P409A: value pack toner cartridge (1 each of cyan / magenta / yellow) for models CLP-315, CLP-315W, CLX-3175FN and CLX-3175FW<br>-	Model # CLT-P409B: Value pack toner cartridge (2 black toners) for CLP-315, CLP-315W, CLX-3175FN, CLX-3175FW<br><br><b><u>Samsung ML-1630W</u></b><br><br>-	Smallest network-ready laser printer in the world<br>o	Integrated 802.11b/g<br>o	Ethernet 10/100 Base TX<br>-	Print speeds of up to 17 ppm (in letter) <br>-	Laser printouts are crisp, sharp and smudge-free<br>-	Print resolution of up to 1200 x 1200 dpi effective output<br>-	Windows 2000 / XP / 2003 Server / Vista compatibility <br>-	Powerful 360MHz process and 64MB of memory<br>-	5,000 page monthly duty cycle <br>-	100-sheet sliding input cassette <br>-	Hi-speed USB 2.0 interface <br>-	45 dBA, one of the quietest printers in the world<br>-	Button-less soft-touch sensor panels with blue LED indicators <br>-	Soft, melodic low toner and low paper alert tones <br>-	Smart Panel monitors toner level<br>-	High-style glossy piano black finish<br>-	Consumables<br>-	Single cartridge yield up to 2,000 pages (starter up to 1,000 pages)<br>-	Model# ML-D1630A black toner cartridge compatible with ML-1630 and SCX-4500<br>-	MSRP of $79.99<br><br><b><u>Samsung SCX-4500W</u></b><br><br>-	Network Ready Connectivity <br>-	Integrated 802.11b/g<br>-	Ethernet 10/100 Base TX<br>-	Print, copy and scan<br>-	Laser printouts are crisp, sharp and smudge-free<br>-	Print speeds of up to 17ppm (in letter) (mono) <br>-	Print resolution of up to 600 x 600 dpi effective output<br>-	Copy speeds of up to 17ppm (in letter) (mono) <br>-	Copy resolution of up to 600 x 600 dpi effective output <br>-	Scanner Twain standard. WIA standard compatibility <br>-	Scanner resolution of up to 4,800 x 4,800 dpi (enhanced)<br>-	Windows 2000 / XP / 2003 Server / Vista compatibility <br>-	Powerful 360MHz process and 64MB of memory <br>-	5,000 page monthly duty cycle<br>-	100-sheet sliding input cassette <br>-	Hi-speed USB 2.0 interface <br>-	45 dBA, one of the quietest printers in the world<br>-	Button-less soft-touch sensor panels with blue LED indicators <br>-	Soft, melodic low toner and low paper alert tones <br>-	Smart Panel monitors toner level<br>-	High-style glossy piano black finish<br>-	Consumables<br>-	Single cartridge yield up to 2,000 pages (starter up to 1,000 pages)<br>-	Model# ML-D1630A black toner cartridge compatible with ML-1630 and SCX-4500<br>-	MSRP of $79.99<br><br>Samsung supports customer satisfaction with multiple service and warranty options.  A toll-free technical support line can be accessed by calling 1-800-SAMSUNG - choose option 3 for printers.  For more information on Samsung's full line of professional series, laser printers and MFPs, call 1-866 SAM4BIZ or visit <b>www.samsung.com/printer</b>.  <br><br><br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) is one of the fastest growing IT companies in the U.S., and is committed to serving the IT needs of consumers ranging from the home user to the Fortune 500 elite, and supports the valued channel partners who serve our customers.  Offering innovative solutions and award-winning designs, Samsung ITD presents a complete line of award-winning color- and mono-laser printing solutions, desktop monitors, notebook computers, digital signage solutions and projectors.  Based in Ridgefield Park, N.J., ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com or call 1-800-SAMSUNG.</b><br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit<b> www.samsung.com</b>.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Develops World&#039;s Highest Density DRAM Chip (Low-power 4Gb DDR3)</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>SEOUL, Korea--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd.</b>, the world leader in advanced memory technology, announced today that it has made a significant advancement in the push for higher volume memory chips by developing the world's first four gigabit (Gb) DDR3 DRAM chip, using 50 nanometer (nm) process technology. <br><br>With more and more data centers seeking a reduction in the number of servers they use, the development of low-power 4Gb DDR3 has become critical in reducing data center costs, improving server time management and increasing overall efficiency. <br><br>For the new generation of "green" servers, the 4Gb DDR3's high density combined with its lower level of power consumption will not only provide a reduction in electricity bills, but also a cutback in installment fees, maintenance fees and repair fees involving power suppliers and heat-emitting equipment. <br><br>"We have leveraged our strength in innovation to develop the first 4Gb DDR3, in leading the industry to higher DRAM densities," said Kevin Lee, vice president, technical marketing, Samsung Semiconductor, Inc. "By designing our 4Gb DDR3 using state-of-the-art 50-nm class technology, we are setting the stage for what ultimately will result in significant cost-savings, for servers and for the overall computing market," he added. <br><br>The 4Gb DDR3 can be produced in 16 gigabyte (GB) registered dual in-line memory modules (RDIMM) for servers, as well as 8GB unbuffered DIMM (UDIMM) for workstations and desktop PCs, and 8GB small outline DIMM (SODIMM) for laptops. By applying dual-die package technology, this new device can deliver modules of up to 32GB - offering twice as much capacity as memory modules based on the previous highest chip density of 2Gb. <br><br>Designed to be low-powered, the 4Gb DDR3 DRAM operates at 1.35 volts (V), therein improving its throughput by 20 percent over a 1.5V DDR3. Its maximum speed is 1.6 gigabits per second (Gbps). <br><br>In 16GB module configurations, 4Gb DDR3 can consume 40 percent less power than 2Gb DDR3 because of its higher density and because it uses only half the DRAM (32 vs. 64 chips). <br><br>With an aggressive conversion to 50nm-class production for higher density DDR3, Samsung intends to remain the clear leader in high-volume/high-performance DRAM. <br><br>In September 2008, Samsung announced its development of the world's first 50 nm-class 2Gb DDR3 DRAM. Now, just five months after, it has established the industry's broadest line-up of high-performance DDR3 products using 50 nm-class process technology (4Gb, 2Gb, 1Gb). <br><br>As forecasts have the amount of memory per server doubling every two years, the development of high-density DRAM is expected to keep pace, expanding to other applications such as notebooks and desktop PCs. <br><br>According to the International Data Corporation (IDC), a market research and analysis firm, the worldwide DDR3 DRAM market will account for 29 percent of the total DRAM market in 2009 and 75 percent in 2011. In addition, IDC estimates that 2Gb-or-higher DDR3 DRAM will make up three percent of the total DRAM market in 2009 and 33 percent in 2011 (units in bits). <br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Company </b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solutions. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Survey Says 43 Percent Of Football Fans Are Likely To visit In-Laws If They Owned An HDTV</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>RIDGEFIELD PARK, N.J. Jan. 28, 2009- Samsung Electronics America</b>, the market leader in HDTVs and the Official HDTV of the NFL and Super Bowl XLIII, today announced additional findings from a recently commissioned survey. The survey revealed that an HDTV can entice your spouse to visit the in-laws, even for the Super Bowl, if it means viewing football in high definition. <br>According to the survey, Americans, football fans or not, agree there is no better place to watch the game than at home when there is a high definition television in place. However, the survey also found that football fans are willing to take the show on the road, even to the in-laws, if they had the right incentive. More than four in ten (43%) football fans would be more likely to visit their in-laws if they had an HDTV to watch the game. Among this group, men are more likely than women to visit the in-laws if there was an HDTV waiting for them (50% vs. 34%). <br><br>The survey also revealed surprising results about the football-viewing experience in relation to food. Eighty-one percent of football fans say that TV picture quality is more important than the food while watching football on television. With TV size and HD capability as the most important features considered in viewing football on TV, high definition television comes out as the number one accessory for any football fan. <br><br>Despite the current economic conditions, football fans consider HDTV a worthwhile investment. <br>"As we get closer to the Super Bowl, football fans across the nation will be gearing up to watch The Big Game with their friends and families," said <b>John Revie, senior vice president of Visual Display Marketing for Samsung Electronics America</b>. "As the official HDTV of the NFL and Super Bowl XLIII, Samsung believes in delivering the best HD-viewing experience as part of the overall football-viewing at home."<br><br>The purpose of the survey, Pigskin Power: Football fans have a special bond with their televisions, was to explore the level and type of influence TV has on the football-viewing experience among Americans. The commissioned survey was conducted by Kelton Research among a nationally representative sample of 1,011 Americans, male and female, ages 18 and over.<br><br>*All decimals are rounded to the nearest percentage point. <br><br>Samsung Electronics America's press releases, video content and product images are available at our recently launched <a href="http://www.samsung.com/newsroom" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/newsroom</a>.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America, Inc. </b><br>Headquartered in Ridgefield Park, NJ, Samsung Electronics America, Inc. (SEA), a wholly owned subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., markets a broad range of award-winning digital consumer electronics home appliance products including HDTVs, home theater systems, MP3 players, digital imaging products, refrigerators and washing machines.  A recognized innovation leader in consumer electronics design and technology, Samsung is the HDTV market leader in the U.S.  Please visit www.samsung.com for more information.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Launches Super-Thin LED Monitor As Part Of Its "Touch Of Color" Family For Optimal Viewing</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>LAS VEGAS, Jan. 7, 2008 - Samsung Electronics America Inc</b>., a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, the number one monitor brand in the world, announced today the addition of a super-thin LED monitor to its "Touch of Color" (ToC™) family - the P2370L.  This new high-end, model has a Light Emitting Diode Back Light Unit (LED BLU), instead of the cold cathode fluorescent lamps (CCFL) found in standard LCD displays, and reproduces more vibrant color and higher contrast ratios than other monitors.  With its sophistication-meets-high technology form factor, the P2370L display will ship in late first quarter with an MSRP of $399.<br><br>The monitor's ToC design technology has an ultra-thin wrapper of just 16.5mm (0.65-inches) and is a great fit for any home or office environment, helping to maximize desktop real estate and minimize its physical and carbon footprint reduced.   Key eco-friendly benefits of the P2370L model include LED fluorescent lamps that do not contain harmful elements such as mercury or lead, consumption of  30% less energy and a longer life than a standard CCFL backlit unit.  In addition, the ToC manufacturing process eliminates harmful paints and sprays to enhance the recyclability of the entire monitor.<br><br>"As one would expect from Samsung, the P2370L represents the pinnacle of premium display craftsmanship as a high-end monitor that is sophisticated in not only appearance, but in the quality and performance it offers and in how it impacts the environment," said <b>R.A Atanus, Vice President of Product Marketing at Samsung Electronics' Information Technology Division</b>.  "This monitor is truly a leadership product that will further solidify Samsung's position as the foremost authority in the design, engineering and performance of displays worldwide."<br><br>The P2370L uses white LEDs and has a ultra-high contrast ratio of 2M:1.  The monitor also has an ultra fast 2ms (GTG) video response time and offers a 1080p full-HD experience.  <br><br>The P2370L display's transparent, crystal-like, bezel frame has blue gradation that gives it a glass-like appearance, and helps to reduce the reflection of light to decrease glare.  The model also has a unique glass stand neck that gives the illusion that the monitor is floating.  It is also equipped with Samsung's dual-injection technology that lends it a smooth, finished appearance without any screws or joints.<br><br>The P2370L is designed so that there are no obtrusive buttons on the front or sides on the panel.  Instead, each display features Samsung's unique Startlight Touch Controls which integrate the On Screen Display (OSD) buttons into the bezel for a seamless look and feel.<br><br>P2370L LED BLU Monitor<br>-	White LEDs<br>-	Ultra-thin, 16.5mm design<br>-	Ultra-high contrast ratio of 2M:1<br>-	Ultra fast 2ms (GTG) video response time<br>-	DVI-I Input<br>-	Offers a 1080p full-HD experience<br>-	Touch of Color" (ToC™) technology<br>-	Crystal-like bezel frame to help reduce glare<br>-	Swivel stand for optimal screen positioning<br>-	Starlight Touch Controls<br><br>All monitors are available through Samsung resellers and distribution channels, which can be located by calling 1-800-SAMSUNG or by visiting www.samsung.com.  Samsung Power Partners receive special promotions, lead referrals, training and technical support, as well as collateral and marketing materials. To find out more about becoming a Samsung Power Partner, visit <a href="http:www.samsungpartner.com" target="_blank"> www.samsungpartner.com</a>. <br><br>Samsung Electronics America's CES press releases, product images and video content is available at <a href="http://www.samsung.com/icespress" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/icespress </a> and its recently launched newsroom at <a href="http://www.samsung.com/newsroom" target="_blank"> www.samsung.com/newsroom</a><br><br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) markets a complete line of award-winning LCD Monitor products, including professional large format LCD and Plasma displays.  ITD also markets an award-winning line of color and monochrome laser printers and multifunction devices, and the new family of notebook PC including the innovative Samsung Q1 Ultra-Mobile Personal Computers (UMPC).  Samsung ITD is committed to supporting the needs of its channel partners in the professional, commercial, corporate, and SOHO markets.  Based in Ridgefield Park, New Jersey, ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  The SEA organization oversees the North American operations of Samsung including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc.  Please visit www.samsung.com for more information or call 1-800-SAMSUNG.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics Company </b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of two main business units: Digital Media & Communications and Device Solution. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit www.samsung.com.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
		<item>
			<title>SAMSUNG Monitors Use New Display Technology To Create Seamless Multi-DIisplay Solution</title>
			<description>			
				<![CDATA[
					<b>LAS VEGAS, Jan. 7, 2009 - Samsung Electronics America</b>, a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Corporation, the number one brand of LCD monitors in the world, today launched a set of high-performance monitors that offer a seamless multi-display solution for optimal viewing opportunities.  The monitors include a new 22-inch <b>SyncMaster 2243QW</b>, as well as the laptop companion monitors <b>LD220 and LD190X</b>.  All three monitors incorporate Samsung's UbiSync technology to help extend users' visual workspace by connecting up to six displays to a PC via USB cable.  <br><br>UbiSync technology creates a multi-monitor system that can be operated from a single PC without a graphics card or complex software installations.  The technology is especially valuable to users who desire portability and a larger, richer screen surface to help maximize productivity and visual effects.<br><br>"Samsung's UbiSync technology takes our monitors to a new level of distinction among users whose expectations increase with the ever-evolving display market," said <b>R.A Atanus, Vice President of Product Marketing at Samsung Electronics' Information Technology Division</b>.  "These three new monitors show that innovation, technology and style are not exclusive of each other.  Samsung's commitment to provide the best displays ensures users always get excellent graphics and versatility."<br><br>The Samsung 2243QW has a resolution of 1680 x 1050, a 1000:1 contrast ratio, and 5 ms response time ensuing smooth video performance on each networked display.  In addition to a built-in USB hub, it features the traditional VGA (15-pin D-sub) and DVI-D connections. The monitor is compatible with both Mac and Windows systems, and it comes with a pivot function that allows it to operate in either portrait or landscape mode.<br><br>The LD-series monitors feature sleek, clean contours and high-glossy black encasements to serve as secondary displays for today's stylish laptops.  The models' intelligent image size function projects 4:3 images from laptops in Movie Wide aspect ratios of 16:9 in HD content, allowing users to enjoy optimized visual effects for both entertainment and business purposes.  The LD220 and LD190X monitors have a resolution of 1920 x 1080 and 1366 x 768, 5ms response time, contrast ratio of 1000:1, and are compatible with Windows Vista operating systems.  With green in mind, the monitors have two-lamp low power consumption and an off timer to help conserve energy.  <br><br>The LD190X model uses UbiSync wireless technology that transmits video signal to the monitor from the host notebook and uses about 33 percent less energy than conventional 19" product.  <br><br>The UbiSync software allows the LD-series monitors to attain the same level of brightness on two screens, with one button, to help reduce eye fatigue, and an easy-to-adjust viewpoint.<br><br>Monitor Product Specifications <br><br><b>2243QW USB</b><br>-	1680 x 1050 resolution <br>-	1000:1 contrast ratio <br>-	5ms response time<br>-	Built-in USB hub(1U2D)<br>-	VGA (15-pin D-sub) and DVI-D connections<br>-	Mac and Windows compatibility<br>-	Pivot function for portrait or landscape mode<br><br><b>LD190X</b> <br>-	1366 x 768 native resolution<br>-	250 cd/m2 brightness<br>-	1000:1 contrast ratio <br>-	5ms response time<br>-	VGA and USB interface<br>-	Windows Vista compatibility<br>-	UbiSync Wireless technology<br>-	2-lamp low power consumption<br><br><b>LD220</b><br>-	1366 x 768 native resolution<br>-	250 cd/m2 brightness<br>-	1000:1 contrast ratio <br>-	5ms response time<br>-	VGA and USB interface<br>-	Windows Vista compatibility<br>-	UbiSync USB technology<br><br><br>All monitors are available through Samsung resellers and distribution channels, which can be located by calling 1-800-SAMSUNG or by visiting www.samsung.com.  Samsung Power Partners receive special promotions, lead referrals, training and technical support, as well as collateral and marketing materials. To find out more about becoming a Samsung Power Partner, visit www.samsungpartner.com. <br><br>Samsung Electronics America's CES press releases, product images and video content is available at <b>www.samsung.com/icespress</b> and its recently launched newsroom at www.samsung.com/newsroom.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics America Information Technology Division</b><br>Samsung's Information Technology Division (ITD) markets a complete line of award-winning LCD Monitor products, including professional large format LCD and Plasma displays.  ITD also markets an award-winning line of color and monochrome laser printers and multifunction devices, and the new family of notebook PC including the innovative Samsung Q1 Ultra-Mobile Personal Computers (UMPC).  Samsung ITD is committed to supporting the needs of its channel partners in the professional, commercial, corporate, and SOHO markets.  Based in Ridgefield Park, NJ, ITD is a division of Samsung Electronics America (SEA), a U.S. subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Company, Ltd. (SEC).  The SEA organization oversees the North American operations of Samsung including Samsung Telecommunications America, LP, Samsung Electronics Canada, Inc. and Samsung Electronics Mexico, Inc.  Please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b> for more information or call 1-800-SAMSUNG.<br><br><b>About Samsung Electronics</b><br>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2007 consolidated sales of approximately US$105 billion. Employing approximately 150,000 people in 134 offices in 62 countries, the company consists of four main business units: Digital Media Business, LCD Business, Semiconductor Business, and Telecommunication Business. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT-LCDs. For more information, please visit <b>www.samsung.com</b>.
				]]>					
			</description>
		</item>
	
	</channel>
</rss>


